Aizawa Azusa
Age Twenty-Seven
Aizawa Azusa, age 27.
Female. Single. Corporate slave.
All my life, I've lived only for my career.
I set aside love, fun, and everything else
to do nothing but work.
I've worked as long as 50 days in a row.
Whatever happened to the
Labor Standards Act?
Then, one day...
I passed out in the middle of work.
Aizawa-san! Aizawa-san!
Oh, jeez. I just died, didn't I?
Correct.
You worked yourself to death
while still in your twenties.
How very heartbreaking.
I see. So I literally lived
and died for my career...
It might not make up for it,
but I will give you a new life where you
can live in happiness from beginning to end.
You will be free to do nearly
anything however you please!
Sparkle!
Really? Whatever I want?
Yes! I have a soft spot for women, you see.
So... it's okay for a god to be biased?
Yes, it is!
Okay, then, make me immortal and ageless!
Sure!
Wait, it's really just that easy?
That's awesome.
Mana is now going to
circulate throughout you,
reincarnating you into a
body that will never age.
Anything else?
No, that's enough.
My only goal is to live a slow, lazy life.
Very well!
I will reincarnate you as an immortal
in some nice, relaxing highlands.
And I might as well give
you a youthful appearance!
Around age 17, just the way I like it!
There!
Puririn harurun powapowarin!
Definitely highlands...
I Maxed Out My Level
It's not Japanese, but I can read it.
Let's see... "Free to anyone who wants it"?
How generous.
Did that goddess put this here for me?
This is me?
Wow, I really do look 17.
I'm pretty cute.
And what's this outfit?
I kinda look like a witch.
I truly have been reborn.
That corporate slave is gone!
From now on, I am no longer
Aizawa Azusa, but Azusa Aizawa!
And starting today, this is my house!
With that field, I can be self-sufficient.
Hey, there's a village!
I have a weapon, too...
And money!
Maybe I'll go out for a bit...
A slime?
So I really am in an another world, then?
I can beat it, right?
I guess it didn't hurt that much.
Then...
Take that! And that! And that!
Is this... some kind of money?
I said I'd be self-sufficient, but I'll
need money for day-to-day necessities.
I'll just help myself to this.
I guess slimes are pretty common...
Wow...
Haven't seen you around here before.
I just moved into a house in the highlands.
Would you tell me about this village?
This is the village of Flatta.
We have an adventurers' guild.
You should talk to them.
Thank you!
It's not a very big village, but it's pretty.
Welcome to the adventurers' guild!
What sets this village apart
is how peaceful it is.
The only monsters in the area
are things like slimes.
I got these from some slimes
I defeated on my way here.
Those are magic stones.
You need to register with the guild if
you want to exchange them for money.
Is that all right?
Sure.
Please place your hand on this.
Your job is "witch."
You're level 1.
I really am a witch...
Azusa   Aizawa
Job   Witch
Stamina                                 Magic
Attack                                  Speed
Defense                                Intelligence
Magic
None
Special abilities, etc.
Medicinal Plant Knowledge            Immortality due to witch powers
Experience earned
Special abilities... Immortality?!
That's incredible!
There are some witches who
live very long lives,
but immortality at level 1 is remarkable!
Yeah, I guess I'm just lucky...
I won't tell her it was a bonus
that came with being reincarnated.
All set. We're happy to
have you in our guild!
And now I've got a source of income.
That was the day my new, slow life began.
I just take it easy every day,
sleep as much as I want,
tend to my field...
and when I feel like getting some
exercise, I beat up slimes!
They're valuable as my income source,
so I try to defeat at least 25 slimes a day.
I've visited the nearby forest, too.
As a witch, I know right away
which plants have medicinal uses.
I make some medicines occasionally
and sell them in the village.
With just minimal labor
and a nice, easy day-to-day life...
I truly live a life of leisure.
My second life is treating
me fantastically well!
And then, 300 years passed.
And that's 26.
I guess after doing this for 300 years,
I must have leveled up a little...
Oh, the Witch of the Highlands!
Hello.
The medicine you brought
last time worked great.
Glad to hear it!
It has been 300 years.
I know more about this village's
history than anyone else now.
We've been through a lot.
I examined emergency patients and
treated them with my medicines...
I even stopped the spread of a plague.
And now they all treat me
like a guardian deity.
Not that it bothers me at all.
Hello!
That's 5,200 gold for you.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow, then.
Say, Witch of the Highlands...
What is it?
There's something I've been
wondering for a while.
Just how strong are you now?
How strong? Like in battle?
Likely not all that strong...
I've registered as an adventurer,
but I've never been on an adventure.
Would you mind letting me
take a look at your stats?
Now that you mention it, they haven't
been checked in 300 years...
But you've been protecting
Flatta all this time,
so I bet your stats are through the roof!
Fine with me, but I'm really just a witch
with knowledge of medicinal plants.
Don't get your hopes up.
Azusa   Aizawa
Job   Witch
Stamina                                 Magic
Attack                                  Speed
Defense                                Intelligence
Magic
Special abilities, etc.
Medicinal Plant Knowledge            Immortality due to witch powers
Experience Boost
Experience earned
Teleportation        ■Float■       Blaze    Tornado        Item Appraisal
Earthquake      Freeze     Lightning   Mind Control   Remove Curse Remove Poison
Reflect Magic   Mana Absorption Language Comprehension Transform Create Magic
Level 99?!
You're seriously way too strong!
Nah, this thing's just broken.
I mean, I've never beaten
anything but slimes.
Experience earned
There's no way I can have
10,840,086 experience points.
No, hang on!
You've been defeating slimes every single day,
365 days a year, for 300 years, right?
Well, yeah. I average about 25 per day.
And then there's this!
You have a special ability that boosts
the experience points you earn!
That means you get two additional experience
points for every monster you defeat.
Just two?
Slimes are worth two experience points,
but with this ability, that becomes four.
Which means...
Four times 25 times 365 times
300 equals 10,950,000!
I know they say slow and
steady wins the race, but...
A large dragon is said to be
worth 2,500 experience points,
so that's 4,380 dragons
worth of experience points!
I'm a super dragon killer, then!
It's insane!
This has to make you the strongest
adventurer in the world!
What? The whole world?
I always knew the Witch of the
Highlands was truly a great witch!
D'oh!
You're kidding...
If people find out about this and
I get more and more famous...
My slow life is over!
Natalie, you can't tell a
single soul about this!
Why not? I want to glorify
you as much as you deserve!
My stats are personal information.
You wouldn't want the size of your
breasts getting out, would you?
I'm quite confident in their size, though.
Boing!
Flat...
Anyway...
Please don't tell anyone about my stats.
I just want to live a quiet, secretive life.
You got it!
I swear I'll never tell anyone that
you're the strongest there is!
I would never do anything
to betray your trust!
Level 99? I just can't believe it.
How can numbers like that be possible
just from beating slimes daily?
Freeze everything solid!
It's true...
There.
Freeze solid!
I didn't even realize I'd learned
this magic, but it's super handy.
And I can just use fire magic to thaw it.
Can I help you?
You are Azusa, the Witch
of the Highlands, yes?
Yes, that's right.
What would adventurers
like you want with me?
I would like to test my skills against you.
Huh?
I'm just a witch who ekes out a
living gathering medicinal plants.
What point is there in fighting me?
I was told that a level 99 witch lived here.
Gulp!
You're mistaken!
The panel just brought up some weird
numbers because it was broken.
My actual strength is around
level 10 at best...
No, more like level 3...
It's no use trying to lie.
The mana is practically gushing
forth from your body!
There's no doubt that
you're incredibly strong!
All right. I'll spar with you.
But on one condition!
If I win, you have to tell everyone that the
Witch of the Highlands was no big deal.
I'd really rather not
fight if I can avoid it.
If you leave this circle, you lose.
Anyone who steps outside
it is out of the fight.
If everyone in your party
leaves it, you lose.
Now, begin!
Wind, be my servant and
blow with all your might!
Oh, so that's how you use tornado magic.
Keep it weak... as weak as possible...
Wind, be my servant and
blow with all your might.
No way!
Run!
She's a monster!
Natalie!
Oh, Witch of the Highlands.
Didn't you promise me you
wouldn't tell anyone?!
I swear I told no one!
Then how...
It was me!
Who's that?!
You're Ernst, the adventurer who's
notorious for being loose-lipped!
Were you sitting at that
table back then, too?
I couldn't believe the witch was level 99.
So the rumor was true?!
I saw her incredible magic with my own eyes!
She's definitely level 99!
That's how the Witch of the
Highlands maxed out her level.
And when that got around...
Um... What can I do for you?
You are the strongest of witches?
...a dragon came to see me.
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
I am the most powerful dragon
in the province of Nanterre.
My name is Laika.
I have heard rumors that the
strongest of witches resided here.
You're not gonna tell me you want to
test your strength against me, are you?
You've saved me the trouble of asking.
Gloom...
How far has that stupid rumor spread?!
At least limit it to humans!
I have no desire to be
known as the strongest.
I just want to live here quietly.
You can have the title of the strongest.
I cannot accept that! Fight me!
We must settle this matter
beyond a shadow of a doubt!
This is a royal pain in the ass.
And if I refuse?
I will rampage.
Okay, fine. I don't want
my house to get wrecked.
Let's do this.
Remember, I never claimed to
be the strongest anything,
so if I turn out to be a
lot weaker, go easy on me.
Very well.
I am only concerned with proving
that I am the strongest.
I now bid a brief farewell to the earth.
Ah, truly the skills of a witch.
But do not assume you are my equal
simply because you can fly.
Freeze everything solid!
It appears that you truly are
a witch of high caliber.
But it matters not how
advanced your magic is!
Take this!
You will not escape!
Freeze everything solid!
How was that? Feeling a little brain freeze?
W-Wait!
Don't tear up my house!
Don't you dare tear it up!
It's so cold...
I told you...
not to wreck my house!
Wh-What power...
How could I suffer such a humiliating loss?
So, Laika the dragon,
make sure you fix my house, okay?
Because if you don't...
I'll make you regret it.
V-Very well... I will take care of it.
Um... I have a fair amount of money
stored in the mountain where I live.
May I go and retrieve it?
Fine, but if you run away on me...
Rest assured, I will keep my promise!
Guess I'll stay in the
village for a while...
Oh, it's the witch!
I heard you defeated a dragon!
We saw it fleeing!
Sorry... I did defeat the dragon,
but my house was destroyed.
Is it all right if I stay here for a while?
Flatta Village Office
Wow, nice...
But isn't this a guest room?
I'd be fine with a room at the inn.
Oh, my, no!
You're the great witch who protected
our village from a terrible dragon.
Please use this room as you'd like.
Um, Great Witch...
When I was a child,
your medicine saved my life.
There are many people in this village
who've been saved thanks to you.
Well, I guess it can't hurt to take advantage
of people's kindness now and then.
Okay!
Good evening!
Restaurant: The Keen Eagle
Welcome.
The Witch of the Highlands!
A toast to the witch!
Cheers!
I'll take my usual omelette,
and a beef stew.
The omelettes here are just the best!
And we feel "the best"
with you protecting us.
The great witch rules!
Aw...
Oh, well.
Cheers to Flatta Village!
Cheers!
Last night was awesome.
It actually made me glad I'm a witch.
I'm sorry to interrupt your rest.
There's someone here who
says they wish to see you.
Huh?
I'm very sorry for the
trouble I caused yesterday!
Yesterday? Um, have we met somewhere?
Oh, right. This is the first time
you've seen me in this form.
I am Laika, the Red Dragon
you met yesterday.
What?!
We members of the dragon
race can change our forms.
I've brought the money
that I had been saving.
Thanks!
This should be more than
enough to repair my house.
A-Also, um...
The truth is, I would like to ask a favor...
What is it?
M-May I...
May I be your pupil?!
Huh? Pupil?
Yes! Fighting you made me realize
that I still have much to learn!
I'd like to cast away the vain notion
that I am the strongest in Nanterre
and start studying from square one!
Your gung-ho attitude is fantastic,
but I didn't get strong by
doing any special training!
I just made a habit of beating up the
local slimes, and this is what happened!
I overestimated my powers as a dragon,
growing too proud and neglecting
the need to polish my skills.
And that resulted in my humiliating defeat!
So it is your diligent day-to-day
efforts that I wish to learn from!
Industrious much?!
Please allow me to live
with you as a worker!
I want to learn your way of life!
A live-in worker?
Does that mean you'd cook
and clean for me, too?
Yes, of course! With pleasure!
This might just add another
layer of ease to my slow life!
Very well. I will accept you as my pupil.
Thank you!
By the way, how old are you?
I was born about 300 years ago.
Same as me, then...
Is something wrong?
I was just thinking, even after it's fixed up,
it might be too small for two people.
Maybe we should expand it a bit.
In that case, since I'm here,
why don't I build it?
Build it? You're not an architect, are you?
As long as I have wood and stones,
all that remains is to put them
together. Please, allow me!
How to Build a Log House,
Laika's Way
Now, then...
Bring lots of wood
from the forest
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Skillfully strip the bark
from the wood
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup...
Carry the building materials efficiently
Hi-yah!
Finally, put it all together
Et cetera
Hey!
Why don't we wrap up for the day?
Let's head back to the village.
Actually, Lady Azusa, I'm not tired.
I can keep going.
Dragons can see in the dark, so if I work
all night, I can finish by morning.
Laika...
That kind of thing is a hard no!
Um... Did I say something wrong?
Laika, you just said you'd
work all night, didn't you?
You can't do that. Absolutely not!
I just... wanted to show
you how hard I can work...
It's not good to overuse the phrase
"work hard" in a positive light!
Look. See how it's getting dark?
That's the world telling you that
you've done enough for today.
If nothing else, I didn't get strong
by pushing myself too hard.
I just put in a moderate
amount of effort every day.
Now that you're my pupil, I want
you to uphold that lifestyle.
I understand.
I will do as you say, Lady Azusa.
Good.
From now on, if you're tired
or just can't keep going,
don't hesitate to say so.
Your consideration toward
your pupil touches my heart.
Aren't you being a bit dramatic?
Um, it's finished now.
Does it please you?
Yeah! It's amazing!
You did it, Laika!
I-If it pleases you, Lady Azusa,
I could not be happier.
Okay!
Let's go, Laika! Today we
celebrate in the village!
Thus, 300 years after I reincarnated
and became a witch,
my life with my very first pupil began.
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level