Amazing! It happened so quickly,
my eyes couldn't keep up!
Well, I have been beating up
slimes for 300 years now.
And how many slimes did you defeat
each day to get so strong?
Like... 25?
Oh, but I have an ability that
increases the experience I earn,
so it actually comes out to about 50 a day.
It sounds like you had it easier I expected.
I thought you would say you worked
hard enough to sweat blood.
Laika, you need to throw away
those kinds of thoughts.
What? Why?
Because if you're working
hard enough to sweat blood,
it means you know people are watching you.
So you've probably been using that
expression with the intention of boasting.
Wh-When you put it that way...
Anyway, you just keep steadily
plugging along every day.
Looking at any activity that way
makes it easier to keep it up,
and you'll level up naturally along the way.
Such meaningful, priceless words...
I will fully dedicate myself to
reaching your level one day!
It's not like the slimes are
ever gonna try to get revenge.
Let's just keep mowing them down!
Witch of the Highlands...
You shall pay dearly.
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
Along Came the Daughters
Lady Azusa, I shall prepare
our meal for today!
Okay, I guess I'll leave you to it.
I didn't know dragons could cook, though.
Of course. Dragons are
one of the noble races.
Cooking is but a simple task!
Dun!
Da-dun!
This is my finest creation.
Please, help yourself!
Shine!
I do enjoy omelettes...
But I think you might've
used a few too many eggs.
This is way too much for two people.
I'm so sorry!
I just can't cast aside
my values as a dragon!
I see. Well, let's eat
it before it gets cold.
Right...
Let's eat.
This is great!
I gotta be honest! You're fantastic, Laika!
Thank you!
In that case, I'll make it every day!
Nah, we'll rotate. I'll do
my share of cooking, too.
You can show off your skills
when it's your day.
Okay! I'll give it my all, then, too!
Laika, if there's anything you want to
know about the life we live, just ask.
Well... there is one thing,
about that village.
About Flatta?
Yes. Its magic defense is extremely weak.
Just one evil mage could reduce
it to a sea of flames in moments.
Yeah, but wouldn't that be
true pretty much anywhere?
It's not only that.
It has no measures in place to
deal with land-based attacks.
If large monsters attacked en masse,
it wouldn't stand a chance.
I think you might be overthinking this...
But the news of your strength just
recently became widely known, yes?
Some vile fiend could take the whole
village hostage just to get rid of you!
I get it... But it's not like I
can guard them around the clock.
But there is something we can do.
A DIY barrier?
One of your many skills
is Create Magic, right?
You can use it to make a
barrier around the village.
If you want it to have a long-term effect,
the best way is to draw a magic circle.
Wow, you dragons know a
lot about magic, huh?
I learned about it when I went
to an all-girls school...
All-girls school?!
All right, it's done.
I'll give it a shot, then.
You who have wicked hearts,
be caught in this net and
become incapacitated!
Did it work?
Yes, they should be fine now.
What is it?
I don't know... I just have
this foreboding feeling...
This thief who entered the
village suddenly can't move.
Lady Azusa, it's already working!
What could have happened?
Lady Azusa put a barrier over
the village just moments ago!
Oh! At last, the debate over
village safety measures
that has plagued us for
many long years is over!
Everyone, listen!
Thanks to the great witch,
this village will be even more peaceful!
Please, Headman, that's not necessary.
If you're going to praise someone...
You should praise Laika.
Huh?
It was my pupil, Laika the Dragon,
who suggested putting up the barrier.
N-No, it was none other than Lady
Azusa who erected the barrier!
I did nothing!
A dragon?
The dragon you defeated before, Great Witch?
Yeah. Laika became my pupil a few days ago.
She's a very nice, thoughtful girl,
so treat her well, okay?
My name is Laika.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
No wonder! The Great Witch's
pupil is bound to be special!
This village is gonna be
even nicer to live in now!
Having a good-hearted dragon on our
side gives us the strength of an army!
I'm so glad you're here now, Laika.
You do such a good job with the chores,
and you make such tasty meals for us.
I have also learned a great
deal from you, Lady Azusa.
I hope we can keep living
this easy life forever.
A little girl?
Hi there. Can I help you?
I've been dying to see you, Mama!
Lady Azusa?
Mama, are you okay?
Do we have a visitor?
I'm Falfa! I came to see my mama!
Lady Azusa has a child?
No, I don't! This kid's mistaken!
I'm not mistaken!
So your name's Falfa?
"Mama" is what you'd call the woman
who gave birth to you and raised you.
You gave birth to me, Mama!
They call you the
Witch of the Highlands, right?
I know 'cause my little
sister looked into it!
You have a little sister, too?!
W-Well, it does make sense that you'd have
a love child or two after living 300 years.
I have learned so much from you, Lady Azusa!
You don't need to learn that!
Anyway, Mama, there's trouble!
My little sister's trying to kill you!
Someone wants to kill me?!
This just turned into a suspense story.
I don't want you to die, Mama.
That's why I'm here.
Lady Azusa, we should let her in
and hear what she has to say.
I guess so.
Want to come in and have
some cookies, Falfa?
Yeah! I'd love some!
Now that I look closer,
she does kinda look like
me when I was little...
Actually, no, she doesn't.
Yay!
Time to eat!
So... can you tell me your
little sister's name?
It's Shalsha.
Then is this Shalsha... my child, too?
That's right.
But why would she want to kill Lady Azusa?
I think she's holding a grudge against Mama,
since Mama killed her and all.
My slow life just took an occultish turn...
I still don't understand all the details,
but in any case, I believe we need
to protect you from this Shalsha.
You're right.
Falfa, do you know how she
might try to attack me?
Hmm...
Shalsha was always studying
Smite Evil magic.
Smite Evil?
Isn't that a really powerful type of
magic that only works on certain races?
Yes, including...
humans,
orcs,
and elves.
The more specific its target is,
the stronger its effects are.
So if you said, "Smite Evil: Living Thing,"
it wouldn't do much at all?
Yes, but it's said that it takes
several decades to learn the spell.
How long have you two been alive?
Hmm... About 50 years?
Which means they're not just normal humans.
In that case, there's a chance she
could be a powerful magic user.
But what Smite Evil spell
would specifically target me?
Shalsha!
I've finally found you.
That's Shalsha?
What an ominous aura...
Shalsha!
Don't be mean to Mama!
I will avenge my death.
Shalsha, there's no way
I could have killed you!
You're—
You have killed countless slimes.
Huh? Slimes? What do you mean?
The two of us are made up of the
souls of the slimes that you killed.
We're basically slime spirits.
Slime spirits?!
I will kill you so that
all slimes can rest in peace.
But there's no way I can fight a child...
Lady Azusa, why don't you use your
tornado magic and see what happens?
If she's a spirit, there's no risk of
killing her with a little tornado.
Well, I guess we're not
getting anywhere now.
Might as well try it.
Wind, be my servant and
blow with all your might!
Tornado...
Disappear.
That's the Smite Evil spell?
But how can it be powerful enough
to erase Lady Azusa's power?
Many years of training to defeat you
allowed me to perfect this spell.
Smite Evil: Witch of the Highlands!
"Smite Evil: Witch of the Highlands"?!
O-Of course.
The more specific Smite Evil's target
is, the stronger its effects are.
If it's specific enough to
target Lady Azusa alone...
It will negate any magic you try to use.
Seriously?
Go ahead. Use any magic spell you'd like.
Red flame...
Blue flame...
Black flame! Become my power!
Y-You're kidding!
Shalsha's been
saving up her strength for this day
ever since she was born 50 years ago.
Even though a spell that consumes
as much mana as Smite Evil
only lasts an hour...
That's so ineffective!
This isn't good.
She's only after me,
so Laika and Falfa won't be harmed.
In my past life,
I died of exhaustion when I couldn't
escape the corporate slave lifestyle.
So I know this feeling firsthand.
When times are tough...
You run!
Magic, disappear.
Huh?!
Whoa, wait!
Ow...
Hey! That's dangerous!
If I wasn't a level 99 witch,
I might've broken some bones!
You will not escape.
I will kill you, just like
you killed all those slimes.
Lady Azusa!
Mama!
Then again...
Maybe it's high time I paid the piper.
I've lived for 300 years already.
I'm glad I met you two.
Don't talk like that!
Prepare to die.
Mama!
Laika?!
I will not allow you to
come one step closer!
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
Step aside, Dragon.
I will not! I have a duty
to protect my master!
Then I will not hold back.
Stop, Laika!
Dragon Punch!
Ouch.
Poke, poke.
Lady Azusa, she has lost consciousness.
I... have won.
What?!
My little sister, Shalsha,
focused too specifically
on magic targeting you,
so I guess she's really
weak against anyone else.
What a little klutz!
Oh, Shalsha!
Where am I?
You're in my house.
Witch of the Highlands!
You were unconscious after losing to Laika,
so we brought you here.
I asked for no such pity!
Smite Evil: Witch of the Highlands!
I think you already used up all your magic.
You won't be able to use Smite
Evil again for decades.
Shock!
But... I have lived solely to get revenge
on the Witch of the Highlands...
What has my entire life been for?
Actually, isn't it a good
thing that I'm still alive?
If I was dead, you'd have
no reason to live anymore,
but as long as I don't die,
you can still have your goal
to get revenge on me, right?
One could put it that way...
Mama took care of you.
Why would you do that for me?
Well, I'm the mother who gave
birth to you, aren't I?
So I can't just leave you injured.
You could indeed be called my mother,
but you are still the one
who killed the slimes...
Shalsha, stop being so stubborn.
Big Sister...
It's nature's way for slimes
and humans to fight.
No matter how much you hate Mama,
all kinds of people around the
world are killing slimes.
Just listen closely, and you'll
hear their screams, even now.
Wow, that's scary.
Anyway, you can't hold a grudge against
everyone who's ever killed a slime.
More importantly...
Since we were lucky enough to be born,
we should think about how
we can live happily.
That'll be more fun, don't you think?
All right.
It appears this issue has been resolved.
Yeah. I wasn't sure what was
gonna happen for a while there.
By the way, where do you two live?
In a shack in the forest that
no one ever comes near.
Anyone else live there?
No.
I see.
Then you should both live here.
Huh?
There are lots of rooms here.
Besides, it makes sense for a mother
and her kids to live together, right?
Yeah! I wanna live with you, Mama!
Okay, Shalsha?
Witch of the Highlands...
Don't call me that. Make it
sound like we're family.
M-Mother...
I will live with you, as well.
Okay, then, it's settled!
Lady Azusa, why don't we have
a welcome party tonight?
Good idea!
Okay, let's all go buy stuff for dinner!
Yes!
Yeah!
Yeah...
By the way, what did you two
do before you came here?
We got rid of evil slimes.
Evil slimes?
There are both good slimes and evil slimes.
Um, I just want to make sure...
It's okay to kill slimes, right?
Sure, it's fine!
It never bothered me,
and Shalsha seems to be okay with it now.
The slimes of Nanterre are
typically dark-colored...
But the ones here are quite pale.
Light-colored slimes are evil slimes.
They should be eliminated.
R-Really? How informative.
Also, slimes have a hole
that's their weak spot!
You are already dead!
Jab!
See?
They truly are slime spirits!
That's the baker,
and next door is the tailor.
Remember all this so you won't get
lost when you run errands here.
Okay, Mama! I've got it all down pat!
Really?
Okay, how many of the shops on
the main street can you name?
The sixth building from the village's
south entrance is Noelis Shoes,
and the next one is Meitz Dairy.
The fifth building was a general store
until a year ago, but now it's vacant.
The next one, Kant's Store,
sells seeds and farm equipment.
Oh, and the owner threw out
their back the other day.
That's too much detail!
What about you, Shalsha? You seemed
quite curious about lots of things.
That slightly wider street
is the old highway.
If you look closely, you can see
remnants of when it was a shrine road.
The area around it used to be a
checkpoint in the old kingdom.
They are definitely your
daughters, Lady Azusa!
They're so intelligent!
I think this goes far beyond that.
Let's eat!
Big Sis Laika, this omelette is really good!
Delicious.
I'm so glad to hear that.
It means my extra effort was worth it.
But...
I'm so sorry! I've made too much again!
Nah, our family has two more members now.
This is perfect!
What's wrong, you two?
You don't like it?
Mama, do we have to eat the celery, too?
I don't like celery, either.
Okay, if you eat it,
you can have some chiffon cake later.
Very good! You shouldn't
be picky with your food.
What? Did you leave your celery, too, Laika?
A-A-Actually, there's a rule within my
clan that we must never eat celery!
Laika, it's not good to lie to your master.
I-I'm so sorry! I'll eat it!
Why must celery taste like this?
Good job!
Living my slow life alone was nice,
but I think I prefer having a more
lively place to come home to.
After killing slimes for 300 years,
I gained one pupil
and two daughters.
Mama!
The two of us can share a room!
Not a problem.
Then we can take in more family members.
We have a dragon and spirits,
so should an elf be next?
Or perhaps a demon?
Well...
I guess a slow life with a big
family is nice in its own way.