My life has suddenly become
a lot more lively.
The reason couldn't be clearer:
because we're a family of four now.
Shall we read a book, Big Sister?
Sure!
I love the books you read
to me! They're so fun!
Then let's read Lauretta's History of
the Rise and Fall of the Elvish People: Vol. 3,
chapter 5, passage 2,
the commercial policy failures of the
Clar Dynasty of the province of Hrant.
That's way too specialized!
The private army of Kranke, the first ruler
of the Clar Dynasty, grew so mighty
that it attained the status of a military
clique among the elves of Hrant.
Eventually, in the year 405,
he declared himself king.
Elves, huh? I've never met an elf.
Boing!
Tight!
Um...
It's an elf.
And what can I do for you?
Um, someone is after me...
and I was hoping the Witch of
the Highlands could help me.
I bet I can guess who
would go after an elf...
Are there any orcs around here?
It's not orcs!
I want you to save me from
the high demon Beelzebub!
I'm not home right now.
Wait! I'm begging you!
I don't know of anyone who could help
me but the Witch of the Highlands!
I don't want to fight a monster that scary!
Please don't say that! I heard
you're incredibly strong!
I refuse!
I'm begging you, Most Powerful,
Berserk, Wonderful, Strong Witch!
Don't give me weird names that
make me sound like a wrestler!
Bzzz...
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
Along Came an Elf
I came here from a small nation of
elves in the province of Hrant.
I'm Halkara the apothecary.
Apothecary?
It's someone who makes medicines.
That's similar to my line of work.
Yes, witches make medicines, as well.
I specialize in plants, though.
Well, now we know what you do for a living,
but why would Beelzebub want
to go after an apothecary?
The truth is, I'm one of the
highest-paid apothecaries.
I collected components of mushrooms and
plants with exceptional nutritional value
to make an alcoholic drink
called Nutri-Spirit.
Nutri-Spirit?
When you're tired,
just one bottle of this...
...clears your mind!
...strengthens your body!
Halkara's Nutri-Spirit!
It'll get you through your tough job!
Hustle charge!
It's just an energy drink.
Sure, I had a lot of them when
I pulled all-nighters, but...
Nutri-Spirit became popular everywhere,
making it an explosive hit.
I even started a factory in town,
but production still couldn't keep up.
It's just that successful and profitable!
Yeah, I got that.
And why is Beelzebub after you?
Apparently, she acquired some and drank it,
but it seems to be poisonous to demons.
After drinking it, she passed
out with a high fever
and nearly ended up going straight to Hell.
A demon... going to Hell?
So you're saying Beelzebub is
holding a grudge over that.
That's right.
She's been fuming that she'll kill
"whoever made this vile poison."
It got me chased out of my own town!
I have nowhere to go anymore!
Please! You have to help me!
Mama, I feel so bad for the elf lady.
I can't bear to see someone
with no home to go back to.
All right. I'll help y—
Thank you so much!
You changed your tune quick!
But I have no intention
of fighting Beelzebub!
I'll only shelter you!
When you go out, wear this robe.
The story is that you're the second
pupil of Azusa, Witch of the Highlands.
Thank you, Master!
Boom!
Boing!
I'm sorry... It's just a bit tight on me...
This might not work.
Halkara, has anyone ever told
you that you're very well-developed?
About 750 times a year or so...
That's about twice a day!
Bzzz...
You who have wicked hearts,
be caught in this net and
become incapacitated.
This net will fall upon you as
if it has a will of its own.
There. That doesn't look too bad.
Now Beelzebub won't be able to get in.
Thank you so much!
Let's eat!
Um, is something wrong?
When I was busy with work,
I ate out all the time,
and when I was being chased, I survived
on tree nuts I found in the forest.
It's been so long since I had a warm
meal like this with anyone else...
Cheer up, Halkara!
Halkara, have some of this
raspberry jam. It's my favorite.
Thank you so much!
Sorry to have you gather
medicinal herbs with me.
I bet the ones around here are
different from yours, huh?
Yes, they are.
Ah! Here we go!
A dawn king mushroom!
This one's a greater round mushroom.
And these are rolling rat mushrooms!
You're only picking mushrooms...
Well, mushrooms are my specialty!
Please be very careful.
Some of these are poison mushrooms
that are dangerous to eat raw.
But take this one, for example...
If you boil it for about ten minutes,
the poisons break down and disappear!
Then you can use them for cooking!
Wow...
By the way, the poison gives
you a warm, fuzzy feeling,
so connoisseurs leave a bit
in them when cooking them.
That mushroom's borderline insane!
This herb-gathering was way more
productive than I expected!
Thanks!
Not at all. I'm glad you
had such a good time.
Oh, looks like the small ones are ready.
This called elvin sauce.
It's made by fermenting
several types of beans.
It smells like soy sauce.
This is good!
It is soy sauce!
Please eat all you'd like.
I had no idea there were
so many edible mushrooms!
We elves don't live in
the forest for nothing.
I'd love to teach the villagers how to make
optimal use of the forest's bounties, too.
That's a nice idea!
I need to get my daughters
and Laika to try it, too!
I'll be glad to provide all
the guidance you need!
Come on, you're laughing a little too much.
You're right... But I just can't stop!
Wait...
Halkara, are those poison
mushrooms you're eating?
What are you talking about?
I'm a mushroom expert!
Striped wave mushrooms don't contain poison.
Orange pencil mushrooms don't
contain poison, either.
Triangular chestnut mushrooms
do contain poison!
You did have a poisonous one in the mix!
You're right!
I put one from the
medicinal-use zone in here!
Your sorting method's too careless!
That's one I haven't eaten yet.
That's a silver lining, I guess.
I did eat one...
What symptoms does it cause?
It stimulates your mind and body
so you laugh uncontrollably...
And... it works as an aphrodisiac, too...
Huh? Aphrodisiac?
That means it temporarily
makes you feel very lewd.
Huh?
Why are you moving away, Master?
Because I suspect you're
full of poison right now!
Master...
Jiggle, jiggle...
Would you like to do something fun with me?
Actually... please do it...
No way!
Don't worry. I promise
it'll make you feel good.
That's not what I'm worried about!
Please...
Ta-da!
Um... What happened while you
two were gathering herbs?
Oh, stuff.
I neutralized the poison with magic, though.
I made a careless mistake...
I'm sorry. Please don't ask questions.
Accept these mushroom dishes as my apology.
Yummy!
It's wonderfully seasoned.
This is delicious!
Isn't it?!
Striped wave mushrooms puff up
when you wrap them before cooking!
They're the best!
You bounced back quick!
Our cooking repertoire will
expand with you here, Halkara.
Thank you so much!
Bzzz...
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
Master, you're so quick at defeating slimes.
I've been doing it for 300 years.
Okay, Halkara, give it a try.
Yah!
Bob!
Boing!
Tch.
Yah!
I managed to defeat it.
Wow, check it out...
Thank you for this blessing.
So... do you always get stared at this much?
Oh...
It's sort of my fate.
You should have more confidence,
too, even if you're small.
I-I'm not that small!
But...
It does seem curious that there are
more women staring at you, too.
Oh, an adventurer put that up this morning.
Oh, dear...
A "wanted" notice?
The reward for it is quite generous, isn't it?
I guess those who have it, have it...
and those who don't... don't.
I do all kinds of mundane
tasks, day in and day out!
"Searching for a female apothecary
in the province of Hrant
who makes a product called Nutri-Spirit.
Maybe I should become an adventurer, too...
Goes by the name Halkara.
She is currently on the run from Hrant.
Most notable physical feature:
her very large chest.
Reward of 15 million gold for
the one who captures her.
Posted by the demon Beelzebub."
She's already made her move...
At least we have the lack of a physical
description going in our favor...
But it's just a matter of
time before she comes here.
Laika, can you evacuate my daughters
to some village far from here?
Of course.
Mother, I want to fight with you.
Thank you.
Your willingness alone is enough.
But...
Shalsha, don't make things
difficult for Mama.
You might think what you're saying
makes you a good daughter,
but that's not what being
a good daughter means.
Okay, Big Sister. I understand.
Good girl, Shalsha!
Thanks, you two.
Now, we must hurry.
I will revert to my dragon form
at once and take them away.
Right.
I hope the barrier I put up
this morning keeps her away.
Bzzz...
Please don't let anything happen...
Having Nutri-Spirit on hand makes
me feel like I can fight all night!
I can't believe you can drink
that at a time like this.
The whole concept of my medicine-making
is to make things I'd
want to consume myself.
You're drinking it yourself,
aren't you, Master?
Huh? No, I haven't had any.
Huh?
But look.
I really didn't have any.
Also, Halkara, did you eat dinner?
What? No, I didn't.
Th-This is a joke, right?
I wouldn't joke at a time like this.
Bzzz...
Hey...
Yes?
Beelzebub is a fly, right?
Bzzz...
Yes, she's also known as
the Lord of the Flies.
I'm just wondering here, but...
C-Certainly not!
That's just a filthy little fly!
It's a lowly creature that
swarms around horse poop!
There's no way it's a
terrifying demon like...
Who are you calling a lowly creature?
Master, don't start doing
crazy voice impersonations!
I didn't say anything.
Then whose voice was that?
Mine!
My name is Beelzebub.
Excuse me for being nothing
but a lowly creature.
"Lowly creature" was just
a figure of speech!
I am but a speck of dust!
I had no intention of saying such a
thing about a great being like you!
It is that speck of dust
that I came here to find.
You've been hiding out in this
house all along, haven't you?
Of course.
I've been making myself at
home since she arrived.
Why didn't you reveal yourself right away?
I wanted to make sure this
woman truly was Halkara.
Also, flying around in houses
in the form of a fly
is my favorite way to spend
my extended vacations.
That's pretty unique!
Halkara, I went through
great pains to find you,
but it was very much worth it.
Please spare me! I'll do anything!
Oh?
Anything, you say?
That is what my ears heard.
All dealings with my pupil will
have to be made through me.
Master!
Witch of the Highlands,
you intend to stand in my way?
My pupil doesn't seem
interested in seeing you.
I'll have to ask you to leave.
When told to leave, it is only natural
that I want to leave even less.
Or... do you wish to fight me?
That's perfect.
I haven't fought in so long,
I was starting to get rusty.
Let's fight fair and square.
My thoughts exactly.
I suppose I'll go over there, too.
Are you sure about this? A mere human
is bound to regret defying me!
I will show you just how terrifying
the power of a high demon is—
Oh, the barrier.
Oh, no!
Did you not say we would
fight fair and square?!
What was that?!
Uh, I mean...
I didn't think it would work when
you tried to leave, too... uh...
Sorry.
You think apologizing will help?!
Honestly, talk about raining on my parade...
I challenge you...
Uh, aren't you exhausted already?
Please! This is nothing!
I feel ill...
And I'm having chills...
and I feel a bit nauseous...
I... can't...
Whoa, whoa!
Huh? What happened?
Halkara, help me out!
Master, what are you doing?
Making healing magic.
Huh?!
God of the earth, it is not yet known
whether your chaotic power is good or evil.
Grant that power unto me now.
Wait...
Hey, is healing magic...
something you can use on a demon?
Huh? I think... it should be fine...
Okay! If it's not, I blame you!
That's too heavy a burden to bear!
Her color looks a bit better!
All right! We're gonna keep doing this!
Master, she's awake!
Beelzebub, you okay?
Yes, the nausea has subsided.
And the chills are gone.
Thank goodness!
You just need to rest for a while now.
Witch of the Highlands,
I thought you were a coward,
but you are quite the remarkable woman.
If you died on me because of that,
I'd regret it for centuries.
Once I recover, I'd like to
drink your Nutri-Spirit again.
Huh?
But if you do, it might
almost kill you again!
What are you talking about?
I heard that you developed a high fever
and nearly died after drinking it...
Ah...
I drank it during an all-nighter,
and it filled me with the drive to work.
I took it too far and overworked myself,
which caused me to break out in a fever,
but only because I put too
much stress on my body.
Huh?
Your Nutri-Spirit is loved
not only by the Devil himself,
but by all demons.
Which is why I came to ask
you to make some more.
S-So that's what you wanted...
That's all? What a relief!
Hey.
I'm sorry!
Let's eat!
I'm so relieved that it
was a misunderstanding.
I made another careless mistake...
Well, I'm just glad I didn't
end up fighting for no reason.
That's great, Halkara!
Now you can make Nutri-Spirit again.
Oh, about that..
I was thinking of relocating
my factory to this province.
Moving it here? Why?
Because even if it was all a mistake,
I don't want to pay exorbitant taxes
to the town that abandoned me.
Reality!
Also... if I stay here, I can
live with you, Master...
Well, we still have rooms, so that's fine...
But we all take turns doing
the cooking and cleaning.
Of course! I'll work hard!
That sounds rather fun.
Beelzebub?!
What are you doing here?
Witch of the Highlands, Azusa...
I have yet to settle my score with you.
Next time, we'll fight without the barrier.
Uh-huh...
Of course, if you do anything else
that's fun, you must invite me!
I'll teach you a spell to summon me later.
Okay...
Beelzebub.
Have some tea!
Indeed.
Beelzebub, can we ask you something?
Ask me anything.
What is the current state of demon society?
The same dynasty has persisted
for several centuries.
It is quite peaceful.
Are you married?
D-Don't ask silly questions!
Only races that age quickly do such things!
Say... I'd like to adopt one of
these two as my own daughter.
I'm honored, but I must decline.
Beelzebub, what kind of life do you live?
Do you live as a fly all the time?
W-Well, you see...
Things have gotten more lively here.
A dragon,
spirits,
an elf,
and a demon, huh?
We're quite a crew, but it's starting
to feel like we're a family...
Maybe.
Amid the bustle, I get to
spend time taking it easy.
I was starting to think this
slow life would last forever...
but then, a problem arose the very next day.
I will be returning to my own home.
Our family's falling apart!