Hey, Master, let's chat about
our romantic experiences!
Got none.
Oh, come on. You must've had
something in 300 years.
None means none.
Since I'm so young, I always
want to talk about love.
Young? How old are you, anyway?
Sparkle!
Seventeen!
And 2,500 months.
You're well over 200 years old!
In elf terms, I'm just hitting my stride!
Falfa and Shalsha, do you
two have anyone you like?
I love Mama!
My answer is the same.
My sweet daughters!
That's not what I meant...
All right, everyone, it's ready now.
Thanks, Laika!
Well, let's get right to it!
Time to eat!
Um, Lady Azusa...
I will be returning to my own home.
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
Laika, you're leaving this house?
But I'll miss you!
Me, too.
Laika, does something bother you or
worry you about the life we live?
No, it's—
I know I'm your master and you're my pupil,
but I think of everyone here as my family!
So don't say you're leaving!
Um, it's not exactly like that.
I'll be attending my older sister's wedding,
so I need to return home for a short time.
Huh? A wedding?
Would you all like to come with me?
Love chat!
We Went to a Dragon's Wedding
And on that note...
We're now headed for Mount Rokko,
the volcano where Laika's family lives.
What a great view, eh, Halkara?
Yes, yes, there you go. There you go.
Yes, that's it. Get all that puke out.
I feel better now.
Are you okay? Don't push yourself too hard.
You really are kind, Master...
I think I actually wouldn't
mind being kissed by you.
Sparkle!
Absolutely not.
Everyone, we'll be arriving shortly.
That's Mount Rokko.
This is the venue for the first party.
Wow! Look at all the dragons!
Biologically speaking, they're Red Dragons.
They're classified as part of the
Dragon clan rather than as monsters.
Greetings, Elder Sister Laika.
Whoa...
Your wings look as beautiful as ever today.
What we need most is not the
wings we were born with.
It is knowing what we wish to improve upon.
You are so wonderful, Elder Sister Laika!
Why do I feel like I'm at
a school for rich girls?
Forgive me, Lady Azusa.
These are my juniors from
the all-girls school I attended.
Juniors from an all-girls school?!
Elder Sister!
Now, allow me to introduce you to my family.
They're all so big!
They are indeed enormous.
Be very careful not to step onto any plates.
Wait, no! No! I'm not food!
I have returned,
Father, Mother.
Welcome home, Laika.
It's good to have you home, my daughter!
Your dad is so cheerful.
Father, there are guests here!
Ah, pardon me.
Our daughter has told us about you.
She hasn't caused any
trouble for you, has she?
No, not at all.
She's actually been a big help.
Laika!
Sister!
You made it!
This is my older sister and her groom.
I am Laika's older sister, Leila.
Congratulations on your wedding.
So how did you two get together?
She really is into love chats...
We were friends as children,
but when we saw each other again after
80 years, we decided to get married.
Eighty years is a heck of a span!
I am glad today has been so peaceful.
I hope the party concludes without incident.
Are you worried something might happen?
Yes. Not all tribes within
the Dragon clan get along.
Sometimes, Dragons from other
clans come to crash our weddings.
I'm pretty sure that was a flag...
So you've come after all...
Blue Dragons!
Cold Breath?!
So cold...
They are the Blue Dragons
of the Heynt province!
They are shameless, barbaric Dragons
that spew their icy breath everywhere!
Red Dragons, I hear you're
celebrating a wedding today.
That pisses us off,
so we're here to torment you!
That one's name is Flatorte.
She is known as the
Bully Queen of the Blue Dragons.
She sounds like a pain in the ass.
The nerve of getting married when
you're barely 300 years old!
I've been single for over 400 years!
That's the most pathetic
reason you could give!
It's not only this party venue
that I'm going to harass.
I've sent a separate force to the volcano.
We'll freeze it solid, too!
Father...
We have no choice. This calls for...
an all-out confrontation!
I'm scared, Mama.
We should get away from here.
Girls, just leave this to your mama.
Halkara, we're running!
Ding...
What are you doing?!
My late grandpa's last words were that if
you run into a dragon, you should play dead.
Okay, I won't play dead anymore!
Mama!
Get down!
Let's move!
Flatorte, I will not tolerate
any further violence!
Shut up, Laika!
You haven't forgotten the fate
of the Dragon tribes, have you?
Then I hope you are prepared.
Bring it on!
We should be safe now.
Laika's fighting her hardest.
That's my pupil for you!
It does irritate me,
but this is their own clan's problem.
An outsider like me shouldn't be butting in.
You are friends of the
Red Dragons, are you not?
And what if we are?
We will hurt you and ruin their wedding!
Mama!
Mother...
Don't you go scaring little
kids like these...
just to be a bully!
Mama, you're amazing!
I respect you so much...
Halkara, take Falfa and
Shalsha somewhere to hide.
Okay, Master! Got it!
I maxed out my level without
even realizing it,
but I'm gonna use this power
to protect my family...
in any way I can!
Laika, can we handle them?
There are far too many of them, even for us.
What?!
Is this...
Lady Azusa!
Damn it!
Wh-What?!
Everyone, fire!
Watch out!
What?!
She took out so many of them alone?
Lady Azusa! Flatorte is behind you!
Just who are you?
How? How is it possible for a human
to physically defeat a dragon?
Rome wasn't built in a day. I guess
that's what it comes down to.
Rome?
It means if you just keep
steadily working at something,
it'll all work out!
Curse you...
I'll freeze you!
Oh, come on.
Is that all you know how to do?!
Take this!
That's hot!
Witch's...
Axe Kick!
Still want to fight?
We're sorry!
Lady Azusa!
Everyone! Lady Azusa has won the battle!
This is the power of the
Witch of the Highlands!
Long live the Witch of the Highlands!
Laika!
It's too soon to declare this finished.
She did say she sent a separate
force to the volcano.
Lady Azusa, please get on my back.
Right!
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
There are hot springs in this town,
so I'm worried that innocent
tourists will be hurt.
At a glance, I don't see
any signs of fighting.
If nothing is happening,
all the better, but still...
I only want my sister's wedding
to be a joyous occasion.
Don't worry. This'll be over soon,
and your sister's wedding will continue.
Right.
What's that?
Lady Azusa...
What is this?!
Blue Dragons?
It's draining their power to weaken them!
This is some pretty underhanded magic.
What brings you two here?
Quite the coincidence,
seeing you here of all places.
Beelzebub!
What are you doing here?
This volcano produces some fine hot springs.
I come here occasionally
to relax and rejuvenate.
Then was this...
Yes, I was strolling around the town,
and I found these fools saying they
were here to harass the place,
so I cast some demon magic that
causes extreme weakness upon them.
You defeated five Blue Dragons by yourself?
I am a high demon who has
lived for 3,000 years.
It's inconceivable that I would lose.
And you, Azusa, cannot begin
to fathom what will happen
the next time you fight me fair and square.
I am strong, after all...
Beelzebub!
You just saved the
Red Dragons from disaster!
Thank you!
Don't hug me!
I didn't do it for you!
I only took down those dragons
because they were acting cocky!
Sniff, sniff.
You smell so nice!
That's because I just got out of the bath.
Wait, forget about that!
Get off of me at once!
I was so scared, Mama!
Mother...
Was the volcano all right?
Yeah.
All thanks to Beelzebub.
Oh, come on. I was only there
to make use of the baths.
Well, I think it's time we finish this,
Falafel Tart.
It's Flatorte! Get my name right!
Fine, I get it. So take
your human form already.
Let's talk.
Is this what you want?
This is the amount you owe in
damages after today's conflict.
We will need you to pay this.
Huh?!
Y-You're making me pay that much?
This covers all expenses,
including treatment for the injured
and inconvenience recompense.
If you refuse, you will never
move from this spot again.
Is that what you want?
I-I don't like that, either...
Fine. I'll accept your conditions.
Good. The negotiations are complete.
But since we're talking, there's one
more thing I'd like to discuss.
I want you to agree to a treaty,
in addition to the damages you're paying.
A treaty?
Yes, a non-aggression treaty between
the Blue Dragons and the Red Dragons.
Of course, coming around to harass
them will be out of the question.
B-But then I would have no reason to live!
If you don't agree, you can
never go back to your homeland.
Do you want to feel like you're stuck at work
for three straight days
with no chance to go home?
Your smile is scaring me!
Then, let's seal this agreement. Okay?
Fine, I agree! I agree!
So please forgive me now...
Okay, the treaty is concluded.
Now, Mount Rokko should have peace.
Lady Azusa...
Thank you for doing all
this for our homeland!
Beelzebub, take care of the rest, okay?
I know.
Ahem.
The Witch of the Highlands and myself have
borne witness to the creation of this treaty.
If either party should
break this agreement...
you know what will happen, yes?
Grovel!
I never should have done this...
Beelzebub, thanks so much for everything!
No one but you would use the
Lord of the Flies in this way.
I'll be counting on you even
more from now on!
Stop hugging me over every little thing!
So everyone takes their human
forms for the second party, huh?
Yes, the second party is
where we all eat our fill!
I'm already full.
Shalsha, you should rest for a bit.
Thanks.
Falfa, you're being such
a good older sister.
Master!
This booze is way too strong!
Halkara, you ate a lot before drinking.
You'd better be careful.
I'll be fine!
I've already puked my guts out today!
That's my point!
Honestly, that elf has nothing going for
her but the Nutri-Spirit she makes.
Lady Azusa.
Wow...
Leila, you look beautiful!
We were able to continue the
ceremony thanks to all of you.
We are grateful.
Oh, no... all I did was lend a little hand.
It's good to see you know your place.
If you will continue to idolize me this way,
I would be glad to offer
my assistance again.
Beelzebub, don't act so high-and-mighty.
Well, can you blame me?
I am high and mighty.
I'm happy for you, Laika.
You've made such wonderful friends.
Now you won't be lonely
when I'm no longer around.
Sister...
I truly congratulate you.
Thank you, Laika.
Sister—
Leila, may I?
Regarding our plans after this...
So... Leila...
Congratulations.
You'd better live in happiness.
Flatorte...
I was defeated this time.
Having lost, I give you
my sincerest blessings.
This Blue Dragon does have her
good points, doesn't she?
Thank you.
I'll live in happiness for you, as well,
since you can't marry.
Why did you have to say it like that?!
It's not that I can't!
I'm just not going to!
What's this? Did you not come
here to give me your blessing?
Hmph! I hope you get divorced right away!
Red Dragons and Blue Dragons have
a complicated relationship.
This little scene kinda
gave me that impression.
Whew, I ate so much. And it was all so good!
I hope Halkara's okay.
She seemed to be drinking a lot.
U-Um, Lady Azusa...
I'd like... to ask you for a favor.
I was always more athletic
than my older sister,
and I was always better
at fighting, as well...
but when our parents yelled at
me or anything made me upset,
my older sister always did this for me.
It'll be hard to ask her for this
now that she's married, huh?
Yes.
Well, then...
I don't mind doing this every now and then.
N-No...
This can be considered a special occasion.
Thank you.
What's going on?
What the heck is she doing?
Come on, Halkara, wake up.
When you drink booze,
the booze shouldn't drink you.
Are you saying my fruit
wine isn't drinkable?!
Honestly, this elf is nothing but trouble.
Hup.
I feel sick...
If you puke, I will tear you apart and
roast every piece, down to your soul.
I'll hold it in...
Beelzebub! Sorry about that!
Azusa, I do believe she's had enough.
Since you're here, why don't you spend
the night at the volcano hot spring resort?
I'm staying there, as well.
Hot springs, huh? Should we?
I wanna go in the hot springs!
The Rokko Hot Springs feature seven
different types of hot springs,
excluding only sulfuric and acidic types.
They're good for people with cold
sensitivity or high blood pressure.
If you wish to stay there,
I will make the arrangements.
Well, we don't need to
be home tonight, so...
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Klik-klak!
Truly, though...
I do enjoy being around you people.
I always know fun things will happen.
Well, Beelzebub, you help me
out a lot when I ask for it,
and you like looking out for us.
You're kinda like an older sister.
Me? An older sister?
It seems to me you're only
using me for your convenience.
I have my two daughters...
Laika for my younger sister...
and Beelzebub for my older sister.
That sounds like a pretty
nice family, right?
Hey, wait a minute!
You left me out of the family!
Oh, that's right.
Let's see... Halkara can be...
the trouble-making junior!
Master! That's not fair!
Come on, Master!
Okay, sorry!