Something is definitely weird here.
It is weird.
Very weird.
I find it strange, as well.
Master, it's my turn to cook
the day after tomorrow,
but would you mind swapping
so I can do it today instead?
Sure, that's fine. Is something going on?
I have things to do in
the town of Nascúte...
It's important to make a fresh start!
Bye, grasshopper!
Goodbyes should always
be clean and complete...
Do you think Halkara intends to move out?
No doubt about it.
I don't want her to go!
But if that's what Halkara's
decided to do...
I'm back!
I'm so hungry.
Huh?
Halkara...
Thanks for everything!
Please be well in your new location.
We'll miss you.
I don't want you to go, Halkara!
Falfa, don't cry.
We must see her off with smiles.
What in the world is this all about?
Why all the talk of leaving?
Blink, blink!
What? You're not moving out?
I have no intention of doing that!
But you mentioned looking for
a new place in Nascúte...
Yes, one to build my new factory in!
Huh?
What?!
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
A Ghost Appeared
I'm back.
You're home so late every
evening. You must be busy.
Sure you're not working too hard?
No, no...
Even if I'm tired, I just need some
Nutri-Spirit, and I can keep fighting.
I've been using more of them
in a day recently, though...
That's a bad thing!
Come home once the sun goes down.
That's an order from your master!
But there's a reason why
I can't come home...
A ghost?!
Yes, apparently, a ghost has
been showing up in my factory.
And now none of the locals
want to work there...
I can't get anyone at all.
So that's why...
A ghost that just shows up in your factory?
They call those "bound spirits."
Scientifically, ghosts are
known as "separated spirits."
This type is most likely one that's
bound to the place where it died,
so it can't leave.
You mean it's the ghost of
someone who died there?
Master, would you please get
rid of the ghost for me?
Huh?
Uh, actually, I don't really
like things like that...
Please! I need your help!
Otherwise, I'll have to run
the entire factory by myself!
True...
Oh, all right. I'll go
check it out tomorrow.
Thank you so much, Master!
But!
Only if I can bring a helper with me!
A helper?
What is this thing?
It's summoning magic I learned a while ago.
I don't know if it'll work or not, but...
Vosanosanon ujishidau veyani enrila.
Nothing is happening...
What in all Hell is going on?!
So cold... so cold... so cold... so cold...
Why'd you close the door?!
Your pronunciation was a bit off,
so I wasn't summoned into the
exact location you wanted.
Why was your tub full of cold
water in the morning, anyway?
It's for watering our crops!
It's eco-friendly!
Eco-friendly is all well and good, but...
Anyway, what was is it you want?
What?!
You summoned me here just for that?
I'm sorry, really!
But I had a feeling you'd be a big help.
Scoot, scoot.
Yeah!
We knew you could...
...do something about it.
Squee!
Squee, indeed...
Well, it is true that I could
do something about it.
All right, take me to this factory.
I'll pulverize this ghost!
Lightbulb!
The ghost only shows up at night,
so could you wait until this evening?
Snap!
You should've waited until
evening to call me, then!
The Town of Nascúte
Skree, skree, skree...
I can imagine ghosts showing up here.
That cat statue is super creepy.
Oh, I put that there.
Isn't it cute?
Halkara's tastes are kinda...
What are you babbling about? Let's go.
She really is a demon. No hesitation at all.
Looks like I chose the right helper.
Sure is dark in here...
I really hope nothing shows up...
Don't be dumb. If nothing
shows up, why am I even here?
Hey, Beelzebub...
What?
Would you hold my hand? I'm scared.
I feel as embarrassed as a little girl...
but I suppose it can't hurt, so very well.
Master! Please hold my hand, too!
Halkara, where does this ghost show up?
In the room up ahead.
Then that room will be
the focus of our search.
Um... Can we not go into
that room? It scares me.
I agree! We should at
least save it for last...
Snap, snap!
Would you two cut it out?!
Maybe we should call this off...
Agreed! There's nothing in this...
Oh, quiet down.
You two are more of a
nuisance than that ghost.
Point!
Looks like it's over there.
It is here!
I'm about to lose it in more ways than one!
You two are making too much noise!
Just cool your heads for a minute!
It's only a ghost! The
spirit of a dead girl!
What's scary about that?
That's what's scary about it!
How are you so relaxed about this?!
You're only scared because
you can't see her.
Hey, girl's spirit! Show yourself!
She's forcing it out!
I am the high demon Beelzebub.
Loom!
I oversee the agriculture
of the land of demons.
With my authority, I could turn this
place into a horse manure shed.
That's low-key barbaric!
Please don't! This is my factory!
If you don't want that, show yourself
by the time I count to ten!
One...
Ten!
You skipped a heck of a lot!
There you are!
I've got her! Give me some light!
Stop that! Hold still!
Get your hands off me!
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
What's your name?
I'm Rosalie.
I'm the ghost of a girl who committed
suicide in the house that once stood here.
Hmph.
Bad attitude...
Um... And why are you here?
Why do you think?
This is the only place I can be!
A few centuries ago,
I was offered the chance to
marry into a noble family.
I had a reputation throughout the
town for being pretty and polite,
so I believed my parents.
But my rotten father and mother
were lying about everything!
They intended to sell me
off for chump change!
I see... You poor thing.
Yeah, well, that's in the past.
Um... I understand your story now,
but were you really regarded as polite?
In the centuries since I became a ghost...
I went bad.
That's certainly believable.
I would expect an adolescent to change
like that when betrayed by her parents.
This is my turf!
I don't want outsiders coming in here!
Which is why I've defended
it all this time...
And then you guys showed up.
Rosalie...
So what do you want to do from now on?
What do I... want?
Ah, in that case...
I can erase you in an instant
so you won't have to suffer.
None of that!
Why not?
I can help this ghost move on to the next
life without leaving a trace behind.
No way! I don't wanna disappear yet!
I guess not.
Okay, Rosalie, why don't
you stay in this world?
You mean it?
But won't I be a bother?
What do you say, Halkara?
Um, you don't need to disappear.
Can't you just go somewhere else?
I've tried to move a few times,
but I can't leave this building.
I see. That's what Shalsha
was talking about.
She said bound spirits can't
leave the place where they died.
I know a good way to resolve this.
Huh?
Demons have done extensive
research on spirits.
The latest research shows that if a
ghost possesses a living human once,
they will be able to go
wherever that human goes.
Possess?
She would basically be using a
human as a vessel to relocate.
The best humans to possess are
those with many weak points,
those who are weak-willed and
readily let others control them.
Huh?
Wha?
Eh?
What?!
Please, no!
Just seeing a ghost scares me!
There's no way I can endure
having one inside me!
You'd be doing it for your factory.
Just bear with it for a little bit.
Master! How can you be so dismissive?!
Sorry, but I'm comin' in!
No! I'll be traumatized!
All right! I'm in!
It feels weird to be in
a physical body again.
These boobs are so heavy.
Boing! Boing!
That's your first thought, huh?
So, where are we taking her?
Well, we're running her out
for our own reasons, so...
Rosalie, want to live at my house?
Can I?! I won't be a bother?
You were so unhappy in your previous
life that you died, right?
Nothing bad will come of you
finding happiness after death.
Come home with me.
Let me call you "Sister"!
I'll protect you if it kills me!
I mean, you're already dead.
What a smooth operator...
A ghost operator, rather.
Sister Laika!
Sister's daughters!
My name's Rosalie!
Nice to meet all of you!
It does feel quite strange...
Nice to meet you!
My first ghost... I'm so intrigued.
Well, I'm tired, so I'm going to bed now.
Okay, thanks.
Now, then!
I will show you the real Rosalie!
Yay!
Here goes!
Huh?
Beelzebububububububububub!
Too many "bubs"!
It's no use!
It's like being stuck in
a box! I can't get out!
You two must have been
exceptionally compatible.
Um, this isn't going to cause any
irregularities in Halkara's body, is it?
Obviously, if another's spirit
spends a full day in there,
it will cause strain on her body.
Strain? How?
In the worst case... she dies.
That's really bad!
I don't wanna kill someone
who helped me out!
If I have to do something that shameful...
If it really comes to that...
I have to die again to apologize!
No, don't!
If you do that now, Halkara
will be the one to die!
On that note, we're going to begin the
mission to separate Rosalie from Halkara.
Anyone have any good ideas?
Me!
Yes, Laika?
Rosalie spoke of being
stuck in a box earlier.
When I have a cookie that's stuck in a box,
the first thing I try is shaking it.
Vwoom, vwoom, vwoom...
Sparkle!
Then I try pounding on the back of it.
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Otherwise... I break the box.
Stop!
I know!
How about startling her,
like when someone has the hiccups?
S-Sister, where are we?
This intense wind concerns me...
Huh?
Where am I?!
I'm so high up!
I guess even ghosts don't like heights.
Well? Think you can leave her body now?
N-No! I'm just scared!
I see... Guess we can't help that.
Time for phase two, then.
Huh? Phase two?
No!
Well?
Did she come out?
No, but I thought a few other
things might come out...
It didn't work?
I guess we'll just have to try
everything we can think of.
It's already noon.
We're in trouble if we
don't get her out soon.
Halkara's body might not
be able to take much more.
It looks like she's already reached
that point in another sense.
If only we could, at least, summon
Halkara out of the body...
Yeah...
If we put Rosalie to sleep right now,
would Halkara's spirit come out?
I see...
So we move that one in front
that's getting in the way.
That just might work.
But how do we put Rosalie to sleep?
Help...
Is this alcohol?
Halkara gets drunk on this all the time.
But I've never had alcohol before!
Your body is Halkara's, so you'll be fine!
It always puts her right to sleep.
Okay, here I go!
This is noth—
It put her right out!
Huh? Why are we in Master's house?
Weren't we in my factory?
It's Halkara!
H-Huh?
Okay! Now let's wake up
Rosalie and revive her!
Then she might come flying
out of Halkara's body!
I know just how to do that.
Leave this to me.
Huh?
The bath?
Beelzebub, how bold of you...
Yes, I'm going to be bold, all right.
There you go!
That's cold!
There.
She's out!
It worked!
All right! I made it out!
S-So cold...
I'm sorry for all the trouble!
I'm going to be living here as of today!
I'm Rosalie! I hope we can be friends!
You really are a ghost.
Wow...
I'm intrigued.
I can't even see her as a different person.
I'm impressed you figured out that
cold water would revive her.
I remembered what happened when
you summoned me yesterday.
O-Oh, yeah...
But I'm glad Halkara's factory
will be able to operate now.
Yes.
I'll just wait patiently until the
rumors about ghosts fade away.
I'm sorry. It was all my fault.
Sister Halkara, at least
let me pour you a drink.
Wow, that's amazing!
Hey, I know a way to get
rid of that rumor quickly!
Heya!
I'm working at Sister Halkara's factory!
My name's Rosalie!
I'm a ghost, and I hope I can use
this power to help all of you!
That's remarkable!
I guess not all ghosts are scary, huh?
She's cute, even!
This is great.
It looks like the people of
the town will accept her.
Yeah.
Sister!
Thanks so much, Sister!
I never knew I could find
happiness after death!
I'm so glad I died!
I'm not sure you should say that, though...
Hey, Rosalie!
Wipe my windows, too!
And mine!
You got it!
I'll get each of your houses in turn!
At this point,
you might as well strive to be the most
cheerful ghost in the world.