Dun-da-da-dah!
Congratulations!
Azusa, Witch of the Highlands,
you are to be awarded the
Demon Medal of Honor!
Beelzebub, what did you show
up out of the blue for?
Could you try to sound a little happier?
It's a prestigious award
bestowed only upon those
who are loved by many demons and
have made a drastic difference
by giving bright hope to the world.
You recently ended the conflict
between the Red Dragons
and the Blue Dragons that
had lasted for generations,
and made them agree permanently to peace.
You were recognized for that, and you
get the medal in the peace category.
That's just how it ended
up working out, though...
Of course, you will accept it, won't you?
That's a great honor, Lady Azusa!
Way to go, Sister!
You're amazing, Mama!
I'm proud to be your daughter.
Yeah?
Okay, then, I'll gratefully accept.
The ceremony will be held in three weeks.
You should all attend.
I'll come to collect you
shortly before it starts.
Wait, where are we going?
The Demon Realm.
That's where the ceremony is held.
The Demon Realm?!
Crash!
There's no need to get so up in arms.
Most demons are well-bred
ladies and gentlemen.
The ones who wanted to destroy humanity,
like in olden days, are gone.
As long as you show the bare minimum
of good etiquette, that is.
Bare minimum...
...of good etiquette?
What?
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
Along Came a Leviathan
A demon ceremony gives me
nothing but bad feelings...
Is it all right if I develop a
stomachache on just that day?
You're gonna fake being sick, Halkara?
No, no! I just have a feeling
that, by total coincidence,
my stomach is going to hurt that day...
You might as well give up.
Missing such a prestigious ceremony
would bring shame to the demons.
Understood!
I will attend with the resolution of someone
planning to leap off the Kyalar Spire!
Hup!
What's the Kyalar Spire?
I guess this world has its own
idiom that means "take a plunge,"
A famous building of great historical value,
making it an important cultural asset.
like "jump off the stage at Kiyomizu."
Lady Azusa, what shall
we wear to the ceremony?
Wow!
Why don't we just wear what we
wore to the dragon's wedding?
Uh, Sister...
You really think it's okay for a ghost
like me to attend such a major ceremony?
Huh? Of course it is!
You're part of my family now, Rosalie.
Sister! Thank you!
Oh, yeah. You'll need a dress, won't you?
Want to go to the village and have one made?
No way. I'm a ghost.
I'm not even sure how to change my outfit.
You can't take that off?
I can't even touch it.
This poses an unexpected problem.
You think there are stores
that sell clothes for ghosts?
That kind of business isn't even possible.
Ghosts don't have any money, remember?
Spoken like a true business owner!
If you need a scholar specializing
in ghosts, I recently met one.
Now, listen.
Ghosts are spirits that have
remained in this world
with an appearance close to
what they looked like in life.
What looks like clothing is
only a part of that spirit.
It is not possible to change
a spirit's clothes.
I see.
Shalsha knows people like this?
So your clothes are a memory
of when you were alive?
Yeah, I think I did wear
stuff like this a lot.
Maybe if you envision other
clothes strongly enough,
you can change into them.
That's not something we can help with...
Sister, it's okay, really.
What's impossible is impossible.
I'm just fine sticking with this outfit.
Rosalie,	 you think everything's fine
if you can just endure it, don't you?
But just enduring isn't always a good thing.
Besides, you want to wear a dress to the
ceremony with the rest of us, right?
If it's possible... I'd like to wear one.
Right?
Then we shouldn't give up. Let's find a way!
How, though? Doing that would be like magic.
Magic?
That's right. I have the Create Magic skill.
There's no spell that can
change a ghost's clothes,
which means I just need to create one!
Time to show off what a cheat witch can do!
Ta-da!
Uh, Sister...
Showing me a real dress won't help.
I can't put it on.
Rosalie, take a good look at this
dress and ingrain it in your mind.
Then envision yourself wearing
this dress at a party.
Sister, if you're making this some kind of
"those who believe shall be saved" thing...
I don't think I like being treated
like an occultist by a ghost...
No, that's not the point!
Don't worry!
Just believe in me!
Sparkle, sparkle...
Sister... Okay, then!
I will repay your fiery passion in kind!
There, all set.
Here goes!
Okay, Sister! I'm ready!
Land of the living, land of the dead...
Shine upon the darkness
between the two realms,
and allow this outstretched
hand to reach the other side!
Work, magic!
Change, Rosalie!
Sister, now...
I could even go to a ball
without any trouble!
All right! It worked!
Rosalie, you look so pretty!
You're just like a princess!
Except the way you speak...
Sister Azusa!
Thank you so much!
What kind of magic did you use?
I basically tried to enhance my image of you
in a way that wouldn't
damage your spirit body.
Your image of me?
Sister, would it be possible
to do a little fine tuning?
Huh? You want to add something?
Yes!
Please put "Rosalie Is Here" on my back!
Yeah, no.
Soon, it was time to head out.
What is that?
Is it a demon?
It bears a slight resemblance
to us Dragons...
I really hope the demons don't hate me!
Please don't hate me...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I have arrived to collect you!
At last, the time came to depart
for the Demon Realm.
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
A Leviathan?
Correct.
It is a large type of demon that can fly.
This is the one who will carry
you to the Demon Realm.
There's a big building on its back.
Are we dreaming or something?
Awesome!
It's like a luxury liner!
Not entirely correct, but not wrong.
Let me show you the inside.
This is the VIP guest room.
Klik-klak!
This is the large bath.
Also, this bath—
Hey! What are you doing
when you're on the clock?!
Gulp!
I'm sorry, boss!
Who's that?
It's a pleasure to meet all of you!
I am Vania the Leviathan!
Get dressed before you introduce yourself!
I'm sorry, boss!
Now, allow me to explain the bath.
This large bath is a demon spring.
Demon spring? Is that a demons' hot spring?
Indeed. It feels slippery on the
skin and is great for beauty,
but be careful.
If you stay in for several
hours, you'll melt.
That's scary! And bad for you!
Only after several hours.
No one stays in the bath that long.
Halkara, please be careful not
to get in this bath alone!
Nobody trusts me at all, do they?
Thank you for waiting.
Hey, aren't Leviathans...
Yes, the one you're riding right
now is my older sister, Fatla.
We rotate the tasks of flying and
attending to guests in our human forms.
Vania is also in charge of your meals.
Your meal today will have
a focus on poultry!
The vegetables are carefully selected
first-class products, as well.
Look forward to it!
Wow, I can't wait!
By the way, Vania, you will write
a letter of apology later.
Oh, no! Please be lenient with me this time!
No. You will write.
Wow, what a view!
The buildings all look so tiny!
It looks so boundless.
I believe I've shown you everything now.
If you need anything, just let Vania know.
Thanks!
But do we really deserve
such a glamorous reception?
Must you ask?
That is just how incredible
your accomplishment was.
Shalsha, let's go look over there!
Okay.
You ended a long-lasting
conflict between Dragon clans.
Your name will go down in history for that.
Azusa, you can be a bit
more proud of yourself.
Well, I'll do my best not to
embarrass us at the ceremony.
You have no ambition, do you?
Everyone, thank you for waiting!
This is a salad made with
twenty types of vegetables.
Wow, high luxury right from the start!
It's delicious!
I've never tasted anything like it.
This is a potage made from mashed
Northern thick-shelled beans.
Cockatrice eggs wrapped in lettuce.
An omelette made from Roc eggs.
So light and runny!
This might be the best egg
dish I've ever tasted!
I never knew there was
an omelette like this...
I still have much to learn!
The difference in flavor is only natural.
These ingredients are worth a
thousand times more than yours.
A thousand... times...
If she somehow made anything
bad from these ingredients,
Vania would have to write
another apology letter.
I can't slack off at all when
working under Lady Beelzebub...
You're saying that after taking
a bath while on the clock?!
Vania, it really was delicious!
Klik-klak!
The food was great,
and the bath is fantastic.
I was a little nervous about
going to the land of the demons,
but I guess there was no need to worry.
I'm beginning to feel that way, too.
I think this might turn out to be a
nice trip with no problems at all.
Cut it out.
When you say stuff like that,
it feels like another flag.
Come on, that's not true!
We're flying over an empty wilderness.
The Demon Realm's still a ways off, I guess.
The stars are so close.
Even up this high, I'm still
nowhere near Heaven...
Huh?
Hey, Sister Halkara.
I woke up for some reason,
so I thought I'd take a bath.
You're headed in the wrong direction.
I was so sleepy, I made a mistake.
And what are you up to?
Just checking out the scenery.
There's nothing to see at all, is there?
It's still totally new to me.
If I'd stayed a bound spirit, I never
would've been able to see this!
That makes sense.
And it's all because you made
that building your factory!
I can't thank you and Sister enough!
I swear I'll repay this debt someday!
Don't trouble yourself with that.
There are no debts between us.
We're family now, after all.
I'm sure Master would
tell you the same thing.
Well, I'm going to the bath now.
I feel as warm as if I'd just
been in the bath, too, Sister.
Morning, Mama!
Morning. You two are up early.
Wait, where's Halkara, anyway?
She wasn't there when we got up.
Sister Halkara came out in the middle of the
night saying she was gonna take a bath.
You don't think...
The middle of the night...
A bath?
Halkara!
What did I tell you?!
Slither, slither.
Good morning.
I was so sleepy, I fell under the bed.
Everyone awake? We're about
to enter the Demon Realm.
Thank goodness!
I didn't know what we'd do!
What happened here?
What do you mean?
Do you see that?
The giant fortress city in the distance
is the royal capital Vanzeld.
You lot will first visit the
palace to meet the Demon King.
Huh?
After that... let's see...
The ceremony is tomorrow, so I
could show you around the capital.
Um, Beelzebub? What did you just say?
I said I could show you around the capital.
Before that!
Oh, about the Demon King?
What?!
Demon King?!
Fortress City Vanzeld - Castle Town
There are many different races of demons.
Some are just like humans.
Some are similar to animals.
They come in many shapes and sizes.
Vanzeld Castle
We'll walk from here.
Don't worry about your things.
Vania will carry them in later.
Um, Beelzebub...
Do we absolutely have
to meet the Demon King?
Of course you do.
The Demon Medal of Honor is awarded
by the head of the state.
Better to have your first audience
beforehand than at the ceremony, right?
Listen to me, Halkara!
Please try not to do anything silly!
I know. If I do, I'll probably be killed.
They'll skin me and then
throw me into the fire!
No one's going to do that!
If you insult our king,
I'll throw you into the fire!
I'm dead either way!
It's like a maze!
It's to confuse any enemies that
attack, so they can be eliminated.
A relic of the old days.
That's so demon-like.
Um, excuse me...
Can I just fake illness
for the rest of the day?
Actually, my stomach really
is starting to hurt...
Only because of all the walking.
Look, we're almost there.
The Demon King's chamber
is beyond this door.
It's huge...
Everyone, remember your manners.
No need to worry.
The Demon King is a friendly sort.
You can just act as you always do.
But, Beelzebub,
no matter how careful I am,
I usually mess things up regardless...
Our king is big-hearted enough to
forgive even someone like you.
Let us pass.
Ma'am!
Hi!
Welcome to Vanzeld Castle!
Um... Hi?
You're Azusa, the Witch
of the Highlands, right?
Yes...
It's really you!
Please shake my hand!
Okay...
Master, if we stand around here talking
and keep the Demon King waiting,
it'll make a bad impression.
You must be Halkara, right?
I drink Nutri-Spirit all the time!
Please shake my hand!
Ouch! That hurts!
Your grip is much too strong!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here! Healing magic!
Oh, thank you...
Um, I'm sorry, but could you
go elsewhere for a while?
We need to go and meet the Demon King.
We don't want him to say,
"You're late! Off with the elf's head!"
Aw, the Demon King wouldn't
say anything that mean.
Oh, but you don't know that for sure!
Friendly or not, his values may
be very different from ours.
I must demonstrate proper manners
and hide my true nature to be safe.
I hope I can manage to fool him...
You want to fool the Demon King?
Not out of malice, of course!
But that's an important part of
interpersonal relationships!
Um... Beelzebub?
There's no one on the throne.
Where is the Demon King?
Hm? Right in front of you, obviously.
I'm the Demon King, Provat Pecora Allières.
I don't like towering over
people when I meet them,
so I came down here to wait for you!
Right, of course...
I'm so...
so sorry!
All that stuff about fooling you and
hiding my nature was a figure of speech!
Are you okay, Halkara?
You said you wanted to fake sick,
but does your stomach hurt for real?
Illnesses start within.
It's possible she was focusing so much
on faking sick that she really got sick.
Cut her some slack!
Wow, you were actually thinking about that?
No... I was only worried that
I'd make some silly mistake,
King Plot Pecona Alias...
It's King Provat Pecora Allières.
Gulp!
Lady Azusa! She keeps piling on
more and more rude blunders!
Yes, I know...
There's no need to bow to me.
You're not one of my retainers.
So long as there's life in me,
I will never bring harm to any of you.
Demon King...
Please raise your head, Halkara.
Right! Understood!
Click.
My Demon King! Please stay with me!
Pecoraaaa...
Her spirit's flown out of her! This is bad!
Hallll...
Halkara! I can't believe you!
She's unconscious!
Get her to the doctor!
I don't know much about demon laws,
but in human law, anyone who harms
royalty is usually executed.
Um... Beelzebub?
If I'd known she would do this,
I would've let her fake being sick.
Halkara...
will be executed.