Halkara will most likely be executed.
Per the law, she will be impaled
and then burned alive.
In the worst case, the elf village
in her homeland may be destroyed.
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
We Beat Up a Demon King
We might all be executed, not just Halkara.
What she did would warrant that.
I don't wanna die!
There's just one way to save her.
Only the Demon King has the
authority to overturn a law.
If the Demon King awakens before
the execution is carried out...
Everyone, listen!
I got us a hot water pot and a tea set!
Thanks.
The guards look scary,
but they were very nice.
Sister, you were right!
There's a garden where they grow
a bunch of different plants!
Excellent! Now if I can
just get some herbs—
I'll go get them!
But if someone sees you...
No need to worry!
I can also take this form!
What in all hell...
You're so cute!
U-Um, Lady Azusa...
Squeeze!
This isn't so bad every now
and then, but still...
Anyway, I'm going now!
Flap, flap, flap...
I'm back!
Plink. Plonk.
Plop. Plop. Plop.
It's done!
Lady Azusa... what is it?
An analeptic.
It's just incredibly bitter
and hard-hitting, though.
But it's so bitter, I'm sure
it'll awaken the Demon King.
Vania?
Lady Beelzebub ordered me
to bring this to you...
The Demon King rests in this first-aid room.
But the question is how to get there...
Lady Beelzebub has a plan for that.
Sparkle!
This is like some kind of lame comedy skit!
Rumble, rumble...
Take this seriously!
I-I am serious!
Flail, flail, flail...
The current crisis has the
whole castle in a panic!
I'm sure no one's paid attention
to the identity of the doctor!
Really, though?
I will guide you through
the rest personally!
Well, okay.
I'll do what I can.
Mama...
Best of luck.
Yep.
Zoom!
If we're found out,
won't you get caught, too?
Yes...
I don't even fully understand how this
turned into such a serious matter...
But Lady Beelzebub gave me
orders, so I have no choice...
Sorry.
Who are you?
I am Vania, a servant of Lady Beelzebub.
I've brought the doctor.
Wait.
I have not received any reports
of Beelzebub summoning anyone.
I already know the doctor's name.
What is your name?
H-H-H-Her name is... A-Azu...
Pero... Poro...
We're dead!
Beelzebub!
You're ignoring us?!
Something doesn't smell right.
And what's with those horns?
Did you just stick them on?
Let me check for myself.
You leave me no choice.
I am Azusa, the Witch of the Highlands!
I will awaken the Demon King right away!
Let me through!
She's...
A friend of the criminal!
Get her!
Yeah, I saw that coming.
But for the sake of Halkara
and the rest of my family,
I can't just sit here and let you take me!
Impossible!
I-In a mere instant...
Just what is this human?!
Let me get to the Demon King!
Defend to the last!
You have permission to use magic!
Fire!
Really?
That's all you've got?
I never imagined it would turn out this way.
I guess I went a little too far, huh?
When you mean business, you could
flatten an entire country.
Y-You were awake?!
I sensed that a ruffian was approaching,
so I woke up instinctively.
Bwiiing...
You're a Demon King, all right!
What were you trying to get me to drink?
I-It's just an analeptic!
I was only trying to wake you up!
It looks a lot like poison to me.
It only looks like poison!
If you drink it, you'll be like,
"Augh, gross! But I want another!"
Very well, Witch of the Highlands.
If you wish to prove your innocence...
then face me, Provat Pecora Allières,
in a duel!
Huh? Wh-What do you mean?
If what you've said is true,
then even if you win,
you won't try to kill me.
Oh, of course...
I mean, I get the idea, but...
That would only work if I won, right?
If you lose, then it's over.
Only the fact that the Demon King
defeated an assassin will remain.
I guess that means I have no choice, huh?
Now, Witch of the Highlands...
I will judge...
just how powerful you are!
Losing is not an option.
All of our lives depend on this!
Huh? I can't believe she evaded that...
Well, I am level 99.
Why don't you try attacking me a little?
You'd better not drag your feet too long.
Remember, that elf's life is on the line!
That wasn't a very wise taunt, Demon King.
When it comes to protecting my family...
I'll show no hesitation!
I'd say we're done here, wouldn't you?
I only lost my balance, that's all.
But I've already destroyed it.
You can always train your body more,
but you can only strengthen
a weapon so much.
Checkmate.
Am I wrong, Demon King?
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
I do believe I've won, no?
Are you going to do as I say?
Yes.
I want you to spare Halkara.
She doesn't mean any harm.
She's just a klutz.
Uh... Demon King?
Demon King?
All right, Dear Sister.
What? Dear Sister?
I will obey your every order, Dear Sister.
What kind of joke is this?
For some time, I've wanted to live my life
in reverence for one stronger than me.
I thought you would be the
perfect choice for that,
so I took the liberty of testing you!
What?!
I'd like to respect and adore you for
the rest of my life, Dear Sister!
Um... I'm honored, really,
but before any of that,
could you please guarantee
the safety of Halkara and the others?
Please don't speak so politely to me.
Say it like you're giving me an order!
Oh, and with your hand on my face!
Provat—
Please, call me Pecora.
Touch.
Pecora.
D-Dear Sister, what are you doing?
Pecora, you are to set Halkara free.
Simple enough, yes?
It has been proven that Halkara did
not knock me out intentionally!
She is to be set free!
And treat all of Azusa's
family with utmost care!
Understood!
Well, I guess it all worked out...
Slither, slither, slither...
And our lives are saved, too.
Sorry, but would you mind humoring her?
Gulp, gulp.
I never dreamed I'd get to enjoy
tea like this with my dear sister!
I'm so happy to have an older sister now!
I had grown tired of making people serve me.
Everyone automatically denigrates
themselves before me.
Well, you are the Demon King.
When you slammed me against the
wall, my heart skipped a beat!
A woman with such a dignified
expression as she gives me orders...
My heart was simply pounding!
Drool...
Hmph.
Beelzebub was a candidate
to be my older sister, too,
but she wouldn't scold me or anything!
She seems like she'd be
a better fit than me...
Checkmate.
If there's ever anything the demons
can help you with, just ask!
I'll do everything in my
power for my dear sister!
Thanks...
Um, Dear Sister...
There's one favor I'd like to ask of you.
Uh... What is it?
Would you please give
me a kiss on the cheek?
Huh?
There's a scene in my favorite book
where the older sister
kisses her younger sister.
I just love that so much,
and I really want to experience it myself...
Huh...
And look, there's no one else around now.
W-Wait a sec! A kiss?!
People kiss members of their
own families, don't they?
It's just an extension of that!
I'm not kissing you!
I'll give you a hug, at most!
You should!
Especially for your little sister!
O-Okay, fine!
But only on your cheek, all right?
Thank you so much, Dear Sister!
I was genuinely scared, you know.
That was a close one, huh?
Dangerously close.
Keep your eyes closed, Pecora.
Please try to be a bit more careful.
I was so worried abo—
Master and the Demon King
are a c-c-c-c-coupl—
Master... you're the type who
falls in love with women?
W-Well, um...
You have my support!
No!
It's not like that! You've got it all wrong!
You've intruded upon my precious
time with my dear sister.
Have you no tact whatsoever?!
You won't get away with this!
Execution!
What?!
Let her off the hook! I'll kiss you, okay?!
No need anymore. The mood's already ruined.
A kiss between sisters is a sacred
ritual to deepen their bond.
It's not a matter of merely
touching with the lips.
Sounds complicated...
Mama, I don't think you've ever kissed me.
Falfa...
Come here.
Smooch.
Yay! Mama gave me a kiss!
Yay! Yay! yay!
I want one, too.
Smooch.
You didn't like it?
I... did.
Mama!
I'll give you one, too!
Me, too.
Mama... Smooch!
Je t'aime...
The rest of you get hugs!
Pout...
Squeeze.
Pat, pat.
Whoosh!
Then, I want one, too!
Okay, okay.
I think I might not be
very fond of this one.
If I had to say, I don't
think she's my type, either.
Spoiled girls like her need a
taste of how harsh the world is.
Oh, I almost forgot. Laika, right?
There'll be a part of the ceremony
tomorrow that might surprise you.
Wow, there are so many people here!
Even I was prepared to lose
my head after all this.
So was I.
Sorry about that.
I'll be more careful from now on.
Everyone, thank you for taking time from
your busy schedules to attend today's ceremony.
I'd like to get straight to the awarding
of the Demon Medals of Honor in order.
Next, the peace category.
Azusa, the Witch of the Highlands,
who halted the long-standing conflict
between the Red Dragons and the Blue Dragons...
and Laika the Red Dragon,
if you would both step up.
What? Me, too?
So this was the surprise
you hinted at yesterday?
I'd like to call one more to the stage:
Flatorte, representing the Blue Dragons.
Huh?!
Flatorte has brought the Blue Dragons
together to assure no further conflicts arise,
which I believe is worthy of recognition.
I-It's been a while, Laika.
Yes, it has.
You really seem to like surprising peopl—
And now for the awards!
There!
Toss!
Catch! Catch! Catch!
Haphazard much?!
This should go even further to ensure
peace between the Dragon tribes.
Surely there's no one who would
start a fight now, is there?
I-I understand clearly.
The Blue Dragons won't do anything.
After being forced to say that
on a stage this prestigious,
there's no way she'll break that treaty.
Pecora, you actually thought this through.
The demons themselves are
a highly multiracial clan.
The Demon King has to be a symbol
of the harmony among them all.
Well, I'll just take my leave now.
I still have many things I need to do...
Oh, I came up with a bit of an idea.
I'd like you to demonstrate proof to my dear
sister that the Blue Dragons won't rebel.
I know! You should stroke Flatorte's horns!
N-Not my horns! Anything but my horns!
Do you hate having your
horns touched that much?
I was a bit concerned my own
cleansing wouldn't be enough...
It's a custom unique to the Blue Dragons.
Letting someone touch your horns
means you submit to them completely.
Would you rather have
Laika touch them, then?
That would give the Red Dragons
total control over you.
Well, it's all for the sake of peace.
I guess I'll do it.
Have it your way!
Blast it all! I don't even care anymore!
If you'll excuse me, then...
Honored ancestors...
I have been forced to submit to this witch.
Please forgive me for bringing
such shame upon myself.
That's being a bit dramatic...
This concludes the awarding ceremony!
I, Fatla, will be your attendant
for the return trip.
I am the one you rode to the Demon Realm.
Oh! Thanks for that!
My younger sister, Vania,
will be your transport now.
Unfortunately...
Incidentally... how long
are you going to be here?
Now that I have sworn submission
to the Witch of the Highlands,
I cannot leave my mistress's
side for even a moment.
Wait, you're coming home with us?!
Correct.
Lady Azusa!
Our house in the highlands
doesn't need two dragons!
Please order Flatorte to
return to her homeland!
Our customs demand that I
kill myself if I leave her.
I must protect my mistress,
wherever she goes.
Their customs are hardcore!
Pecora, you knew all this
when you made me touch her!
That damn demon!
Everyone, I've brought some honey wa...ter?!
I-I'm so sorry!
Wh-What was that shaking?!
It was Vania. She must have recalled
something that made her laugh again.
This is Vania, your driver.
I'm very sorry about that.
I just remembered a joke
from a comedy I saw two years ago...
Moron!
Flatorte...
So long as I live, I will
protect you, Mistress.
Fatla, is it okay if I use the bath?
Hey... Don't you think that custom about
total submission is kinda unreasonable?
We Blue Dragons swore lifelong submission
to a dragon knight who overpowered us.
To the strong go all spoils,
and the master's orders are absolute.
These are my tribe's values.
Then if I ordered you to die, would you?
If you so ordered it, I would.
That is the pride of the Blue Dragons.
Okay.
Flatorte, I have one order for you.
Once we reach the house in the highlands,
you are to think for yourself and act of
your own will, without awaiting my orders.
Throw away all thoughts of
submission and live freely.
But then... I wouldn't know how to live...
My orders are absolute, aren't they?
So obey my order.
I'll give you all the advice you need.
If you're wrong, I'll let you know.
But you have to live independently.
You're free!
Mistress...
That order is contradictory.
That doesn't matter. I'm your mistress.
Mistress...
Before we return to the others,
can I ask you to do one thing?
Uh... So you just want me to
pet your head and horns now?
Yes.
Well, okay.
Ah... I belong to you, my mistress...
She spent all those years trying her
hardest to be the Blue Dragons' leader.
Mistress...
She couldn't show any
weakness or rely on anyone.
Mama...
Mama?
You're bothering Lady Azusa.
It's time for you to move.
Laika!
Why did you have to butt in?!
You were doing something weird,
so I stopped you! That's all!
You Red Dragons are always
doing such silly things!
What do you mean, "weird"?!
Lying in her lap while she
petted you made me env—
I mean, made you seem like a dog!
I am not a dog!
Woof!
I am a free, obedient Dragon who
gives her all for her mistress!
Thus our excursion to the
land of the demons ended,
and we finally began our trip home...
But our family gained
yet another new member.
Seems like things are about to get hectic...