What a refreshing morning.
The weather's so nice.
Today should be another peaceful day...
It appears you and I must settle our score!
Fine by me!
I challenge you to a duel!
Very well!
I haven't trained my body to be so weak
as to lose to the likes of a Blue Dragon!
What did you say?!
What was that?!
Stop!
What's all the fuss so early in the morning?
Lady Azusa! Whose cookies taste better?
Huh?
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
A Fake Witch of the Highlands Appeared
Basically, since Sister Flatorte came along,
the two of them have been arguing nonstop,
but since they swore before the
Demon King to stop fighting,
they can't fight with their fists,
so they had a cookie-baking contest
as a way to resolve their
disagreement peacefully.
Pop!
Whose is it?!
My judgment is...
Pop!
Pop! Pop!
They're both delicious, so you both win!
Lady Azusa, that's not good enough!
We need you to judge us without mercy!
Yeah, but...
Those two are awfully heated
today, aren't they?
We know why!
Because they haven't eaten any meat!
Dragons are carnivores.
They were complaining that they
haven't had fresh meat in a while.
Meat, huh?
Good morning.
It's unusual for you to drop by, Natalie.
What's up?
Well, it seems there's been an outbreak
of longhammer boars in Nilka Forest.
Longhammer boars?
This is the request.
They're very vicious beasts, so local
adventurers can't handle them,
and they hoped the Witch of the
Highlands would take care of it.
Hmm... Getting rid of monsters, huh?
I have plenty of magic
stones already, though.
Longhammer boars are wild
animals, not monsters.
They won't give you magic stones.
If you kill one, you'll only
get a lump of boar meat.
Meat?!
Lady Azusa! Let's leave at once!
We have to do this!
What's gotten into you two?
Master, it seems the two of
them are starved for meat.
Ah, so that's it.
Well, I don't want them starting
up weird contests again, so...
Okay, let's go beat up some boars.
I will make preparations right away!
There's no time to waste!
Zoom!
Nilka Forest
Meat! Meat! Time for some meat!
Meat juices overflowing! Meat juices flying!
So much, you can drink it!
The path is awfully steep.
Yeah, maybe being such a tough trip for
humans makes it safer for the boars.
We were right to leave Halkara
at home with Falfa and Shalsha.
She'd fall for sure.
Sister!
If you keep going straight,
the path slopes down into a
river through the valley.
I saw about fifteen boars there.
Thanks, Rosalie.
Slide...
Fifteen?!
It's a mountain of food! Let's go eat!
Wait! If you actually go straight...
I got stuck in tree branches.
I tried to tell you.
Of course your clothes would catch on
branches if you go the same way Rosalie did.
I don't wear clothes when in dragon form,
so I never got used to them.
So...
If they're in the way, they can get lost!
Whoa!
What are you doing?!
Have you lost your mind?!
This is what freedom is! Freedom!
Flatorte is free!
Then again...
No one's around, so I guess it's okay.
Sniffle, sniffle...
There were people at the
river, and they saw me.
They didn't do anything bad, did they?
They seemed to be female, so it was fine.
Honestly... Here.
Thanks. I owe you.
All you owe me is to put on your clothes.
There! All good now!
I'm going back!
Why?!
Yikes.
Laika, we're going after her!
They're gonna think we're
a group of streakers!
Yes! She'll bring shame to all Dragons!
Stop!
Sister Flatorte!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Give that back!
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle...
Splish.
It's floating away!
What in the world is she doing?
No idea.
I can't make the trip back
if I don't have those!
Splish.
My clothes are floating away, too!
Think about the direction
you kick things in.
Well, it's not like she's lost everything.
Forget it!
All right, boars.
If you're naked, the great
Flatorte will fight naked, too!
That's what you call taking
a fight seriously!
Wha—
Well, that's it! We have to help her!
Understood!
Got it!
I think it's ready now.
Nice! This is great!
Salt is really all it needs!
Hear that, you two?
Now, this is what I call a meal!
I feel energy welling up throughout my body!
You have some impressive appetites...
What are you lot up to?
Beelzebub!
Hey! My clothes!
They came floating downstream while
we were investigating the area.
We thought they must belong to the naked
person we saw earlier, so we picked them up.
I see that person was you, Flatorte.
You saved me! Thank you!
Beelzebub, what were you investigating?
Well, we heard the rumor
about the longhammer boars,
so we came to gather some
food for the Demon Realm...
But it appears you saved us the time.
Since we're here, perhaps
we'll help ourselves, too.
In that case...
Glint.
Slice!
I will prepare the finest wild
game dishes you've ever had!
I'll make sure there's plenty for everyone!
Lady Azusa!
Yeah!
Let's get the whole gang here!
A lot of crazy stuff happened,
but in the end, it was a good day.
So, you got to eat plenty of meat.
Do you feel better?
Yes. I'm sorry you had to see
us in that shameful state.
The thought of a reward
made us a bit overzealous.
A reward?
The truth is... the two of us had
decided on a reward for that contest.
The winner would get to sleep
beside you for one night.
This is news to me!
Sleeping like this makes it feel
like we're all sisters, huh?
Based on our heights, I'm the oldest sister,
Flatorte's in the middle,
and Laika's the youngest.
You two had better get along. Understood?
Understood, Mistress.
I will do as you say, Lady Azusa.
Okay, let's sleep together tonight.
Yes!
I'm the one who brought this back!
Don't be so stubborn.
I'm so hungry, I can't sleep!
That goes for me, too!
You two...
Uh...
Indeed...
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
Halkara Pharmaceuticals  Nascúte Factory
Time for a little break.
You've been working hard, Azusa.
You have a knack for this.
Thank you for saying so.
I thought I'd work here to kill
some time since Halkara asked,
but doing this sort of work like
a normal girl isn't so bad.
Did you hear? They say the Witch
of the Highlands showed up again.
Oh, yeah.
I heard she's traveling around the
world helping people in trouble.
The Witch of the Highlands
is such a virtuous person.
Say what?
So on that note...
There's a fake me out there!
Pung!
That's unforgivable!
Pang!
Let's pulverize 'em!
Pong!
We'll tear them limb from limb!
Peng!
Let's get them to work at the factory!
Ping!
Let's sue.
If precedent is followed,
they'll get, at least, five years.
Po-pong!
There's only one of our Mama!
Right... some of you said
some scary things, but...
I just want them to realize
what they're doing is wrong.
We'll start gathering
information right away.
We're going to split up
so we can all search in every direction!
A Town in the West
Zoom...
This is a pretty big town.
It should be easy to get information here.
Huh... Is there some kind of event going on?
Lady Azusa, if we're gathering information,
perhaps a bar is the best place to start?
Lady Azusa!
Don't worry.
Hi there.
Welcome to our public bar,
A Pig Would Be Far More Useful Than You.
There's no way this is a "public" bar!
That name is far too eccentric!
Yo, miss, I need a refill.
Shut up.
If you're hungry, get your own food, pig.
Oink...
Huh?
This bar was once in danger of going
under because of its poor service,
but it's turned around.
We turned our crude treatment
of customers into a theme,
and business boomed instantly.
A change in perspective led us to victory.
That's too drastic a change!
So, are you two pigs?
That's a question I never
thought I'd be asked.
Looking for part-time work, then?
I'd rather die than work
at a place like this!
There's actually something
we'd like to ask you.
We want to know about the
Witch of the Highlands.
I see. Information, is it?
I did hear a little tidbit about the
Witch of the Highlands recently.
What? Really?
If you want me to tell you,
why don't you try throwing some
insults at those boys over there?
I'd appreciate it even more if you'd look
at them with dismay and displeasure,
as if you were looking at something filthy.
What the hell kind of bar did we walk into?
Let's leave, Lady Azusa.
If it'll get us information, though...
Hey, miss, I want to order something else.
Could you keep your
booze-reeking mouth shut?
It's rotting my ears.
Oink, oink!
Lady Azusa?
Hey, miss, what about me?
One more word, and I'll kick you.
Oink!
Maybe I'll order the expensive booze!
I think whatever's in the horse's water
bucket should be plenty for you.
Oink!
Hey, miss! Smile for me!
Excuse me? Who said you
could give me orders?
Oink!
Verbal abuse is the best!
It was worth walking
three hours to get here!
I'm getting chills...
Lady Azusa, would you mind
if I ended these people?
Oh, those icy eyes make me tingle!
Oink, oink!
Put me down like I'm nothing but trash!
Quiet! Stay away from me, vermin!
Oink!
Give me more!
Keep your mouth shut!
Do you want to be torn apart
by a dragon's claws?!
Y-Yes, please!
Oink!
You obscene humans!
None of you have the authority
to make demands of me!
Oink!
Laika, you're giving them too much service.
Thanks a lot!
Now these pigs will drop
lots of money for me again.
You wanted to know about the
Witch of the Highlands?
In that case, the pigs told
me north is the way to go.
The Road to the North
Zoom...
My goodness! It's the
Witch of the Highlands!
We're so grateful you're here!
Lady Azusa.
Yep. Found her.
I am the Witch of the Highlands.
I have lived in the highlands for 300 years.
Great Witch, please sell
your secret medicine!
My skills are not nearly good enough
to produce medicine worth selling.
I'll sell it after I've improved more.
She's so humble!
Just as the Witch of the
Highlands should be!
You know that's not true!
You've been at it for 300 years, right?
How many years does it
take to become good enough?
Being a witch isn't such a tough job that
you're still a rookie after 500 years!
Everyone! This Witch of
the Highlands is a fake!
I am the Witch of the Highlands'... friend!
This woman looks nothing like her!
She's a fake?
I did hear that the Witch of the Highlands
was supposed to be a young beauty.
Right? Right?
Ahem!
If you're the real Witch of the Highlands,
surely you won't lose in a
magic battle against me.
Point!
Therefore, I challenge you to a duel!
Blink, blink.
Huh?
Lady Azusa, over there!
Now, give it up!
Huh?
I-I'm sorry!
You're right. I'm a fake!
I'm very sorry!
What?!
You're the real Witch of the Highlands?!
Now I'm even more sorry!
Well, it doesn't seem like you
meant any harm, so it's okay...
But you do appear to be a witch.
Yes, I am a witch. My name is Eno.
That aside, Eno...
You're the type that likes
to look the part, huh?
You make medicines here?
That's right!
These Mandragora Pills, for example,
are pills that I make from dried mandragora.
They relieve exhaustion and eye strain,
and they even keep your gut healthy!
You make some pretty good stuff, then.
I think this would be a
big hit if you sold it.
Oh, no.
I don't think it's wise for a witch
to advertise herself indiscreetly,
so I don't sell anything.
That seems like a waste of talent.
But if someone came along and said
they wanted to sell it to the public,
I'd be willing to consider it...
You could say I like the idea of being
a genius only to those in the know.
You're making this so complicated.
Pardon me... but isn't that a contradiction?
Huh?
You want to be familiar to those in the know,
but you also want to be known publicly?
You can't have it both ways.
I don't quite understand.
Well... yes. You're precisely right...
I just... you know...
There've been nothing but inconsistencies
in the things you've said.
Do you want to be known to
the public or don't you?
So what is it that you want, exactly?
What is your goal?
Could you explain it so that I,
an uneducated outsider, can understand?
W-Well...
Laika, that's enough. I'll explain it.
See, humans have this thing called vanity.
Eno's vanity takes the form of wanting
to be a genius witch who isn't into doing
business and is only known to those who know.
But at the same time, you have the desire
to be recognized as a great witch, right?
But that's...
Yes, it's a contradiction.
But humans are walking contradictions
in the first place.
Is that how it is?
This is just my personal opinion,
but am I correct?
Yes... You are right. I'm sorry.
In other words, you want
to be fawned over, right?
Yes! I want people to fawn over me!
Is that all?
No.
I want to stand out more and
be gazed upon with admiration!
And...
I'd like someone to make
a bronze statue of me
and be treated like some sort of
honored citizen in my hometown!
You're spouting some very
worldly desires suddenly.
What do you think you'd need
to do to achieve all that?
Th-The only way is to do things
that will make me famous!
Yes, well said.
So let's start doing that, then.
Huh?
Wow!
This is a pretty big marketplace.
Mama, where is this witch's shop?
Uh, I think it was A-23b?
Oh, it's along the wall!
The wall is the best spot!
Is this a doujinshi convention or what?!
Witch of the Highlands!
Eno... Is that...
Well, you know how I suffer
from stage fright, right?
So I decided to overcome my
embarrassment by becoming
someone completely different from myself!
I see.
Well, if it makes sense
to you, I'm all for it.
Where are Laika and Flatorte, anyway?
Get your Red Dragon brand butter cookies!
Try some cookies made with beans roasted
in the valley of the Blue Dragons!
Mine are better than the ones beside me!
The ones beside me aren't worth considering!
For the love of...
Don't you walk up to me
grinning like morons!
I'll make you regret that in the next life!
Go wash your faces in a
ditch and never come back!
Insult me more!
Lady Rosalie!
She might be perfect for that job...
Yes, one bottle of Mandragora Pills.
Thank you very much!
With that, Eno's shop turned
out to be fairly successful,
and she was able to shed a few
layers in more ways than one.
Lady Azusa, you have mail.
Oh, it's from Eno!
Dearest Lady Azusa.
Thank you for your help the other day.
Thanks to you, my Mandragora Pills became
all the rage through word of mouth,
and sales have been explosive!
I can't produce enough to keep up.
I'm struggling to figure out
what I should do about this.
Wow, so that medicine became a hit?
It sounds like she's quite popular.
Hmm...
It sounds as if she might work
out as a new business partner.
Well, she was able to draw
out her latent talent.
Maybe this was for the best.