Mother! There's trouble!
Shalsha? What's the matter?
Big Sister...
Big Sister is...
Falfa!
What is a slime doing in here?
I'd better kill—
Mother!
Don't!
Why not? It's a slime.
That's Big Sister!
Falfa?
I don't get what's going on...
When we woke up this
morning, she was a slime.
You're kidding...
The window in our room was closed,
so there's no way anyone could've
come in from outside.
So this slime can't be
anyone but my sister.
Are you really Falfa?
It really is Falfa!
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
My Daughter Turned Into a Slime
and Couldn't Change Back
This is...
...Falfa?
Really?
Is it?
I don't want to believe it, either.
Does anyone know how to turn her back?
I guess not...
Falfa is the spirit of a slime, right?
Could it be she had the ability
to transform into a slime?
Not that I've heard...
So, uh...
Can't you do anything about
it with your magic, Sister?
I think it'd be tough to create a new
spell for a case this specific.
If you have a question about monsters,
demons are the ones to ask!
Demons?
Vosanosanon ujishidau veyani enrila!
Beelzebub! Falfa turned into a slime!
You...
did this to me over a poor
excuse for a joke like that?!
No, it's true!
Gah!
Oh, Falfa... I can't believe
what you've become...
She woke up this morning looking like that.
Do you know a way to change her back?
Well, they say you should
buy bread from a baker,
so we should ask a slime
about slime matters.
Ask a slime?
I hear there's a special slime known as
"Intelligent Slime" at Vanzeld Castle.
That's where you'll likely
find your answer.
The demon capital does it again.
So what is this intelligent slime's name?
I told you, it's Intelligent Slime.
That doesn't sound very
intelligent to me...
Okay, I'm gonna pay a
visit to Vanzeld Castle.
Mother...
Can I go with you?
Of course. I know you're worried, too.
No need to be so serious.
Azusa and I will take care of everything.
Intelligent Slime seeks out quiet places,
so it resides at the castle's lowest level.
I'm impressed you don't get lost
with all these complicated paths.
Was this path here before?
You were lost?!
I thought this might happen,
so I've been leaving a
trail of bread crumbs.
Big Sister, you shouldn't eat
things you find on the ground.
Wait, how are we back on the surface?!
Ugh! This castle is so confusing!
Isn't this where you work?
Well, well!
I'm simply overjoyed to see
you again, Dear Sister!
Scoot, scoot, scoot...
Please greet me with a kiss on the cheek.
You know I'm not gonna do that!
You're looking for Intelligent Slime, are you not?
Do you not want to know how to find it?
And you're really going to tell me?
But of course!
Smooch.
Flutter...
A kiss from my dear sister is
such a wonderful experience!
I'm so ecstatic, I could simply die!
Okay, I get it! Just tell me where
Intelligent Slime is already!
Check that shed over there.
It just looks like a normal shed to me.
This is it.
We never would've found this!
There's a lot of writing on
the wall. What does it say?
You are...
Intelligent Slime, correct?
“Yes”
It hit the word "yes."
Ah, I see. It uses this to communicate.
And that's why it's black all over?
Intelligent Slime, this young slime spirit
suddenly took on the form of a slime.
Do you know how to change her back?
To... mu... re...
“To...
“To...mu...
“To...mu...re...
Backspace...
Oh, it made a mistake.
“To...mu...ri...
“To...mu...ri...a...
“To...mu...ri...a...na...
That's a lot of work.
“To...mu...ri...a...na... P...
“To...mu...ri...a...na... P...ro...
“To...mu...ri...a...na... P...ro...vin...
“To...mu...ri...a...na... P...ro...vin...ce...”
Tomuriana Province's tallest mountain...
Ask the Magician Slime that lives there.
A magician slime now?
The tallest mountain in Tomuriana Province?
We'll need some time to look into this.
Azusa, why don't we resume tomorrow?
Yeah, I think everyone's tired,
anyway. Let's do that.
Intellie, thanks a lot.
Intellie?
Intelligent Slime... or Intellie for short!
You have such simplistic naming sense.
I didn't know slimes ate meals, too.
It doesn't need to be a meal.
We can get our nutrition from dirt
and plants we find anywhere,
but I want her to have real food.
Ah, a moment's repose...
Mother...
What is it?
Do you think we'll find a way
to change my sister back?
Don't worry. Just leave it to your mother.
But even in a different form,
Falfa is still Falfa.
Even if she was in a group
with dozens of other slimes,
I'd find her in a heartbeat.
That's it.
Hello!
Oh? Who might you be?
This is where Magician Slime lives, isn't it?
Oh, I'm sorry to have confused you.
I am a slime.
You're a slime?!
I'm in this form because I
used transformation magic.
So that's it...
This isn't the place to talk.
Please come in.
I'm sorry I don't have any
chairs meant for guests.
Since I'm a slime, I don't need
furniture or bathroom fixtures.
By the way, what's your name?
Magician Slime.
Of course it is! Then can I
call you "Magie" for short?
Magie?
Yes, that's fine.
So what is it you wanted to ask of me?
You want to return this slime
to her previous form?
That's right.
May I borrow her for a moment?
Uh-huh... I see.
Her elasticity is quite different
from a normal slime's.
She is definitely a special slime!
Ah, I see, I see...
So that's it... Uh-huh...
You're that type? Ah, you're that type...
What type?!
I have the answer!
The reason this slime ended
up in this form is...
Is...?!
Is...
Her sleeping position.
Sleeping position?!
By touching her, I could feel
that her body was stiff.
I'm sure she damaged a
muscle while sleeping.
That made it difficult for her
to maintain her human form,
so she took the form of a slime.
Can you not turn her back with
your transformation magic?
The magic only works for a short time.
It doesn't solve the problem itself.
Then what can we do?
The quickest way is for this slime herself
to understand the way to change back.
For help with that, I think you
should ask Fighter Slime.
Fighter Slime?!
Unlike me, Fighter Slime attained a
human form through bodily movement,
so I think the solution is to
learn the same technique.
And where can we find this Fighter Slime?
I believe she's in a southern
town called Kelney
to participate in a fighting tournament.
A fighting tournament?
The rumors say she's a solitary
fighter who seeks only strength.
I see. In that case...
I'll enter this fighting tournament, too!
Why?
If I enter it and prove that I'm
stronger than Fighter Slime,
I bet she'll listen to me!
Hmm, good point...
And what is this fighter slime's name?
Naturally...
It's Fightie!
Fightie...
The same naming scheme I use for things!
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
There really are a lot more men than women.
Hey, that outfit...
I've been waiting for you.
Everyone in the arena will freak out
if a demon enters the tournament!
It'll be fine.
I hid my horns, and I'm
going by the name "Belzie."
Pretty sloppy name choice!
That's rich, coming from you!
The use of magic is prohibited in
this tournament, so watch yourself.
I'd look pretty dumb if I
got disqualified, huh?
Round 1
Lady Azusa!
You can do it!
Go get 'em, Mistress!
Falfa!
I promise I'll get you back to normal!
Hey, little lady!
If you don't wanna get hur—
I won't lose!
The winner is Azusa!
She knocked him out in an instant!
Sister's so awesome!
“Azusa”
“Belzie”
Semifinal
It's already time for the semifinal.
None of them are a match
for our master at all.
Another skinhead?
I've trained this iron body to be
strong enough to repel any—
The winner is Azusa!
She's overwhelming all of them!
Lady Azusa, you're fantastic!
Mother... You did it!
All right. Now I just need to
beat Fightie in the final.
The second match of the semifinal.
Fightie, please take the stage.
She's on the next stage over?
So that's Fightie...
Belzie, please step forward.
The winner is Belzie!
Wait, she beat her!
This Fightie was really
nothing special at all!
Beelzebub, why did you beat her?!
Now I have no way to make contact with her!
Don't worry.
I have the same goal as you.
You can count on me to
negotiate with Fightie.
Can I really?
Just leave it to me.
So, Azusa...
You're free to advance
to the final round now,
and then you can fight me.
To be honest, I don't even care
about the final round anymore.
Too bad!
I want to fight you in the final
round and settle our score.
Understand? You have to make
it to the final round.
Final Round
What's this?
It's your time to shine,
and you look so grumpy.
What did you expect?
I haven't fixed Falfa's problem yet!
Wait a moment.
Mama! I'm back!
Falfa! You're back to your original form!
I'm so glad!
Yeah! Thanks to Beelzebub!
What do you think? Quite the surprise, no?
Wait, you all knew about this? Jeez...
You can do it, Mama!
I'll be rooting for you!
Thanks! I'll do my best!
Now you can focus on our fight.
Azusa, Witch of the Highlands,
the outcome of our battle
is yet to be seen.
This time, we fight with no barriers.
There's no telling how it will end
if we fight fair and square.
I am strong, after all!
She's right. We never finished that battle.
Okay, then! Let's do this, shall we?
This time, I'll show you what
I can do when I get serious!
Begin!
You're flying?!
Hey, she's flying!
Wait, she has horns, too!
Is that what's hot in the big city?
Damn!
It's too stylish for us
country folk to understand!
I guess no one's gonna figure
out you're a demon.
Well, this is a problem.
Huh?
I can't match your speed
by attacking head-on.
I thought I'd try to find a
weak point and strike that...
Wait, I really don't have any weak points?
No, you have countless weak points.
So just come straight at me, then!
You aim for a weak point when
you just happen to find one!
When you have so many of them,
it's hard to choose one to strike!
But we can't fight unless you come at me.
We can't use magic, so I can't fly.
I know, but still...
Fine. Just let me know when
you're going to attack, okay?
I'll wait here until then.
One, two, three, four...
You're mocking me!
Fine! Here I come!
I'm going to send you flying!
What an impact!
Mama!
Mother...
Don't squeeze my face...
It's your own fault for
coming at me face-first.
Stop it this instant!
All right!
Here I come, too!
What incredible force...
I've still got more!
Fine by me!
They're so fast, I can't keep up!
I can't, either...
This is the first time I've
been in a fight for so long!
You're pretty strong, too, aren't you?!
Damn straight!
I'm a demon officer, after all!
It's much more bizarre that a
human is even able to fight me!
And...
I've trained every single day,
in both wind and rain,
both before and after work,
all for this day!
Beelzebub... I had no idea you
saw me as such a worthy rival,
but that makes me kind of happy.
She's really weakening, though.
What can I do to finish this?
Mama!
You can do it!
I was watching you while
I was a slime, too!
You did all that running
around just for me!
It made me so happy!
So I'll keep rooting for you all the way!
You can do it!
Sorry, Beelzebub.
Since my daughter's watching,
I have to look good for her.
I just evolved about two more levels!
What nonsense are you spouting?!
I will be the one to win in the end!
The winner is Azusa!
Mama! You did it!
Congratulations, Mother!
Beelzebub, are you okay?
Yes...
But it does hurt a bit.
Here you go.
Hey! I'll be fine once I rest a bit!
And there are so many people watching...
You're hurt. No complaining.
Thanks, Beelzebub!
From me, too.
No need to thank me.
It seems I've lost to you again.
It was a sound defeat.
I'll give you a rematch if
you still want to fight.
It's kind of a hassle, though,
so you'll have to wait a while.
You're so strong, yet you have no zeal.
This might ruin your peaceful
life again, though.
Huh? What do you mean?
Your strength is now known
even here in the south,
where it was not widely known before.
Witch of the Highlands!
Azusa!
Azusa! Azusa! Azusa!
Greatest witch ever! Azusa!
Damn it!
Fightie!
Thank you for restoring
my daughter to normal!
Don't mention it.
I'm glad I had the chance
to help a fellow slime.
It's too bad I didn't win the tournament
and get the prize money, though.
But I'll make money again,
even if it's one gold at a time!
Yeah, money is definitely important...
If you know of any martial arts events
where I could get money, let me know!
Boy, I really wanted that
prize money, though!
You're a little too obsessed with money...
Um, actually, I wanted to
ask you for a favor, too.
What is it?
Miss Azusa, please take me as your student!
Huh? You mean as a martial arts student?
Yes! I've never seen a stance
with so many vulnerabilities,
yet prevents all hits from landing!
You're the strongest in your natural form!
That's my ideal as a martial artist!
Look, that's not a stance or anything.
I really do have a ton of weak points.
So there's nothing I could teach you.
I understand!
In that case, please let
me fight you just once!
Then you can decide whether or not I'm
strong enough to be your student!
Were you even listening?
Okay, here I come!
Fightie Style Slime Fist!
Shiver!
Th-That's...
Shake, shake
an aura only emitted by those who have
slain an unimaginable number of slimes!
Countless souls are crying out!
What's wrong, Fightie?
H-Help m—
You're awake now?
I wasn't expecting that fight
to end before it even began.
Did it convince you to give up
on being my student, though?
Yes...
Oh, so this is where all of you were.
It's time to start clearing out.
Ah, Miss Belzie!
I've realized that your strength
is like that of a demon!
As such...
Sparkle!
Please take me as your student!
This girl has no integrity at all.
Why should I take you as my student?
No, I will not.
Please! I'm begging you!
I don't take students.
Oh, that could work, though.
If we know where she is,
it'll be easier to get her help if my
daughter turns into a slime again.
Flash!
Are you trying to pawn me off?!
Please! I'll wash your dishes
or do anything else you want!
Beelzebub, I'm asking you, too.
I'm asking, too!
Me, too.
All right, fine! Fine, I say!
Thank you!
All right, I guess that's case closed.
Falfa!
I'll pamper you as much as you want today!
What do you want to eat?
Mama, I want something sweet!
Okay, maybe I'll make a cake or something.
I'll help, too.
Oh, then I'll help, too!
I maxed out my level without
even realizing it,
but after this, I decided to
raise my level as a mother, too.