Okay, shall we head home?
Yes.
Mama!
Look, look!
It says a minstrel is coming to town!
Oh?
"The famous minstrel Schifanoia is
paying her first visit to Flatta."
That's... not quite what I was expecting.
Anyone know who this is?
I've never even heard of her.
Probably some nameless chick.
It does seem a bit sketchy.
Schifanoia, eh? She's certainly
been around a while.
You know her, Flatorte?
I like minstrels.
I know at least 1,000 groups.
That's hardcore!
Schifanoia has only ever
performed in the capital,
but it sounds as if she's
begun touring the nation.
I wanna hear the minstrel sing!
Some minstrels tour all manner
of towns and villages,
It might be fun to give her a listen.
while others stick to different
areas within the same large city
Okay, then... since we're here...
and never visit towns with
small populations...
I guess we can check her out.
A Minstrel Came to Town
There are quite a lot of people here.
Is that Schifanoia?
It appears so.
What... is she doing?
Death! Death! Death! Death! Execute!
Execute! Execute! Execute!
I'm scared!
Let's go over there, Big Sister.
This is hurting my ears, dear.
Lady Azusa, Halkara seems
to have a stomachache.
Let's go home, honey.
I just don't get the music
they like in the capital.
I'm going with her to rest.
The scale of my fake sickness is growing...
Let's go play chess over there.
Hey, wait...
This song truly is Schifanoia's style.
Papa, buy me some butter candy!
You know what this is?!
It's death-style, from the
crime-style of emotional-style.
Actually, it's a lonely-style-leaning form
of death-style called drag-down-style.
Sorry, I didn't understand a word of that.
This is my first time coming
to this village on tour,
This is the kind of stuff
people in the capital like?
but I can feel your passion!
I think Schifanoia draws
crowds of about 30 or so.
This next song is another of my
biggest hits, "Gray Dreams."
Less than impressive...
I'm surprised you knew about
someone so nameless.
Oh, it isn't about listening to famous
ones and ignoring the nameless ones.
I give all minstrels a listen
just because they're minstrels.
If you put black and white
together, you get gray!
Those are the words of
someone who's hooked!
Well, in crime-style, the lute tends to
be given more focus than the vocals,
If you add even more black...
She's on her second song now...
but death-style has a sound that feels
like it's splitting your ears.
It gets duller...
Flump.
Wait, is this part of the act?
This is awful!
She's actually lost consciousness!
Yeah, I thought so!
Are you okay?! I'm gonna help you now!
You're awake? If anything
feels off, tell me!
Grrr! Gurgle gurgle gurgle...
Grrr...
Oh.
So good! So good!
She must've been really hungry.
When you're done eating,
you're welcome to take a bath, too.
Okay! Thank you!
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Kuku the almiraj.
That's how you look without the makeup?
That's right.
You know...
I bet you've passed out like
that before, haven't you?
A few times...
I can't support myself with
minstrel work alone,
so I do some part-time jobs.
Very few minstrels actually
earn enough to live on.
Yes... I wanted to be like them,
so I left my hometown 63 years ago.
I believed that I was gonna be big...
that I'd ditch my weak self
and become a great minstrel.
Just like a guy who left his
hometown to be in a band...
But I couldn't get anywhere at all.
Over and over, I told myself I'd quit,
but I decided to keep trying
just a little longer...
Kuku, why don't you stay here
and take it easy for a while?
The air's fresh. It's a great
place to rest and recover.
Thank you so much.
But... well...
I think it's time to quit music
and start living my second life.
Do you have a plan in mind?
Actually, I've gotten offers
from a few places like this.
There's a steady demand for
beastfolk in these sorts of jobs.
Almiraj are particularly popular.
I've been told numerous times that I could
make all the money I need in this line of work.
I thought, at this point, I should
just work where I'm wanted.
So, Kuku...
Do you not like music anymore?
It's not like that!
I love music!
Really? You shouldn't quit
making music, then.
Stick with it.
Huh?
You might not be making any money now,
but you never would've kept it up
this long if you didn't love it.
It'd be a shame to just give that up.
I bet you'd regret it one day.
If you're optimistic about starting
a new job, I won't stop you.
But that's not what you're doing right now,
so you should stick with what you're doing.
For now, just devote yourself to your music
while you think about your
future one more time.
You can stay here in the meantime.
B-But I can't pay rent...
You don't need to.
I'm the one who told you
to stick with music,
so I'll do everything I can.
I appreciate it!
To celebrate our new friendship,
let me play for you!
Welcome to my feast of
death and destruction!
Her personality changed!
Poison, poison, poison, poison,
poison, poison, poison...
Wormwood... Wormwood...
I can't tell how it's any different
from her other songs!
Poison, poison, poison, poison,
poison, poison, poison...
They all sound the same!
That's a pretty real complaint!
Wormwood... Wormwood...
Sorry, Kuku, but could you stop now?!
Wh-Who are you talking to?!
I am Schifanoia!
I'm here to bring true despair to all of—
You can drop that act.
I messed up in two spots...
I couldn't give you a good performance.
I think we're way beyond that level here.
Speaking from the perspective
of a listener,
lonely-style-leaning death-style
doesn't sell in this day and age.
Why don't you try some
flowery-style-leaning excessive-style?
Yes, but... I really prefer the death-style
that lets me use my artistry...
I bet you're just afraid to
do something that sells.
Th-That's not true!
It is true.
You do tend to look down on minstrels
who have a lot of fans.
Is this a drinking party
for young band boys?
And forget using your artistry.
You just suck.
I-I'm doing the best I can!
Amateurs should just stay out of this!
Oh? Let me see your lute, then.
It's not a guitar?
The clear, sunny sky just makes
this Sabbath even colder
I yawn as I wait for you to arrive
To a place higher than the clouds,
where there's no background noise
We'll fly, let's fly
That's amazing, Flatorte! I didn't
know you had that kind of talent!
You see? Even an amateur like the
great Flatorte can manage that much!
If you understand,
then stop making excuses!
I'm sorry.
Gloom...
Hey, you know, I was thinking...
Why don't you try writing lyrics
that are easier to understand?
But I've been performing
this way for so long now,
I wouldn't know what's
easy to understand...
Blink, blink!
Since we have such a big family,
let's have everyone write some lyrics!
Okay, we'll start with Laika.
Ah, Devotion
Laika   Lyrics
Kuku   Music
Only through step-by-step devotion
Can one achieve anything
And—
I think the message is a little
too direct for song lyrics.
Unusable. Try again.
D'oh!
Okay, next is Halkara.
My lyrics are great! They'd sell for sure!
Jingle!
Halkara Pharmaceuticals'
Nutri-Spirit
Halkara   Lyrics
Kuku       Music
One more push to get through work today!
Nu...
~Performance Halted~
Okay, next!
Master! At least give me
constructive criticism!
The Field
Falfa & Shalsha   Lyrics
Kuku                     Music
Praying mantises are scary
They're scary because
they have those scythes
Grasshoppers jump
They shake their legs to jump
Nature is so big
And I am part of nature, too
What am I?
I am a being that amounts to nothing
In other words, I think that means I'm me
I love it! So cute!
Yes... Its theological elements
might be rather novel.
Yay!
And last is Rosalie!
Got it!
Nothing
Rosalie   Lyrics
Kuku     Music
When you've been stuck in
one place for a long time
Even the daytime seems dark
So dark, so dark, so dark,
there's truly nothing
I don't even know how to laugh anymore
Even though I want to die, I can't
That's what that night was like
Gloom...
Oh, I'm having fun now, though!
I was singing about things
like destruction and death,
but it was all just words.
I've never actually died.
No kidding.
So... I realize now that I can't beat
the power of words spoken in truth...
Sparkle, sparkle!
I'm going to abandon the name Schifanoia
and go by my real name, Kuku!
And I'm going to try writing a new song
incorporating all of your lyrics!
Thank you all so much for everything!
If you're ever in the area on tour,
drop by the highlands to see us.
In fact, you can think
of it as coming home.
I will! I promise!
Put on good concerts.
If you can do that,
everything will work out.
Right!
Frankly, you have no musical talent.
But success in this world doesn't
always favor the talented first.
So it's possible that even you
could end up successful.
First, you have to fight!
Then just keep fighting from now on!
Right!
They're master and pupil already.
I got some great sake,
so I brought it here!
Beelzebub, welcome!
You don't have work to do?
Spinny spin!
It's my day off!
I'm spending today with Falfa and Shalsha!
Who's this?
I'm Kuku the minstrel.
She's been staying here at
the house for reasons.
Oh?
Then you should sing while we drink.
Hey, don't put her on the spot like that.
I'll do it!
No, please let me do it!
To find out if I can get by
as my new, reborn self...
I want someone who doesn't know me
to hear my song and be the judge!
Thank you for listening.
Fantastic.
That was great!
Th-Thank you!
I want you to perform at
our next music festival!
What's that?
It's the biggest demon music event
held in the castle town of Vanzeld.
So it's a festival?
I'll invite all of you, as well.
Yay!
Kuku, was it? Will you perform for us?
Yes, if you'll have me!
Oh, but how big is the stage?
Well, you'll be performing for
an audience of about 20,000.
Twenty thousand?!
Kuku?!
Um... I'll practice like
my life depends on it,
so would you mind letting
me stay here a bit longer?
It looks like our life with
Kuku isn't over just yet.
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
Now, everyone,
please enjoy our music festival.
Thanks, Fatla.
You're welcome to visit the stage and
rehearse before the event tonight.
Would you like to?
Yes, of course.
It's a much bigger stage
than any I've experienced.
Kuku, give it your best!
I will!
Master, what shall we do?
There are a bunch of shops set up!
I want to go see!
Me, too.
That was fun!
Kuku, what's wrong?
I visited the venue,
and it was just too big.
When I think of performing on that stage...
The new Kuku will pull through just fine.
That's right. I'm no expert, but I can
still tell that you've improved.
I hope so...
You'll be fine.
You already have the perseverance to stick
with the same thing for a long time.
You were just investing your
effort in the wrong way.
Now that you've fixed that, you can
put on a good performance for sure.
Right...
For all you say, Flatorte, you have no
perseverance and never invest effort for long.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What do you mean by that?!
Well, you only crashed my sister
Leila's wedding on a whim, right?
If you wanted to defeat us Red Dragons,
shouldn't you have started trying sooner?
That was the kind of thing
that's best done on a whim!
Well, even if you had tried,
I doubt you could have beaten us.
Fine! Let's settle this right here and now!
Okay, you two, that's enough!
We'll have a contest to see who has
better luck in today's horoscope.
I accept!
That's too peaceful a solution!
What are you laughing at?
I'm sorry... I didn't mean to...
Kuku, you've done all you could.
All that's left is to let the
audience hear your song!
Right!
How's Kuku doing?
She was a little nervous,
but I think she's okay now.
Beelzebub, thanks for offering
Kuku this opportunity.
All I did was give her a opportunity.
Whether or not she seizes
that opportunity is up to her.
I'm Kuku.
The song I'm about to perform...
is called "Thank You."
I know that
I should be saying goodbye
But that would be too sad
So I'll say this instead
Thank you
I'm not disappearing and going away forever
We'll both still be living under the same sky
In different places, but at the same time
There may be things that we forget
Because we are alive
But because we're alive, we can remember
Yes, we can remember
So whenever you feel like it, at least,
Come and see me, please come and see me
Thank you
Cheers!
Kuku, you were awesome!
I never thought it would go so well!
I owe everything to all of you!
I don't know how to thank you...
What?
There's only one thing to
say at a time like that.
"Thank you," right?
Thank you!
You've already got a ton of requests from
the organizers to make appearances!
This...
It looks like enough work to keep me
going in the capital for a while!
Good for you, Kuku!
You've become an overnight sensation!
Yes...
Kuku, can I borrow your lute?
Y-Yes, of course.
I have a song for you.
It's not a very good one, though.
Is this...
Schifanoia!
As Schifanoia, you sang so hard
that you lost consciousness!
Of course you wouldn't get popular
with music like this, but still!
You kept doing it because
you believed it was right!
So if you ever want to go back, you can!
Don't you dare get any dumb ideas
about giving up on it forever!
You're not clever enough to keep up
with what's popular in the world!
If you were, you would've
been popular long ago!
Even I, Flatorte, got it wrong
over and over and over again...
And now, I'm living here.
There is no right answer, but as
long as you don't stop completely,
there are no total failures!
So you just sing however you want!
That's what your life is.
Thank you so much!
I'll do my best right here!
They're definitely master and pupil.