The skies are clear!
A day like this calls for...
Ta-da!
A mushroom-grilling party!
Or for short, a shroompa!
A shroompa! That sounds fun!
No meat, though?
These are all types I've never seen before.
Are you sure they're safe to eat?
Of course!
I made sure to only pick the edible ones!
I've perfectly memorized which
mushrooms in the nearby forests
are edible and which ones aren't!
They're definitely safe!
You already have a bad record.
Why are you so confident?
Well, if you insist, I'll believe you.
Click, click.
Now, let the shroompa begin!
We spread some butter on the grill
and toss the mushrooms on.
Then we drizzle on some elvin, and...
Ta-da!
That's all it takes to
make them super tasty!
Scoot, scoot...
What do you think?
Br...
Bring on the booze!
This is quite good.
It's not meat, but it's
good in its own way!
Delicious.
I didn't know there were so many
different types of mushrooms!
Forests are amazing!
Here you go, Sister.
Man, nothing beats the combo of grilled
mushrooms and butter with soy sauce!
Soy sauce?
Pop!
What's this mushroom called?
They're black dwarf mushrooms.
I only picked the ones that
hadn't grown too big yet.
Pop!
And this one?
Gnome's hideaways.
They don't grow in this area,
so I grow them in my room.
At their full size, they're big
enough for a gnome to hide under.
Pop!
Is this the same kind?
Yes!
That's also a gnome's hideaway...
or rather, it's a gnome-maker mushroom.
It's what they call a poison mushroom.
Eating it makes you shrink!
Gulp.
Did you just say "poison"?
Did you really just say "poison"?
Master, your smile looks scary!
Boom!
You said they were all
definitely safe to eat!
The ones I picked are perfectly fine!
This is one I've been growing in my room!
You think I care?!
Master?
Mother!
Mama!
Lady Azusa!
Mistress!
Sister!
Wh-What? What just happened?
Lady Azusa...
Mama, you're so cute!
Cute? What?
Wait, what is this?! Don't tell me I...
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
I Ate a Mushroom and
Turned Into a Child
I'm totally a child.
You certainly look young enough.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
But don't worry! It doesn't do any
harm, other than making you shrink!
I'll find out how to turn you
back to normal in no time!
Hmph.
Do that.
I hope I can change back to normal soon...
Um, Lady Azusa...
This is very difficult
for me to say, but...
Sparkle, sparkle...
You're so cute!
You're crying?!
Scoot, scoot...
Upsy-daisy!
That's not going to make me happy!
I'm not actually a child!
Even though your body's smaller,
I guess your soul weighs the same.
What are you seeing, exactly?!
I'm glad the village had clothes
like yours in children's sizes.
Here, Mama! Open wide!
Again, I'm not a child...
Memoirs, Volume 1: The Intrinsic Differences
Between Knowledge and Experience.
What book is that?
A literary masterpiece about
intuitive cognition.
That's not a book you'd read to
a child. Not that I'm a child.
Listening to it will make you sleepy.
It's great for getting babies to nap.
This is...
A kids' lunch...
I tried making it fancy
to suit your appearance.
You're enjoying this...
Where's Halkara?
She's secluded herself in her room to
search for a way to turn you back.
She'd better find it...
Um, Lady Azusa... I have a favor to ask...
What is it?
Floaty...
Would you let me pet your head?
Okay, fine!
At this point, you might as
well coddle me all you want!
I've resigned myself!
Pet, pet.
Lady Azusa, you're so cute.
Even your grumpy face is adorable.
Hey! No fair getting her to yourself!
Pet, pet, pet.
I'm petting you more gently
than she did, aren't I?
My petting is much softer
than hers, isn't it?
That is not true!
Pet, pet.
I can pet her more gently!
It's obvious that my way feels nicer!
Are you fighting or petting me?
Make up your minds.
Nope, I can't reach it.
Here you go, Sister.
Thanks, Rosalie.
Hey, Sister... if you want, um...
I could comb your hair for you.
You, too?
Okay, go for it.
Hmm... It's a very distant memory,
but I think I played with dolls this way
back when I lived in the mansion.
Dolls...
Sorry I took so long!
Oh, did you find a clue
to changing me back?
Yes!
I found nothing! I'm sorry!
Then why did you look
pleased with yourself?!
I decided to tell you the truth and
apologize, and this is what my face did!
All I can do is sincerely apologize!
This doesn't solve anything.
I have no choice but to ask the demons.
Vosanosanon ujishidau veyani enrila!
That was a nice bath.
You've gotten used to appearing
in the bathtub, huh?
Oh? Who is this?
You bear an uncanny resemblance to Azusa...
Shoop.
Could you be her daughter?
It's me. I'm Azusa.
I shrank because of a poison mushroom.
How cute! How adorable!
Hey! Don't treat me like a kid!
Resisting being treated like a
child makes you even cuter!
I see. So you decided to rely on
the knowledge of the demons.
Please do something!
I can't stay like this forever!
Can't you?
Would it not be nice to live as the
most adorable child there is?
Fine. I'll tell everyone the great
demon Beelzebub lost to a little kid.
That's not fair!
Very well. I'll search Vanzeld
Castle for a way to restore you.
You'll need to come with me.
All right.
We'll bring Shalsha and Falfa, as well.
Why?
It makes me happy.
Ah, that was just like being in Heaven!
What an explosion of cuteness!
Um, please don't tell
Pecora about this, okay?
If she finds out,
it'll complicate things for sure.
Greetings, Dear Sister.
I've been waiting for you.
I can't have you underestimating
the Demon King's power.
Shine!
I never dreamed you could look
so adorable, Dear Sister!
I want to go back to normal, though.
Oh, what a waste!
You should, at least, stay like
this until I get tired of it!
Pecora!
Then let's ask the members of your family.
Scoot, scoot...
Falfa and Shalsha, do you prefer
your mama as she is now,
or do you want her the way she was before?
If you choose "as she is now,"
I'll give you all the candy you want.
Um, what should we say?
The ultimate decision...
Don't be bought off with candy!
Mama wants to go back to normal!
Um...
All right, enough with the jokes.
Jokes?
Fwip!
Allow me to suggest a way you
can change back to normal.
Within the demon realm, in a forest
far, far away from the castle,
there is a massive tree
known as the World Tree.
At its very top is a pharmacist who
deals in every medicine ever known.
The World Tree?
We have to go that far to fix this?
Slow and steady wins the race.
It's better than trying some shady
treatment method, don't you think?
All right. I'll try climbing
up this World Tree, then.
What's the place like?
The inside of the World Tree is hollow,
and it's laid out like a complex maze.
The top is the 108th floor,
and on the way there are many areas
inhabited by ferocious wild animals.
A dungeon with 108 floors is pretty big.
But still, I have to go.
In that case, Vania, please take
Dear Sister to the World Tree.
So I really have to go, then?
I suppose I do...
Sending my younger sister alone
worries me. I will go, as well.
By the way, Beelzebub, you have plenty of
work to catch up on while they're away.
Understood.
Gloom...
Well, I'll be back soon.
I want to go with you!
It might be dangerous.
You two need to stay here.
Okay...
I know Mother will be fine.
All right!
Let's get going, Fatla, Vania!
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
World Tree
Wow...
Its size is pretty shocking
when I see it in person.
I haven't seen the World Tree in some time.
Since that school field trip, was it?
I came here for a field trip, too!
Wow, you've both been here before?
Okay, let's go.
Even if it's a complex, mysterious dungeon,
I'm doing this to go back to normal.
I'll get through it, no matter what!
Elevator to 10th floor just over there!
1300 Coyns
What does this mean?
Coyns are demon currency.
Not that. The elevator part.
Many people want to go higher
and higher up the World Tree,
which led to the sale of elevator usage.
The higher you want to
go, the more it costs.
I thought it'd be more like a dungeon...
It does have aspects of one, of course.
The 11th and 12th floors are home to
wild World Tree 11th Floor Wolves
and World Tree 12th Floor Wolves,
so we'll need to be careful.
What a dumb way to name animal species...
Wait, where's Vania?
I'm sorry!
I went to buy deep-fried
buns from that shop!
The deep-fried buns here are so
exquisite, they've become famous!
This is just a tourist trap!
That smells good...
Let me try a bit!
Good thing they gave you the
children's price, isn't it, Azusa?
Floor 1 → Floor 10
Step, step, step, step...
There's a lot I'd like to say here,
but let's head to floor 11.
We've got a long way to go.
They want 500 coyns per person
for wild animal conservation?
Incidentally, the 13th floor also has
a gate where you'll need to pay.
This seems like such a shoddy business...
Floor 11: Jungle Area
This definitely looks like a place
where scary animals would live.
What the heck?!
They're totally tame!
Where are the wild animals?!
Many visitors here are powerful demons,
so the animals are no longer hostile.
In fact, they learned to bow
their heads to beg for food.
Elevator to the 17th floor this way
2200 coyns per adult
Suddenly it costs more
to make less progress.
On the 18th floor, we can see
World Tree 18th Floor Wildcats
Meow!
and a rare plant called the
World Tree 18th Floor Rose.
Rose, rose!
And I bet there's another elevator
on the 19th floor, right?
Yes. I believe the fare is 3,000 coyns.
~ Floor 19
~ Floor 17
Floors 1~10
That's demonic business!
They really are demons!
This brings back memories.
When I came here on my field trip,
I tried to see how far I
could get without paying,
but I got lost and ended up
late to our meet-up time.
Life in this area relies
on the tourist industry,
so the maze here is more difficult.
They dig holes, add poisonous
swamps, and other things
to make sure visitors
will use the elevators.
They're building a dungeon...
Floor 11 → Floor 18
Step, step, step...
Rose, rose...
Floor 19 → Floor 38
Step, step, step...
It's getting late.
Let's stay here for the night.
Ka-tunk!
This feels so nice.
It's nothing like the
World Tree I had imagined...
Yes, there was no stopping its
transition to a tourist stop.
That said, there are no elevators
after the eighth station.
What is this, Mount Fuji?
Azusa, it might be a strange
way to bring this up, but...
Thank you for giving me this opportunity.
It had been a long time since my
sister and I took a trip together.
Yeah, I bet. You're both so busy with
work, I'm sure you never had time.
I must apologize. This is
part of our work, as well.
It's fine. Sorry for dragging you
both into such a weird task.
Well, the floors will be more
cramped from this point on,
so we'll be moving upward at a faster pace.
Tomorrow night, we'll
lodge on the 84th floor.
After that, it's a real
dungeon, with no lodging.
Right! Let's do this thing!
Floor 38 → Floor 39
Step, step, step...
Floor 39 → Floor 85
Please be careful.
This floor is home to drooling
sloths and snot-nosed sloths.
Durr!
They are ferocious, so they will attack.
Kiddie Punch!
Durr!
As far as my stats go, I still
seem to be doing pretty well.
Wow! That was amazing!
Durr!
You can leave these to me!
You two are pretty strong, too!
I guess you are Leviathans, huh?
Yes!
Durr!
Now, let us hurry.
Floor 89
Floor 96
Floor 102
Floor 87 → Floor 107
Floor 107
We made it...
I didn't say anything yet.
I knew what you were going to say.
We've come this far together, after all.
I guess so.
What's this? I feel kind of strange.
I'm not normally the type to cry...
You mustn't.
We're still on the job.
When we were still children,
you nearly jumped off and fell
from here, didn't you, Vania?
I didn't do anything that clumsy.
You were the one who just started
complaining more as we kept going.
And then Father said we never
should have brought you along.
Well, climbing that volcano
really was exhausting.
And it took longer than we expected.
As I always tell you, not everything
works out exactly as scheduled.
Or maybe you're just too lazy.
Floor 108
Excuse me.
I ate a gnome-maker mushroom
and became smaller.
Do you have any medicine that
can change me back to normal?
Ah, yes, yes.
Until recently, that mushroom's
effects were difficult to treat,
but I've since learned that a certain
medicine works well against it.
Really?
Yes, it's become a huge hit.
Here it is.
Isn't this...
It's made by a witch named Eno who's
well-known as the Witch of the Cave.
Ah, yeah. Right.
Hello! It's the Witch of the Cave, Eno!
I brought three more
cases of that medicine!
Eno!
What are you doing here?!
Huh? Whose child are you?
Wait, are you... the Witch
of the Highlands?!
Wow! You actually walked
all the way up here?
Yeah...
Dragons can't make it, but wyverns
can come straight to the top.
They carry medicines and such.
Also, it doesn't make sense.
I deliver Mandragora Pills
to Vanzeld Castle, too.
I'm certain the Demon King
knows I transport them there.
Wha—
I forgot that a wyvern could
fly straight to the top!
Oopsie!
Tee-hee!
No, you totally knew. And you
knew about the medicine, too.
Whatever do you mean?
Never mind.
We were allowed to ride a wyvern
back to get here faster.
I just want to take that
medicine and have a bath.
I'm a mess after that crazy adventure.
Wait a moment!
You might as well return to
normal in front of everyone.
Well, we did work hard to get this.
Maybe that would be more moving.
Really? It was just Mandragora Pills?
You worked so hard for nothing.
All's well that ends well.
I'm going back to normal now.
Here it comes!
I'm apprehensive about this.
If she gets bigger,
she won't fit in children's clothes.
Oh, Dear Sister! How scandalous!
As your little sister,
I can't bear to watch!
Pecora! You knew this would
happen and didn't tell me!
I don't know what you
mean. I haven't the foggiest!
At this point, we all might
as well take a bath!
We'll all be naked together,
including you! Got it?!
Huh?
There's nothing better than a big bath.
I hear you.
It hits even deeper when
you're exhausted from work.
Pecora.
D-Dear Sister!
Does being in the bath with
all of us embarrass you?
N-No, it's just... I-I'm not
used to this sort of thing...
Oh, yeah. Since you're the Demon King,
I guess you wouldn't take
baths with anyone.
But when you get me, I get you back.
I'm gonna get a good look at you naked!
Th-That's scandalous!
Being naked is the proper
attire for a bath.
Besides, it's not embarrassing when
everyone's in it together, right?
Still, you took your joke a
little too far this time.
Listen, Pecora.
No matter what your reason is,
I'm your older sister,
and if my little sister does
something bad, I'll scold her.
Understand?
I'm sorry.
Good girl.
No more hard feelings, right?
Um, Dear Sister...
What?
I always dreamed of getting a kiss
because of the books I read,
but nothing beyond that was
written in the books.
Ah. So that's the most
you could imagine, huh?
You're very pure.
So there's something I'd
like you to do for me.
Just name it.
May I... touch your breasts?
What?! What are you saying?!
I thought I should get used to it, too!
I hoped touching your chest
would get me more accustomed!
That is not allowed!
Why isn't it allowed, Dear Sister?!
If the Demon King had some weird awakening,
it'd cause irreversible damage!
I can't grant that favor!
Dear Sister!
For the sake of world peace,
you need to remain pure!