Wow, how pretty!
That's right. I guess it
is festival season now.
What sort of festival is it?
It's Flatta's dance festival.
It started about 250 years ago,
and everyone dances however they please
in the town square or the highlands.
It's about offering the fruits
of the harvest to the earth god
and praying for a bountiful
harvest next year.
The celebration lasts two days,
both on the festival's eve and the day of the festival.
It's nice to be able to
dance however you please!
Are you going to participate, Lady Azusa?
I distance myself from this one a bit.
I've been living around here since
before the festival started,
so if I'm not careful, I could end
up being given the starring role.
I see...
Does this festival have stalls
that sell sweet candies?
The study of festivals is
historically important.
You know, drinks can be
sold at festivals, too.
Even at higher prices,
they sell like hotcakes.
At times, I felt like they make
a little too much profit...
That's true... My family
did grow all of a sudden.
Since we're here, maybe I'll try to change
how I interact with these things.
What should I do, though?
More fruit wine, please!
Halkara, you can drink,
but don't go overboard, okay?
I make drinks out of plants myself,
so I can't help drinking them to compare...
She can make drinks...
I see.
They add pepper as a secret ingredient.
I'm going to try making
this sauce sometime.
And she can cook...
Mama!
Have some water!
I got some share plates.
Thanks, you two.
And we have two cute waitresses!
I have an idea!
We'll open a coffee shop called
The Witch's House on festival's eve!
I've Been Killing Slimes for 300 Years
and Maxed Out My Level
We Opened a Coffee Shop
Sister, it's here!
Ta-da!
What is this?
Waitress uniforms for The Witch's House.
Remember when we all got
measured the other day?
Let's all try them on right now!
Well, I guess it works.
Mama!
Float, float...
How do we look?
It doesn't feel that bad...
Blush!
Hug!
Yes! You're adorable!
Um...
Boing, boing.
They took my measurements,
but the chest is still so tight...
Plump.
What kind of shady shop are we running?!
Halkara, if you wear that,
you're banned from the shop.
Shock!
We haven't even opened up yet!
Flatorte, you look so cute!
It's very harmonious.
It's almost as if they used
the golden ratio somehow.
Y-You think so?
Personally, I find it very restrictive.
I feel more comfortable naked.
The great Flatorte will
fight this battle naked!
There's no way that's better!
Aw, you're all so lucky.
I wish I could try something on, too.
You'll be changing your
outfit, too, of course.
Allow this outstretched
hand to reach the other side!
Work, magic!
Change, Rosalie!
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
Wow, this is great!
Thank you, Sister!
Sure. You look great.
Now, that just leaves Laika...
A god... There's a god here...
It, um...
doesn't look too odd, does it?
Priceless...
I wore something like this for
a school play long ago...
I got the same reaction and
felt just as embarrassed.
Oh, that embarrassed face!
Priceless!
Freeze...
Please don't say the same
thing over and over!
All right! Now we come up with our menu!
Hop!
Sounds like it's my turn!
I've already come up with this!
Hmm...
Okay, this "Fifteen-Flavor
Aphrodisiac Drink Blend" is out.
Why?! It was a huge hit
among the men of Flatta!
I'm still in my prime!
Pop!
That's not the image we want!
And this "Drink Daily to Grow Taller in a Month!
Bone-Lengthening Herbal Blend" is out, too.
Shabam!
Come up with something more normal!
Well, if you want something else...
All I have is this "Wild Grape and Honey Juice
with a Light Flavor and Pleasant Aftertaste."
That's what you should've given me first!
Honestly, you have no
sense for this at all.
You're the one who lacks sense!
What's all the fuss over here?
Lady Azusa!
Please hear out my idea!
Anyone who can eat this giant
omelet within 30 minutes
gets their meal free! What do you think?
Uh, I'm not sure we want
competitive eating material...
It's unthinkable!
What is cooking without meat?
So we serve endless delicious meat dishes!
Om.
This is all we need!
No, it's not!
Both of you are wrong!
Then what about topping boiled pasta
with sweet cream for something unique?
I like that you're up for a challenge,
but that's not necessary!
Master!
Shine!
Slide, slide...
Then let's serve a full-course meal
using 36 types of mushrooms!
Some are gonna be poisonous, though.
Mama!
Look at the big grasshopper I caught!
What if we cook this grasshopper?
We can't serve that in the shop.
I'll come up with the menu!
There we go.
All right, that's done!
Great Witch!
I look forward to seeing your shop.
It's a coffee shop, The Witch's House!
It's opening tomorrow.
Please come and visit.
Check out our coffee shop,
The Witch's House!
We'll have tasty food!
Please come and visit.
You'd better come!
Here you go!
Not bad.
Thanks, everyone.
So, tomorrow's the day we open.
Though I'm not sure if anyone will come...
No, the most important thing
is that we have fun.
Let's all have fun tomorrow!
Yeah!
Well, gotta start getting
things ready early...
I've Been Killing Slimes
for 300 Years and
Maxed Out My Level
This is...
Wow...
They're even coming from outside of Flatta.
Hmm, lining up overnight
is against the rules.
Slither...
Nope, I heard the first ones rushed
here first thing in the morning.
That's okay, then!
We'll have to open ahead of schedule!
Yeah!
Our coffee shop, The Witch's House,
is opening one hour early!
Nobody cheers like that for
a coffee shop opening!
Welcome!
Welcome to our coffee shop,
The Witch's House!
The Great Witch looks
beautiful as a waitress...
Float...
And Halkara looks like the perfect
balance of wholesome and unwholesome.
Float...
May we take your order?
Here's some water.
Her twin daughters couldn't be cuter!
Yes, but above all...
Thank you for waiting.
Here is the omelet you ordered.
Please take your time enjoying your meal.
She's a goddess.
If I had a little sister like that,
I'd be hugging her all the time.
No words are needed... Just...
Priceless!
P-Please don't stare at me so much...
It's embarrassing...
Pshoom!
Hey, hang in there!
It's a shallow wound!
What kind of shop is this?
I hate that Laika is getting
all the attention!
I won't lose to her!
Bam! Bam! Bam!
I can carry all these at once!
Ooh!
Amazing!
How wonderful!
It's a piece of cake!
Wait, if you try to do that...
That was a close one.
There!
The ghost lady is the best!
That's fantastic service!
Thanks.
I guess people enjoy service with style.
Master!
This juice is really refreshing.
And the soup warms me right up.
It's so homely, but so elegant, too.
The wall decorations are adorable.
They all seem to enjoy both
the food and the atmosphere.
All right, everyone, keep up the good work!
Okay!
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, Mother.
My feet can't take any more.
No, I'm sorry I didn't notice.
Just take it easy.
No, I'll take over the register.
This way, I can keep working.
Thank you. But don't overdo it, okay?
Sputter, sputter...
Here's your milk tea!
Here's your salad with forest tree nuts!
Sputter, sputter...
So three coffees, a mini chiffon
cake, and two fruit cakes...
And for you, a black tea, a milk,
a special omelet, and a sandwich?
It's a good kind of surprise, but I
never thought we'd be this successful.
What a fine shop.
Thank you for waiting!
How many in... your...
Don't you have anything to do at work?
You're being awfully rude to a customer.
Did I tell you we were doing this?
You did not!
I only came because I
happened to hear about it!
Don't I always tell you to invite me
along when you're doing something fun?
Hmph!
Oh, she wanted to be invited.
Hey, Beelzebub, it's not too late to
help us serve customers if you want...
I mean... i-if you could, maybe?
I-If you can't, it's okay...
I am a demon, you know.
I'm not someone you can so
easily ask for a favor.
Don't let your head get so big.
Beelzebub, that's... the back door...
Well, I suppose I don't mind.
You're raring to go!
When did you change clothes?!
She's the head waitress, but she has
the intense aura of a queen...
No, she has both the dignity of a soldier
and the class of a proper lady.
She gives off the scent
of something forbidden!
Welcome to our coffee shop, The Witch's House!
When you've decided what you'd
like to order, just let me know.
She's perfect!
Hey, cooks!
An herb tea, carrot chiffon cake set,
and two mixed juices, please!
She's turned out to be quite the helper.
I can't believe she's even
changed her tone of voice.
With Beelzebub helping us now,
maybe we can breathe a little easier.
There's no sign of the crowd
starting to thin, though...
Okay, here we go!
Flick!
Now do it with me, okay?
Be delicious!
Float...
I added a bit of little devil spice, too!
Squee!
You're way past "little devil"!
What are you doing?!
Turn!
Dear Sister!
Sparkle!
What do you think?
Does my outfit look cute?
Should a Demon King who terrifies crying
babies into silences be serving customers?
Of course!
I always wanted to be a part of
a shop like this just once!
Wait, if you're here, does that mean...
And here's your fosca sheep
sauté with truffles!
I thought so.
It's the chef's special platter.
My sister came up with an improved
version for human palates.
She just made herself the chef!
Chef, one more of the special!
Got it!
And it's already on the menu...
Halkara, please take this
dessert menu to table three.
Yes, Manager!
And Fatla's the floor manager now!
A group just came in!
Huh?
I have an addition to an order!
There are so many customers!
Huh?!
Master! Is that outfit some
new kind of training?
I'll help, too!
What are you doing here?
I have some samples of the Eno
brand's latest supplement!
Feel free to take one! Here you go!
Hey! Did anyone say you could do that?
Here's a free song for all
the folks waiting in line!
Listen to the cries of
Kuku and Flatorte's souls!
This is turning into something
kind of crazy...
Nothing to do but continue doing my job!
Great Witch, thank you for the lovely meal.
Thank you for coming.
Well, I guess we can close up now.
This new product uses fruit juice
to counter the bitterness.
Let's talk business sometime.
Let's perform together again!
I'll write a song that'll
make your heart tremble!
Master, please spar with me!
Just go home already.
Dear Sister!
Flash!
Zoom!
I had so much fun today!
Stretch!
I'll come help again!
Hug!
See you next time.
Goodbye.
Thanks for your help, everyone.
All right.
Good work, everyone!
Same to you, Lady Azusa.
We still need to clean up,
but I guess we can take our time.
It's been 300 years since
I reincarnated here.
After finding out I had maxed out my level,
my life turned around completely.
If this keeps up,
I bet lots more fun and
hectic things will happen.
Although if I'm comparing my recent life
to the 300 years before that,
my recent life is still new, but I can
confidently say it's had lots more fun times.
The cost, list price, and profit...
Coffee and chocolate cake....
A biba non non!
Living a slow life alone was nice,
but living a slow life with others
is special in its own way.
And this is still the result of all
those years defeating slimes,
so I can't forget the debt
I owe to the slimes.
That said, there are slimes everywhere,
so I'm sure I'll have to
face one eventually.
But for now, our coffee shop is done.
I think I'd like to live a nice
peaceful life for a while.
Master.
Tonight is the main event of
Flatta's dance festival.
I wonder what it's like!
I want to go!
I'm interested.
Lady Azusa, I'd like to go, as well.
Then I guess we'll all go
check it out tonight.
Yay!
I will show you my demon dance!
Do you have nothing better to do?
Wha—
Have you no gratitude after all
the work I did yesterday?
Slide!
Thanks for helping yesterday, Beelzebub!
You were a big help.
Oh, it was nothing.
You can ask for my help again anytime.
You really can't resist those two, can you?
There, there. You're so cute.
I'm gonna dance, too!
I'll let it all hang out!
Don't you dare! You'll bring
shame to all Dragons!
Boing, boing, boing, boing, boing...
I'm quite confident in
my dancing skills, too!
I'd rather you didn't dance, either.
Why not, Master?
At any rate, if you get out of hand
at the festival, they'll ban you.
How rude!
Come on, Master!
What's wrong with my dancing?
Look, just...
Hey, Beelzebub!
What's your dance like?
It's a mysterious dance handed down
among demons that sucks out mana.
Another peaceful day...
Yes, I'm coming.
How can I help you?
After 300 years of killing slimes,
another fun day is about to begin.