Hey, Yuu.
What?
Where are we, exactly?
Dunno. It's white as far as the eye can see.
It's almost like we're the only people in the world.
You sure have it easy, spouting off poetry.
Meanwhile, I'm desperately trying to find us
a place for us to ride out the cold...
That, or...
We're actually already dead, and we're in
the pure-white world of the afterlife.
Don't say that; it's bad luck.
And stop making snowballs.
Aww, I was just starting to have fun!
My head feels heavy, and I'm really cold.
Hey, did you know that the afterlife
is supposed to be really warm?
If that's true, then it doesn't look like we're dead yet.
Sure is cold...
Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
W-we've gotta find a place to rest soon...
Yeah...
Yuu, wake up!
I'm not sleeping.
A b-b-building...
It's big.
Wh-wh-what kind of building is it?
N-no clue.
Let's find a way in.
Whew.
72nd Surface
Power Plant
C-can't read it...
This facility's pretty old.
Don't know how to get in.
Hey, look, look!
What's up?
Th-that pipe doesn't have any snow on it at all.
It's melting?
I-is it hot?!
Lemme shoot it.
H-hot water!
Hot water!
Wh-what should we do?
What do you mean? C'mon.
I'm glad we found a pipe in such good condition.
Yeah.
There we go: a bath.
Let's get in.
Bath
Hot!
The water feels really good, Chi!
Y-yeah.
Feels good...
how long has it been since we had a bath?
I think we've taken two since leaving Grandpa's.
Three.
Huh. So this is our fourth.
I feel like I've been brought back to life.
This is paradise, pure paradise...
Hey, what does "paradise" mean anyway?
It means the afterlife.
That's an unlucky thing to say
after we've been brought back to life.
Yeah.
Ugh, I'm getting dizzy.
Journal
The wind sure is blowing hard.
Yeah, huh.
Glad we found a place we could stay.
We went into a building and
blocked the entrance with snow.
We were lucky to have scrap material
we could use to help retain heat.
Oh, add more fuel.
Okay, okay.
One okay is enough.
Okay.
Must be nice for you, Chi,
making me do all the annoying work.
If you don't have the brains, use your brawn.
You can't even read or write.
Huh.
What're you writing again?
It's a journal or log I've been keeping since we left.
I explained it to you before.
You did?
People like you are exactly why
we need to have a journal like this.
Memories fade, so we write them down.
Memories just get in the way of living.
Can you remember the last time you ate?
Huh? Did we eat today?
Seriously?
Books are really amazing.
Ever since they were invented thousands of years ago,
humanity has been recording things in books.
Huh.
It's thanks to books that we can learn about
things that happened long ago.
You've always liked books, huh, Chi.
You read a whole lot of Grandpa's books.
Yeah, but we had to burn most of them.
Excluding the couple of journals, we have...
One, two, three... four books.
Lemme see.
Sure.
KAPPA
Akutagawa
I wonder how many books are left in the world.
I see.
The fire's getting low. Add more fuel.
Okay.
We don't have much fuel left to burn.
What, are we out of fuel?
The book!
Put it out!
Hot, hot!
Not Kappa...
Kappa?
I literally just told you books were important!
Sorry, I wasn't really listening!
Listen!
I said I was sorry.
Moron! Idiot! Garbage!
Okay.
Don't "okay" me!
Whatever, I'm going to bed!
Chi.
Journal
Chito
C'mon, Yuu, hurry it up.
Chi, are you still mad at me?
No.
You definitely are.
Ready, go!
The storm cleared up!
The snow sure piled up.
What do you think, doable?
Think so.
Hey, are you still mad?
No.
Hurry up and get on.
Even if we lost a book, we still have the journals.
Hup.
If we keep writing things in our journal,
it'll be like a book...
What is this?
Hey, Yuu, you drew something in here, didn't you?
Did I?
Don't go drawing in here.
What is this, even?
It's your face, Chi.
My face doesn't look like this.
It's what you look like when you're asleep.
I wanna draw some more now.
We're short on paper, so don't.
Aww.
And you wrote a letter wrong.
Huh?
I'M SOKKY
"I'M SOKKY"?
Think it's around here.
Sure is nice out, despite it all.
It's been nice out for a bit now.
That's why I figure it's gonna be coming soon.
What's coming?
C'mon, you can hear it.
There it is.
The water from the melted snow.
So that's what you meant, the snow water.
Sure is a lot.
Because it's been warm now for a few days.
It must have really filled up.
Why does a whole lot come out all at once?
Because the ancient city's drainage system
is still here, or something.
In any case, what's important is
we get some drinking water.
We going down on foot?
Yeah, it can't get down there.
Hup.
That, and...
Gotta take our shoes off.
Cold!
So cold!
It's so blue, Chi.
It's like we're in the sky.
Watch your step.
The water might've washed down something sharp.
Let's look up while we walk, Chi.
Look up!
I just told you to watch where you step.
What a waste when the sky's so blue!
When the sky's so blue,
it's good weather for a laundry day.
Laundry
Cold!
What's this rope for?
We could get hurt if we get washed away by a current.
The water gets deep in places, too.
Are you gonna take off your helmet?
I could get hurt if I fell.
Half-naked with a helmet...
Our clothes sure are pretty dirty.
Why is the sky blue?
Hey, Yuu, why're you acting so laid back?
I got the water.
You gotta wash your clothes, too.
Seriously?
Hey, Chi, why is the sky blue?
People long ago said it was
reflecting the blue of the ocean.
The ocean?
It's a place with water that's way bigger
and way deeper than this puddle.
The water under our feet would go on forever.
I heard people long ago lived by the ocean.
Hey, look, look, Chi!
I told you to listen to-
Hey! You idiot, don't start running all of a sudden!
I'm glad I was wearing my helmet.
C'mon, look, look!
Why are you all wet, too?
I fell.
Forget that, look at this!
It's... a fish.
Fish...
Looks like it's dead though.
What's a fish?
It's a living thing that lives in water.
I heard there were a lot of them in the ocean long ago.
I thought humans were the only
living things still out there...
Okay, let's eat it!
What? Can we eat it?
I heard people ate fish long ago,
but is this one okay?
It doesn't look like it's started to decompose...
Well, maybe we can eat it if we roast it.
Let's roast it!
After we hang up our clothes to dry.
Hey, I wonder what it feels like to live in the water.
Dunno. Probably floating, and sinking...
I heard they flap these fins to move forward.
Fins...
Maybe it swam like that.
Maybe.
Should be done by now.
Let's eat it!
Be careful, it's hot.
All right!
Hot!
H-how is it?
It's good!
Let me try.
Don't eat all of it!
I've never tasted anything like it.
It's weird.
Me! I'm next!
Our clothes are all clean now.
And these bones must feel refreshed
with all the meat cleaned off them.
Refreshed, huh...
But where did it come in from?
It must have come in from a higher level, huh...
Maybe if we go up higher,
we'll find a whole bunch of them.
And what if we do?
We eat them.
Eat them, huh...
Yeah.
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey
Farewell.
Bye bye!