Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
Hey, Yuu.
What?
Why do people live?
Hiya!
Why'd you hit me?
I thought you might've gone crazy.
I haven't!
We go around looking for food, right?
We find it, save it, then go on the move again,
always thinking there might be something
waiting for us at our destination...
Ugh, she fell asleep, didn't she.
I'm also interested in learning
where that fish came from.
That tower's gotta keep going up into a higher level...
Well? You find a bridge?
No bridge, huh.
Wish there was something
we could do to help us cross.
What's up?
What's that?
A cigarette.
It's still burning.
Does stuff start burning on its own?
No.
Someone's here.
Chi.
There are footprints.
Yuu, load your gun.
Streetlights
Yuu, are you okay?!
I think so.
What the heck was that...
H-hey. Stop!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Sorry, it's been so long since I spoke,
I can't speak well...
A detonator?
Are you the one who took down that building?
Yeah, that was me.
Thought I'd make a bridge.
Never figured there were people around.
I'm glad you didn't get caught up in the explosion.
I'm Kanazawa.
I'm making a map as I go on my way.
Umm, could you please put down your gun?
Can I put it down?
Yeah.
There was just no way of getting across that gorge.
Good idea, right?
We can cross on top of this.
I see.
You almost killed us in the process, though.
Yeah...
Over here, too.
Is that your vehicle?
Yeah.
Where're you going?
We thought about going across
the gorge to that tower.
Tower?
Thought it might be a way to get to a higher level.
Huh. If that's the case,
there's a little favor I'd like to ask of you...
Favor?
Don't mind letting you ride.
You made us a bridge, after all.
You're good.
Gonna be hard getting this up and over, though...
Stop!
Chi.
What do you think?
Think I can get up...
I tried to take the building down
in a way that it'd be easy to get over...
It's pretty hard...
We could get up it pretty easy
if we didn't have this guy.
I've never seen anything like it.
Did you have a vehicle, Kanazawa?
I had a motorbike, but...
...it broke down.
That's why you want a ride with us.
Just to the entrance to the higher level.
I'll find a way to manage from there.
You made it up.
So tired...
Working up a sweat for the first time in a while
really makes you feel alive, huh?
Alive?
Chi was saying earlier,
she didn't know if we were still alive.
I didn't say anything like that.
Thanks.
Come to think of it, I still haven't asked your names.
I'm Chito. That's Yuuri.
I see. Nice to meet you.
Same.
It's really here.
This is the last one around this area.
It's a legit refueling station.
Let's see...
This should be it. Hose is...
No hose.
Yuu, bring it over.
'Kay.
A little more right.
Here?
Okay.
You're good.
Oh, it's coming out!
That's smart.
We'll transfer it to the tank...
...fill it up once more, and head out.
Lift your legs.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry it's a tight squeeze.
It's alright. You're the ones giving me a ride.
But it was thanks to your map that we
found a refueling station right away.
It worked out for both of us.
There are a lot of residential buildings in this area.
The area around a connection tower
to a higher level is always densely populated.
Though nobody lives here now...
Then maybe the people who lived here built the tower.
No, I don't think so.
I think the people who made the levels of the city
were humans from much longer ago.
I think our ancestors just came to live in
the infrastructure those ancient peoples created.
I see.
Oh, left there.
Got it.
We aren't getting much closer to the tower.
Though we've been able to see it the whole time...
This area's really complicated.
You've gotta take a lot of roundabout ways to get in.
Is the map actually right?
It's accurate.
The refueling station was where I said it was, right?
How'd you make that map?
I traveled all around on my bike,
then climbed up to high places
to check if it was right.
So you've been over there before?
Yeah, back when there was a bridge over that gorge.
I've mapped out most of this level.
Wow! Lemme see, lemme see!
Sure, just be really careful with it.
Be careful. She burns other people's books.
I won't burn it.
Is it really that important?
It's what I live for!
What you live for?
You don't run into other people that often
in this world, so there's not much else to do.
If I lost this, I'd probably die.
Alright, let's burn it!
P-please, don't! Wait, why?!
Just wondering if you'd really die if you lost it.
What are you, the Devil?
You've got something important to you too, don't you?
Something important, huh...
Like Chi's journal.
Sure, it's important to me,
but not so important that I'd die.
Yuu, you wouldn't give up your food
even if you were dead, huh?
That's not how it is.
It isn't.
I said it's not.
Oh, turn right there.
Got it.
We should be really close.
Sure is big.
It's huge.
Hey, if you go up there, are you gonna
make a map of the higher levels?
Yeah.
You look real happy, Kanazawa.
All full of life.
Really?
The real elevator's supposed to be inside the tower,
but nobody knew how to make it work.
So instead, they made this thing.
This was supposedly made
over a hundred years ago, too.
That's old.
It's alright, looks like it'll move.
You're good, you're good.
It's not gonna break down while we're on it, right?
I don't know...
I'm sure it's fine.
You sure are optimistic.
She's so optimistic, she's gotta have a screw loose.
If we go to a higher level,
maybe we'll find way more food,
and lots of people living happily up there...
Wow!
We're high up.
About what you said before...
It's true that there aren't many places left
where you can find food on this level.
And the places where you can get fuel
or water are dying off one by one.
It's possible that the higher and newer the level,
the more of the city facilities remain.
It's just my guess, though.
Chi? What's wrong?
Nothing.
You don't have to force yourself to stand.
No, I'm fine.
Are you bad with heights?
Why isn't there a chain-link fence on here?!
The view's so pretty.
They probably thought it was a waste of materials.
What if it tilts and we fall?
All we've got are these handrails!
It's not gonna tilt all that easily.
It tilted!
Stop it, Kanazawa!
It stopped.
It might've hit something on the rail.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
My map!
You idiot!
Let go of me. Let me fall, too.
Yeah, right!
Ready, up!
Why wasn't there a chain-link fence...
They probably thought it was a waste of materials.
We're all going to die anyway...
There's no point in living.
In any case, we've gotta take a look at the rail.
Can we fix it?
I'm glad it worked.
I wasn't sure what we'd do if we couldn't get it to work.
It's gotten pretty dark, huh.
He's still depressed.
Hey, Kanazawa.
The streetlights...
They're alive!
I wonder what's at that really bright place.
Kanazawa.
You can have this.
It's fruit flavored.
You don't need a reason.
There are nice things sometimes.
Even in this world?
Probably.
I mean, look how pretty the view is.
It's good!
Right?
Thanks.
Oh, right. As thanks for sharing food with me...
It's a photograph machine.
The machine they call a "camera"?
They call it that, too.
Well, have fun with it.
Thank you.
Well, then...
Where are you going?
Thought I'd head north.
I see.
I'm gonna make a map again.
I wonder if we'll meet him again.
Who knows.
Okay, we should get a move on, too.
Our back's opened up again.
Wasn't bad having three people, though.
For now, let's head towards that really bright place.
I wonder what's over there.
Who knows.
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey
Wonder how far I can make it on foot.