Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Say "cheese."
Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
What's "cheese"?
Dunno.
I read in a book that's the kinda signal you give.
Huh.
Cheese.
Isn't it kinda white?
Dunno why... maybe I turned it too much.
You suck.
What?
Photograph
Spin, spin, spin, spin...
C'mon, let's go.
Always better to move when it's still bright out.
Okay!
Whoa...
Hey. Lemme borrow this.
Don't break it.
Don't worry.
Well?
It's blurry.
You have to focus it with the dial on the front.
What dial?
Must be this.
There we go.
Kanazawa should've shown us
how to use it if he was giving it to us...
Oh, right. As thanks for sharing food with me...
It's a photograph machine.
The machine they call a "camera"?
They call it that, too.
Well, have fun with it.
Looks like it's pretty old, so even though
he said to have fun with it, well...
Pretty amazing people back then
could make stuff like this.
Jeez. It's still blurry.
Maybe 'cause we're moving.
There are a lot of those stone statues around here.
Wonder why.
They look a little like your face, Chi.
They don't.
Hey, look here.
What?
No good, it's still blurry.
Look this way one more time, Chi,
and this time, don't move.
You know, I'm driving, I can't look away.
It's fine, it's fine.
Ow, ow...
Don't look away from the road when you're driving!
Ow!
I'm gonna hold onto the camera after all.
Aww, jeez, you're so strict, Chi!
It's dented a little, but looks okay.
I wish your heart were as big
as these stone statues, Chi.
What? Why'd the shutter go off on its own?
Did you mess with it, Yuu?
I might've pushed something
when we ran into that thing.
"Something"...
Is this it?
What?
I think I'm figuring out what this dial is for.
Tell me.
No.
Meanie.
Shut up.
So?
If we keep it up, we'll be able to get
to that glowing building.
I see. That's good.
You sure took a lot... like an idiot.
You still mad at me?
I'm not mad.
Look, it's got a ring! That one's got a ring on it.
There's something growing out of that one.
You took way too many pictures of those statues.
Who cares, it's not like we can use it up or anything.
No, you can.
Really?
How many more can we take?
It's probably this number here.
What number?
This must be the number remaining.
It's gone down from earlier.
Umm, forty... no, that's a five...
Fifty-two thousand.
That's a really big number, huh?
Yeah.
Way more than your books, right Chi?
How do they all fit inside this thing?
I don't think that's how it works.
Then how does it?
I dunno...
Fifty-two thousand...
How many more days of food do we have left?
Thirty days for the two of us.
We won't run out of pictures before then.
Well, I could eat all the food by myself in seven days.
That's not funny.
Ch...
Chee...
Cheese
Chi, the food today's "cheese"-flavored!
Cheese, huh?
What IS "cheese"?
It's weird.
If you eat food, it gets used up,
but if you take pictures, they're here forever.
When the town falls apart and
even those stone statues all break down,
those pictures might still be there.
Yuu.
What're you doing?
The thing I figured out earlier.
Don't move.
Cheese.
That really bright building...
...is probably this one here.
It was really bright when we saw it at night...
...but it's dark inside.
Sure is big.
Wonder what kind of building it was.
It has a lot of really big statues.
All those statues, too.
What is this place?
Dunno...
Maybe this place was a temple?
Temple?
Temple
A temple, a place where a god lives.
Maybe these statues are like gods.
Gods...
What's a god?
A god is like...
I dunno.
Can you eat it?
You can't.
Huh.
Let's see...
What does it say?
Umm...
About four hundred years before now, built...
Revering three gods...
Huh.
So this really is like a temple.
"Western Paradise"...
"Paradise" means the world after death...
It says this temple is a reproduction
of the world beyond.
This is way different than a hot spring.
"May you be released from your sadnesses
and worries, and find happiness..."
Between this and a hot spring,
I like hot spring "paradise" more.
It has stuff written about the god, too.
A being that lights up the world beyond death...
It's not really clear about it...
Huh?
Chi?
It's pitch black.
Hey!
Is the afterlife like this?
No warmth,
so dark you can't see,
with nobody there...
If I lost Chi... what would I do?
Ow, ow, ow...
Chi...
is this your face?
It's my stomach.
Jeez, why didn't you say anything back, Chi?
Your reaction was too hilarious.
A being that lights up the world...
Is this Paradise?
Paradise...
It's like the floor is lighting up, too.
It's reflecting the light.
These are fake plants.
They're made of metal.
Chi, look, look!
What?
Fish!
It's fake, too.
Fake... so we can't eat it then?
Just look at it.
It's encased in the glass.
Looks like the surface of water.
I'm so disappointed.
I'm disappointed in this god.
It's just a stone statue.
You keep saying that and
you'll bring about divine punishment.
But we already knocked over
a stone statue before coming here.
It was just a stone statue.
So it really is just a statue.
Eating rations while looking at
the afterlife is pretty weird.
They're good.
But I just don't get it.
Even this nice god is still all a fake, right?
What's the point of making
a big disappointment like this?
Nobody knows what life's like after death anyway.
Huh...
Remember what you said earlier in the dark, Yuu?
That the afterlife is a dark world.
Maybe they didn't want to think that,
so they made those statues and all the lights.
To feel at ease.
At ease, huh...
I felt way more at ease after I found you, though.
In the dark.
Maybe...
Maybe?
Maybe Chi is a god?!
How would I know?
You have to offer food to gods.
Gimme.
Now I feel like you're not.
No way!
What if I'm a god?
Definitely not.
I am a God.
Nope.
Give me food!
No.
Give!
No!
Me!
No.
Food!
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey
I am a God.