Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
There's a lotta electricity and water left around,
but still no people.
Even though there are all these houses.
I bet a lotta people used to live here.
How many do you mean by "a lot"?
Like a thousand.
That's a lot.
Or maybe even more.
I dunno.
House
Hey.
What?
What are houses for again?
Well, you couldn't live without a house.
Yeah, but we don't have a house now.
Yeah, well.
Hey, what about that? Isn't that a house?
Huh?
Our vehicle.
It's not a house.
Answer either yes or no.
No.
HOUSE sad.
Shut up.
Well, we did have a house a long time ago.
But we lost it, so...
Huh?
This room actually has a door.
You're right.
There're things in here.
This is a pretty nice room.
The water works, too.
This is a nice chair.
What a nice view.
The sun's getting pretty low,
so we might as well stay here.
Okay, let's try it.
Wait, really?
This kinda thing's the stuff of dreams.
What dreams?
Living in a place like this.
Yeah.
It's pretty nice, having an actual roof
and four walls surrounding you.
Yeah.
Oh, if we're gonna live here, I want some stuff.
You know, like a bed.
A bed, huh...
I saw one once that had two levels for two people.
Looked like this.
Oh, that's cool! I want one!
I'd wanna put it over there.
I call the top!
You don't mind being on bottom, right?
You're bad with heights, after all.
Yeah.
Oh, I'd want a bookshelf, too.
What's that?
Really? It's a bunch of shelves with books on them.
It holds tons of books.
Okay, okay, then I want a pantry!
What's that?
It's a bunch of shelves with lots of food on them.
And... I'd want a heater, too.
Like a stove heater.
And a bathtub, too.
I heard people long ago
decorated houses with plants.
I wanna try that.
Let's decorate it with stone statues, too!
We don't need those.
This is nice...
That would be really nice.
If we lazed around here,
we'd run out of food in no time.
Yeah.
It's getting late. Let's just stay here for the night.
In the end, we're back to a cycle
of resupplying and traveling.
That means the road we travel is our house.
A great house with no roof.
HOUSE awesome!
Oh, why don't we put a roof on this thing?
Like this!
No, we're good.
Chi, wall, wall!
I can't, I'm too tired.
Let's take a break, yeah?
It's all 'cause we were up late last night.
'Cause it was so bright...
Man, we sure had a lotta fun last night.
I wouldn't say "fun"...
Okay, you're up, Chi.
Hey, there was a breeze just now!
Maybe there was.
That makes ten wins for me.
Okay, let's do one more.
Hey, why don't we bet one stick
of tomorrow's rations on this one?
Wait, you'll lose, so maybe we shouldn't.
One stick?
Sure, but no "breeze" this time.
There's no breeze right now.
I ended up having to give you a stick...
And she's asleep.
Nap
An earthquake?!
What is this?
Chi, Chi!
Yuu?
You okay?
You're huge.
You idiot, don't move!
L-listen up, Yuu, it'll be really bad for me if this sways.
Hey!
Cut it out!
Why're you dancing?
Why, you...
L-look, listen, just try to grab me
without making it sway!
Hey!
Funny.
You little-!
Just you wait...
This must be the "ocean"...
I wish I could've shown this to Grandpa.
This fish... is it the same one from back then?
No, it's not.
What?
Y-Yuu?!
Yuu?!
Yep.
You're huge.
By the way, this is the fish from back then.
We did eat it.
That fish was really yummy.
You're a fish, too.
You look yummy, too.
Do you not have a brain in there?
Well, I am a fish.
And really, Chi, if you've gotta get eaten,
wouldn't you rather it be by me?
Well, sure, but...
No, hold on, wait...
Wait!
Stop!
She's gonna eat me!
I can't eat any more...
I feel like I went through a bunch of weird places...
This water's really good.
The Sound of Rain
Chi.
What?
It's raining!
Not a time to celebrate.
I wish it'd started when we were in a place with a roof.
Somewhere we can wait out the rain...
Put the sheet over our stuff.
Okay.
We got pretty wet...
Ooh, found a nice stick.
Hasn't rained in a while, huh?
Yeah.
Sure is loud.
Sure am bored.
Yeah.
Sounds cool!
Sure is loud. I wonder why?
Stop all that banging.
It's probably 'cause it's hollow.
Hollow?
That means it's empty inside.
I see.
Like your head.
It's really loud if it's empty.
I s...
Ow, ow!
Ooh, sounds cool! Maybe it's empty inside, too?!
Ow!
It's got more inside than yours.
If you've got nothing to do, go save some water.
Okay.
Man, she's so quick to hit me.
Guess here works.
Lemme borrow your helmet.
Well, okay, but what do you need it for?
That sounds kinda nice.
Right?
Should we make some more?
Yeah, there's a ton of places it's dripping.
We can use this.
Look, I found a bunch of cans!
It's like a flood of sound.
Maybe this is what they call "music".
Music?
I heard it's when high and low sounds
have a rhythm and connect together.
Huh.
Maybe we overdid it a little.
Maybe, but...
The rain's...
Hey, Chi, was the world always like this?
Yeah...
Let's break a little longer.
Yeah.