Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
Sure is warm today.
It's no use.
Good weather, too.
This can't be repaired...
It's so peaceful.
It's hopeless.
Hopeless...
Yuu.
Stop sucking on that metal bit and come help me.
Ugh, don't wanna.
Let's get along with the feeling of hopelessness.
You sure are positive.
Well, if Yuu touched it,
she'd only end up making it even worse.
This isn't good.
If we can't get it fixed,
we won't be able to get anywhere,
let alone the highest level.
It's fine if we don't go anywhere anymore...
This really is hopeless!
Chi, look at that! Look!
Where?
Is that an "airplane"?
Hey, I'm telling you there's an airplane in the sky...
Yuu, look, there's a person!
Huh? A person?
Huh? In the sky? Where?
You're right. There's something in the air.
Look, a person!
I just told you that!
They fell over.
Yeah.
Are they dead?
No, definitely not.
Let's go look.
It works.
It flies really well.
Alright, it's stable...
You scared me!
Who are you?
This is Yuuri, I'm Chito.
And together, we're...
Umm...
when you said it works, were you talking about...
That.
So that airplane had something to do with you...
I made it.
You made it?!
I see, your Kettenkrad...
Let's see...
I could probably fix this.
Huh?
Really?
Probably.
Isn't that great, Chi? We're so lucky!
Y-yeah.
In exchange,
there's something I'd like you to help me with.
I feel very lucky, too...
...to run into someone at a time like this.
Hey, where are we going?
We're almost there.
Come a little more forward.
Yeah, stay right there.
Oh, right, I don't think we got your name yet.
My name?
It's Ishii.
It was supposedly an old air base.
It's got water and power,
and a lot of machine parts lying around.
I've lived here for a long time.
Lived here?
Do you have a bed with two levels?!
What does that even mean?
Darn.
Do you have a pantry?
No pantry, but there's a
ration production facility nearby.
Or was.
It doesn't work anymore.
Sure, there's water and power,
but most everything else doesn't work.
It's just a matter of time for this place.
Umm, by the way, that airplane that was flying before...
Was it okay to just leave it back there?
Yeah, it was just a prototype.
Prototype?
The real one's over here.
This is it.
I want you two to help me finish it.
In exchange, I'll repair your Kettenkrad.
Wow...
So once it's finished, what're you gonna do?
Once it's done, I'm going to get in it...
...and leave this city.
Takeoff
We got a bath! We got a shower!
Ishii's gotta be a good person if she's
letting us use her bath.
Yeah.
Kanazawa was a good person, too.
With his maps...
Sometimes people are good,
but that doesn't mean everyone out there is good.
But c'mon, they say humans are
creatures that help one another!
Big words from someone
who won't even help me with repairs.
Man, it really is nice...
It's always nice whenever we get a bath.
Yeah...
Ishii, thanks for the bath!
Good timing.
Hot, hot...
What is it?
A potato.
Potato?!
It looks like they were ground into
a powder to make rations.
Hot, hot!
So this is a potato...
You can eat them boiled.
It's good.
It's yummy!
They're small, but are very nutritious.
Eat up so you can help me out tomorrow.
You live here, Ishii?
Yes, that's right.
Hey, Ishii?
What?
Why'd you wanna make an airplane?
Hmm?
Most people wouldn't think about making one,
even if they had a lotta equipment.
Part of it was the equipment,
but the biggest reason was...
Hmm...
that's gotta be it.
What?
I had the documents.
Documents?
Documents? You mean...
The things you see before you now.
Before us?
The airplane blueprints.
They were scattered throughout the storehouses
in the base, so I gathered them together.
From the oldest versions humanity ever built...
to ones using technology
that we could never understand.
This base might have served as a repository
for the documentation of this technology.
This is truly the history of
airplane technology development.
I made that airplane using
all these designs as reference.
So that thing before is your own original design!
That's a little worrying.
Looks like it'll fall.
I had to patch it together with the materials
I had at hand. Nothing else I could do.
That, and I didn't have much time.
You mean with your rations?
Sure, with the rations,
but if I miss this warm period without snow or wind,
I might not have another chance to fly.
But... if you fail, then you'll die...
Why are you all scared, Chi?
Still...
True hopelessness is not having anywhere to go, right?
You'll just end up dying along with this city.
Let's get some sleep.
The next container over is open,
so go ahead and use it.
Hey, Chi, what's it like outside this town?
Dunno...
I've never even thought about it.
I don't even really know what this city is.
Maybe Ishii knows.
Maybe.
But maybe she was right when she said
we'd only die if we stayed here.
Ishii.
We found some plugs!
Oh, thanks.
Sure is big.
It's that big, but it can only fit one person?
That's because I'm focusing on
flight distance more than anything.
With an extra fuel tank, it should be able to go
more than two thousand kilometers.
Two thousand?!
Is that far?
Really far.
I wonder what the world looks like from the sky.
Did you want to ride, too?
I'm sorry it only fits one person.
I want to ride in it.
Nope, not at all.
Once we get the control system fixed up,
we'll work on the main wings.
Hopeless, hopeless...
And it's hopeless...
Hopeless, hopeless, hopeless!
Hopeless, hopeless!
It's going!
We were so close to dying...
You're good, you're good, you're good...
Working good, working good.
I'm so glad we were able to fix that.
Hey, Chito!
Can you pull over this way a bit more?
Okay!
Here's good?
Yeah, that's good.
You're good, you're good!
A little further!
Keep going, keep going!
Okay, stop!
Alright.
It's ready.
Alright, let's celebrate the airplane being finished!
Cheers!
This water tastes so good.
What does "cheers" mean again?
I think it's something people did
when they were celebrating something.
That's why...
you get two potatoes today.
Potatoes!
Potatoes, potatoes!
So good!
So good...
Are you sure you wanna give us two?
I can't take them all with me, after all.
Huh? Then I want more!
You really have no shame, Yuuri.
You think so?
Sorry.
But there should still be some more
in the production facility to the west.
Really?! Then we know where we're going next!
Yeah.
I'll draw you a map later.
Where we're going...
We never asked where you were going, Ishii.
You said you were leaving the city...
I'm not going to fly off in a random direction, of course.
Where are you headed?
Are you going to the highest level, then?
What's this?
A course map I found in the base.
It looks like they used to use airplanes
to fly back and forth from the next city over.
The next city over?!
On a sunny day when the air was clear,
I got a small glimpse of what lies on the far shore.
It must still be there now.
The next city over, huh...
I wonder what it's like.
Well, I'll know when I get there.
Say cheese.
Thanks for everything.
And thank you for all the food!
Ishii, you really are going, then?
Of course I am.
I've spent all this time
building it just for this moment
I'm so glad I met the two of you.
You've told us that a lotta times now.
It's not just because you could help me with the work.
The most important thing of all
was having someone watching this moment.
If someone is watching,
then I'm sure it will become history.
History...
Hey, Ishii, you might be...
...the last pilot in human history.
Maybe.
Alright, let's go.
This flight will be etched into the tail end of history.
Engine OK.
Rudder OK.
She did it!
Chi!
Look!
It was no use after all.
It was over so fast...
I spent so long working alone.
Working hard on this...
But, well, once you fail,
you feel so carefree.
She's smiling.
What? Why?
I dunno.
Maybe she's getting along with it now.
With the feeling of hopelessness.
What's that supposed to mean?
In any case, I'm glad Ishii's okay.
If she keeps falling like that,
she'll make it to the lowest level,
and she'll find a way to live again, right?
Who knows.
But if all goes well, I'm sure she will...
What're you writing?
Figured I'd put this down into my journal.
Write down about the airplane and stuff.
Writing down history?
I guess...
Alright, let's go.
To the west, right?
Yeah.
Hopeless, hopeless, hopeless.
Hopeless is hopeless, and hopeless is...
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey
Guess I'm gonna fall all the way to
the lowest level at this rate...