It's no use. I can't do it...
Hey, wait!
Yuu!
Jeez, what am I gonna do with you?
You're the one who said we have to go this way.
No...
well, yeah, but...
I can't do this...
Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
You sure are a scaredy-cat.
Yeah, but...
The only thing Ishii wrote on this map
to the ration production facility is...
"Keep going this way and you'll know".
Will we, though...
Yeah, but that means there's still food up ahead.
Labyrinth
So we've gotta go.
Ugh...
C'mon, get up.
I wish we could stay alive without having to eat...
That wouldn't really be living at all.
C'mon, let's go.
You'll be fine.
Okay.
Chi...
you okay?
That's it, that's what we should do here...
That one thing!
What thing?
You sure do like this sorta thing.
I don't really like it.
Is it so you take me with you if you fall?
No, I figured if I started falling,
you could fall the other way and save me.
Sounds pretty hard to pull off.
Seriously, your fear of heights
hasn't gotten any better, huh.
Why?
...Why?
I mean, we live somewhere real high up to begin with...
Think that's a little different than this...
Oh, are you hungry, Yuu?
Yeah, I am.
But you're always hungry.
No, I'm way hungrier than usual.
Oh, that's it!
You're just way more scared!
Yeah, that's close, I guess.
Hey, Chi, is this the right way to go?
Probably.
Let's go!
Chi!
One, two!
It's getting darker.
Oh no...
I forgot to bring the lantern!
Oh, no. Should we turn back for today?
No...
Wait, hold on...
Which way did we come from again?
Are we...
Lost...
But hey, aren't we always kinda lost?
I think this is a little different.
We're way more lost.
Yeah.
Nothing we can do, then.
Wanna sleep here for the night?
No freaking way!
If I roll over in my sleep,
you'll just have to roll the other way!
Sounds pretty hard to pull off...
Okay, then we've gotta keep going, huh?
Be really careful where you step.
Don't worry, it'll all be fine.
I feel like we're in even more danger
when you say we'll be fine.
I told you to watch your step!
Are you...
Chi's... shining...
Chi!
Whoa, whoa...
Chi, you okay?
Yuu!
Chi!
There's a path!
Huh?
There's a path... inside...
There was a path inside the pipe.
This must be what she meant by "you'll know"!
It's even got arrows.
It's way more of a path.
What was all that hard work for?
Was there even an entrance to the pipe?
We probably missed it...
Ishii must have gone through here to get there.
I see.
Chi.
Yeah?
Don't look down, just keep
moving forward one step at a time.
R-right...
Let's take a little break.
I had no idea this big pipe was here.
We couldn't have known looking in from the outside.
There's a lotta weird junk that's fallen in here.
Big junk.
They must've gotten washed in here.
Life would be so easy if we had
arrows like this all the time.
Aww, that'd be boring!
Boring?
Oh, it wouldn't be fun getting there
just by following signs.
Let's try getting there another way!
What?
Let's go explore!
We could go through that hole!
Nope.
What kind of person would ignore signs
that would help them get to their destination?
This girl right here!
Seriously, cut it out.
Sorry.
If we get way more lost now,
you'll get way more hungry.
Then we'll die.
I get it. Okay, let's go this way then.
Right?
Right.
Cooking
And we're down!
Where's the food at?
Dunno...
Oh, there it is.
A potato.
Wow, so this is how they grow!
It's a plant!
Yeah.
But I can't believe there's only one,
after coming all this way...
This is the last one left, huh.
Ishii did say there wasn't much left.
This is way too little...
That lady was a real airhead, huh.
That's why her wings broke apart.
Hey.
You're the last person who should be
saying that about Ishii.
In any case, we're gonna have to search
every corner of this facility...
Can we go further down from here?
Whee!
Whoa, whoa...
What kind of machines are these, do you think?
It's a food production facility, so they're
probably machines that produce food.
By food, you mean something different
from those potatoes?
Yeah...
What's this?
Hey, Yuu! Make it stop!
Must be this one.
Yuu!
So it still works.
Don't just go touching weird stuff!
You jush had ta wun shidewaysh.
What was that?!
Sideways.
POWDER
Sorry, sorry.
Be careful, okay?
But seriously, what was that machine for?
There's something over here, Chi.
What?
You climbed up again?
That's dangerous, you know.
Whoa, whoa...
There's some kinda powder.
Powder?
Yuu?
It's kinda sweet.
Sweet?
It tastes like those things.
The potatoes.
You're right.
That means...
So this... turned into this.
Through that machine?
You were real close to getting
turned into powder, too!
Sorry.
But that means we can eat this!
We ate the potatoes after boiling them...
What should we do to the powder?
Can we bake it?
Bake it, huh...
Does this work, too?
It turned on.
Looks like it's a baking machine.
Guess they really did bake it.
Hey, hey, Chi!
What does this say?
SUGAR
"Sugar".
Sugar. I found it on the floor over there.
It's sweet.
Yeah, it is...
Sugar...
I feel like I've seen that somewhere before.
Hey, I just remembered something.
She said the potatoes were used to make rations, right?
You're really good at remembering stuff about food.
Oh, that's it!
Look.
"Sugar" is listed in the ingredients for the rations.
There's something else called "salt".
Yes, there was another bag of that, too!
Really?
That means if we have...
Potatoes, sugar, and salt,
we might be able to make rations!
Seriously?! That's awesome!
Okay.
A long time ago, Grandpa used to
make bread for us, right?
That bread was really good.
POWDER
You're really good at remembering stuff about food.
That was the last bread we had...
Maybe we just need to do it like we did back then.
Okay.
Mix together the powder, sugar, and salt...
Then keep adding water,
and knead.
Knead.
It's pretty exhausting...
But the texture's kinda changed.
You're right.
It's getting really doughy!
Doughy...
Here we go!
One, two!
Here we go! Here we go!
One, two! One two!
Stretch it out...
and cut it!
Now we just have to bake it.
Hot...
We gotta watch the heat.
Are they done yet?
They've got a while.
Are they good now?
Nope, not yet.
Should be soon...
Nope.
Pleeeease?
Just...
Hey!
Nope.
Are they done?
They're done!
Smells good.
Think we baked them a little too long.
It's like, sparkling!
Maybe because we put the leftover sugar on top.
Okay!
It's good.
We still have a lot of raw dough left over.
We should bake it.
Sure, but it'll keep for like a year, right?
No way, though it'd be sweet if
your naïve idea was true.
Sweet, huh...
This is super sweet.
Because we put a lot of sugar into it.
Hey.
Sweetness is happiness, huh?
Yeah...
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey
We made a whole lot!
Why's it shaped like that?
This?
It's shaped like that thing.
The fish?
Yeah, that.
This is Grandpa,
this is Kanazawa,
and Ishii...
and that's me,
and you!