Ooh, it opened.
What is this?
What?
Do I turn this?
Doesn't work.
I wonder what it was for.
Dunno.
What is this place, anyway?
Dunno...
Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
Memories
Doesn't look like the kind of place people would live...
Doesn't look like any kind of factory, either.
It's just a bunch of black slabs.
What a weird place.
But that stuff is the weirdest thing here.
You mean this device?
No, not that...
Wait, you brought it with you?
I figured we could use it for something.
We're not gonna use it for anything, jeez...
Huh.
I mean the drawers on the side of the walls.
Most are sealed up tight and inaccessible...
Then there are ones that are empty...
were they empty to start with
or did someone take what was inside?
Whoa, whoa...
Then...
Even when there's something inside, it's not much.
Yeah, huh. All we've found so far is...
...the weird device just now,
an empty shell, a scrap of cloth...
...and a button.
That's all, it looks like.
You brought everything with you?
I figured we could use them for something.
We're not gonna use them for anything, jeez...
Huh.
I really thought we could use them
for something or other.
What're we gonna use a scrap of cloth for?
All these useless, seemingly worthless things
are stored away as if they're important...
I wonder why...
I remember that.
A mysterious statue!
Chi, gimme the camera, the camera!
It's been so long!
You sure like those.
They're shaped real nice,
and they're kinda relaxing to look at!
Cameras are so great.
You'll never forget the things you took pictures of.
Thank Kanazawa for it.
Who was Kanazawa again?
Hey. He was the guy who gave us the camera.
Oh, I remember now.
I would've forgotten about him without the camera.
Thanks, camera.
Normally you wouldn't forget
that sorta thing that easily.
I hope he's doing well...
It's alright.
As long as we have this camera,
we'll never forget him.
Stop talking about him as if he's dead.
But no matter if he's dead or alive,
we're probably not gonna run into him again, huh...
Or Ishii, either.
Yeah, it'd be difficult...
Then one day we'll probably forget about them.
Is that what this is...
Look, right here.
We didn't see it because it was so small,
but every drawer has a name written on it.
I bet that's the person who owned what was inside.
So the stuff inside was forgotten by those people?
I don't think they were forgotten.
They put them in here so they wouldn't be forgotten.
These are graves.
Graves...
I bet they left behind these names
and the things they owned
so someone would see it and remember them.
I see.
But now there isn't anyone
passing through like we are,
and everyone in the world is gone...
so who would remember them?
Well look, they've got this guy.
Is that what that statue's here for?
It's snowing harder, huh.
It's gonna get colder again...
We've gotta put them back.
Put what back?
The stuff you took with you, Yuu.
Aww, why?
They'll lose all their meaning if they leave this place.
Do we know where they all go...?
Huh. Does this go here again?
Well, they're all the same in the end.
No!
Spiral
That scared me...
An old beam fell down...
Is this scaffolding gonna hold up...?
It'll be fine, it'll be fine.
You always say it's gonna be fine, Yuu.
There might be danger lurking ahead.
Everything seems so dangerous that I actually
start thinking that everything'll be fine.
I have no idea what that means.
The elevator on the outside
of the tower was broken down...
But it's a good thing this path was here too.
This tower's way thinner than
the last one we came up, huh.
It might be a different type of tower.
I like going up this way better than riding an elevator.
I'm so done with dangling by a rope like that.
But...
we haven't even made it to the higher level yet.
Yeah...
Around, and around...
Are we really going up, or are we going down?
Um, we're going up.
When we're going around and
around the same location,
it really makes you miss our usual, unchanging days.
So let's hurry and get to the top
so we can go back to those usual days.
Yeah, but the more we move,
the more danger we'll be in.
You sure are quick to turn into a coward
when you're up high, Chi.
Shut up!
How can you live if you're afraid of dying?!
Sounds like a good line.
But it's just stupid.
How long does this path go on for...?
Chi?
My head's starting to spin, too...
A spinning spiral...
My head's spinning...
Chi!
Chi, stop! Stop!
The path...
No, look there.
That the exit?
It's another way around.
Someone must've made it.
Why'd they make it on the outside?!
Doesn't look like it'd be a problem
for people to use, but...
It's pretty heavy...
That's why I hate going up...
Chi, how can you live if-
I got it, you don't have to say it again.
Let's go.
Chi!
Chi, hit the accelerator!
Never thought I'd be this happy
to see this path again...
There's the entrance to the next level!
We made it...
Now we're on the next level up.
We're back to our usual flat path.
Though it sure is dark...
We sleep, wake up, eat, and move...
then sleep again.
When you think about it,
our lives go around and around, too.
That means life is just a spiral!
Where will we end up when we
reach the end of the spiral?
Moonlight
Nights where you can see the Moon
really get you pumped up, huh?
There's nothing here we can use...
It gets you pumped up, huh?
Are you listening to me?
No, I'm not.
You're always in such a bad mood, Chi.
I'm not really in a bad mood, though...
Take this seriously and look for stuff, Yuu.
Ooh, found a nice stick!
For some reason, I feel a stranger power in me...
This must be the Moon's magic power!
Magic power, huh...
I thought there'd be something here
since there were lots of houses still standing, but...
There's nothing here.
This place is falling apart...
So bright!
The moonlight's shining in.
Moonlight power at 100%!
Moonlight!
Jeez, could you calm down...
Moonlight! Moonlight!
Ow.
Sorry, sorry.
Stop picking up sticks.
Glass containers.
Are they empty?
Some have stuff inside.
This one's got stuff inside, too.
There's three altogether.
What's inside them?
Water?
What's written here?
It says...
"B... Beeu", I think.
Well?
The top's on real tight, but...
Opened it.
Wow, it's golden water.
It's kinda sparkly.
Hey, don't we have a glass container with us?
I think we do.
Wow!
It looks almost like the moonlight's melting into it!
What a strange smell.
Okay, then.
How is it?
It's kinda bitter... but kinda sweet...
It's good!
Okay.
It's so fizzy and weird!
Okay, let's open another!
Yuu, think first...
Yuu!
What?!
Chi?
Chi's gone crazy.
Your face is really stretchy, Yuu.
So this is the power of the Moon...
Maybe the moonlight really did melt into that water!
The light of the Moon!
Hey, Yuu.
What?
One day, let's go really really high up...
...and go to the Moon.
Sounds good. The Moon, huh?
Wonder what it's like up there...
Hey, Chi! Don't eat my hair!
It's yummy!
My head hurts...
You okay?