It's so dark.
Iiit's soooo daaaark.
Shut it.
I feel like we've had a conversation like this before.
This place is a lot brighter
than it was back there, though.
It sounds like things are moving,
so maybe this facility's still alive.
Alive...
Girls' Last Tour
Hey, what does "alive" mean?
Well, I meant the machinery is still functioning.
I didn't mean it was alive as a life-form.
Huh.
So what's a "life-form"?
A life-form means a living being.
What's that?
Life...
Chi?
B-be quiet...
So what do you think that was?
That... that really big thing.
I don't have the words to describe it.
Is that a living being?
No, I don't think it's a living being.
No matter how you look at it, it was a machine.
And machines don't breathe or have consciousness.
They're just like this thing we're riding in.
Machines don't move or think on their own.
But... I feel like that thing just now
was moving all on its own...
Someone might be operating it.
Okay then, what if that machine walked toward us
all on its own and said "hello", what'd you do?
No machine would do that.
Besides, this machine debate is pointless,
since they say there are no living beings
other than humans on Earth.
Huh.
There are no other living beings, huh...
Huh?
There's one.
A fish!
It's alive.
They exist.
Chi!
Hello.
Life
Aww, come on!
You cannot.
I am the caretaker of this fish.
Non-staff may not tamper with it.
So it really is a fish.
You cannot eat it.
Wait, a machine is talking to us.
What exactly are you?
I am the automated apparatus
that manages this sector.
You do not need to worry. I will not harm you.
Alright! Then let's go eat that fish!
C'mon, Yuu...
Please stop.
I have the ability to call guard apparatuses
in the event of an aggressive non-employee.
But...
But?
But all communication with them has ceased.
Then you can't.
Come on.
By guard apparatuses, maybe he means
the thing we saw on the way here.
The big thing?
No. That is the construction apparatus
that maintains this sector.
The only apparatuses still functioning
in this area are him and myself.
I can't believe people long ago
could make these kinds of machines...
How did they make them?
We're not gonna eat the fish.
Could you tell us more about
these machines and this place?
Of course. I will guide you.
I don't care about talking with it, I wanna eat!
Shut up.
No, fishie!
It's like we're actually underwater.
We are directly below the largest aquarium tank.
Aw, man! I wanna soak in a water tank this big.
Would you like to?
Wait, can I?
You may enter any unused aquarium tank.
There are one hundred and two tanks in this facility,
but only twelve are still in service,
and only one is in use.
By in use, you mean that one before?
Yes.
So there aren't any fish in the other tanks?
No, there are not.
This place was a fish farming facility
for the mass production of food fish.
Mass production!
However, that fish is the only one remaining.
So...
You cannot eat it.
You may use this tank as you please.
I can't breathe...
I'm floating!
You okay?
So tired.
Hey, I'm tired, so let's go eat that fish.
You cannot.
That thing says you can't.
This feels good.
Hey, Yuu.
Do you think the fish we saw before
came from this place?
The fish when we did laundry.
Oh, that yummy fish.
Hey, c'mon, don't do laundry here!
Huh?
You'll get the water all dirty!
Be careful, I'm swimming here!
No, you're gonna help too.
I don't wanna!
Environmental pollution.
The Earth was once one large living being,
but humans chose to separate themselves
from its processes.
Humans built cities to provide
the environment for their existence...
...as an alternative to the cycles
of water, air, and energy.
Our job is to maintain the infrastructure in the
foundation of the city to the best of our ability.
Even though humans aren't around anymore?
That does not matter to us.
We simply continue to maintain it.
C'mon, Chi, get in!
It's pretty warm!
How is she able to swim so freely?
She possesses a high level of adaptability.
Guess I'll give it a try, too.
Okay...
Why're you in your underwear? Just get in naked.
Well, someone's here.
It's a machine.
Yeah, but...
My legs...
my legs aren't touching anything!
C'mon, Chi!
Wait a sec!
What am I supposed to do?!
You'll float if you kick your legs!
Hey, don't let go of my hand!
You can do it!
If you take a deep breath and relax, you will float.
Wha?!
Hey!
Huh?
The sea...
Fish...
You okay?
The Earth was once one large living being, but...
Then... what is it now?
Wow.
This species does not normally jump out of the water,
but this fish exhibits a mutation.
Mutation?
A mistake in the transmission of orders. A bug.
It is the driving force behind evolution.
The stuff it's saying is really complicated...
I wanna roast it.
Seriously, cut it out.
Hey, can I do that, too?
Feed the fish? Of course.
Really?
Awesome!
There are five pellets left for today.
Okay!
Maybe we can be friends after all!
Predators can't be friends with their prey.
I wanna take you with me on our journey.
You're drooling, too.
Today was exhausting...
If you'd like to sleep,
I recommend sleeping below those pipes.
There is hot water flowing through them.
It's so warm!
I was thinking, you seem like you're really alive,
even though you're just a machine.
Perhaps because we were equipped with
the ability to evoke empathy
in order to communicate with humans.
What's "empathy"?
It means that when you are happy, I am happy.
I see.
Sure is warm.
Yeah.
What's that sound?
Ow, ow...
Hey, Yuu!
Jeez, Chi, you said it'd be yummy if we roasted it...
Wake up!
Hey, Yuu!
It's the big machine!
Why is it here?
It appears he has begun dismantling this facility.
Why?
I don't know.
Sometimes, unnecessary facilities
must be dismantled to preserve materials.
I will ask him.
You can talk to it?
Maybe they're arguing.
Well? What'd it say?
He said he will be dismantling this place.
I proposed that he stop, but he would not listen.
Some help you are!
Hey.
That means the fish is gonna...!
Most of the sectors in this area
were on the disassembly list.
A bug lethal to the city must have occurred.
A bug... is that the driving force behind evolution, too?
If you would call breaking down something
to build something new evolution.
Hey, Chi.
Huh?
Let's save that fish!
But what should we do?
I cannot save it.
But...
But?
You may be able to.
Weren't you gonna eat it?
No, I dunno why, but...
I wanna save that fish.
Maybe that's "empathy."
I see.
Even half this amount should be enough.
If you attach these explosives to his body,
you will destroy his inner mechanisms and stop him.
Can I get on his back if I go on those paths up top?
You can climb up to them from the edge of the room.
Is it safe?
Alright, I'll be back.
You will not be benefited in any way by saving that fish.
Well, honestly, I don't understand
what goes through her head...
Hey, does destroying that
big machine mean we're killing it?
It depends on your definition of "life".
Life... we're alive.
That fish is alive.
The big machine can't talk, but...
But I think it can feel empathy.
Probably because it's alive.
Okay!
A long time ago, people and machine
and the city were alive, living in a cycle...
Yuu! If you don't hurry,
the fish tank's gonna be done for!
Just a bit further...
Okay!
Sorry, big guy.
Chi!
The fish and I will live a bit longer now.
Though we will all die one day.
People, machine, fish, and city are alive...
But they will all come to an end one day.
Hey, Chi.
Maybe "life" means something that has an end?
Yeah.
We saved the fish, but a lot got destroyed, too.
Can they fix it again?
Then it can do that thing! Uh...
Evolution?
Yeah, that.
That is impossible.
The most I can do with my ability
is stop the water from leaking.
So you're too useless to do
anything more than "maintain".
Hey.
There may be limits to evolution as well.
The city stopped evolving
after it suffered large-scale destruction.
The people on this level
eventually disappeared as well.
If there's not reconstruction after destruction,
then that's where it ends, huh.
Yes.
Well, we're gonna go,
but I hope you two live long lives.
I think we will. Take care, you two.
Empathy.