Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
Hey, hey, Chi, look!
Wow. Wonder what those facilities are for.
Train
Sure am bored...
Yup, I’m bored.
Hey, let's go towards the front.
Okay.
I just noticed something awesome.
What?
We're moving in a train that's moving.
So?
So basically, we're moving faster than we usually do!
No, we're not.
Huh?
Why?
I can't explain it myself...
Oh, but on top of all that,
Us
Train
we're moving in addition to the Earth's rotation, so...
Us
Train
Earth
It might be even faster than that.
Rotation?
Rotation means the Earth is spinning.
1 Day
Though it might be spinning the other way
How fast does it spin?
I don't know the actual number,
but fast enough for the whole Earth
to spin around once a day.
Seriously? That's super fast.
Oh, but wait, does that mean every day,
we travel one Earth circumference?
You could say that, yeah.
That's so crazy.
You're the crazy one here.
We run into these guys sometimes now...
But nope, they don't work.
It's just a corpse of a machine.
It makes you remember the graves we saw before.
This train's black, kind of like those boxes.
A moving grave...
Just where is it headed?
Hey, look at this. I found a weird device.
Is that a clock?
A clock?
Those things that tell time, right?
I think the needle goes around twice
every time the Earth goes around once.
It's faster than the Earth!
Time doesn't have a speed...
Wait, does it, though?
In any case, the Earth turns, and time passes.
C'mon, let's go. Get on already.
Hey, wait a sec!
There's no reason for us to hurry!
We're on a moving train!
That is true.
There's no reason for us to hurry
when we're on the Earth that's moving, either.
No, that's different.
I heard that people long ago
all carried clocks with them.
Huh.
Why?
Because it was convenient.
They could use it as a reference
to tell when they had to do certain things.
Forget convenient, it sounds like a hassle.
I don't like rushing.
Yeah, but Yuu, we're...
Are we there?
Okay, let's go.
No, wait a sec.
It looks like this isn't the end.
Those things that look like rations are all in a line.
I think the one that's lit up is our current location.
There's still so many. Are we not getting off?
Back to what we were saying about time...
Our time is constrained by our food.
Huh.
You sure aren't concerned.
Okay, as long as we've got food,
let's keep pressing forward!
That's right. Go as far as we can.
Wavelength
We rode the train for a pretty long time.
I feel like that train took us pretty far...
Yeah. I feel like we slept a ton.
Yuu, you asleep?
No.
What's up?
I think I hear something.
What do you think you hear?
I thought I heard a noise coming from this thing.
The weird device I picked up from the graves.
Oh, that.
Wait, I told you to put it back!
Nah, I thought we could use it.
It belongs to someone who died. That's bad karma.
But isn't there that saying,
"Dead men fell no whales?"
It's "tell no tales."
I'm not afraid of them if they're empty-handed.
They're scary even if they're empty-handed.
So what sound did you hear?
It was a weird sound.
It sounded like someone's voice, but a little different.
It had that thing like the rain... like ahh, ahh.
Rhythm?
Yeah, it had rhythm!
Like this!
Like that.
That might be what's called "singing".
Singing?
Music made with a person's voice.
You do it sometimes, too.
It's dark here.
It's so dark.
Like that?
Yeah. That's singing.
Singing...
that's singing.
I see.
Lemme see that device for a second.
Okay.
I think it's a device that picks up
on radio waves or something...
I felt kinda sad.
Is music something that makes you feel sad?
I dunno,
but listening to it made me feel kinda sad.
Huh.
But you know, when we listened to
the rain music, I felt a little happy.
Yeah.
Feeling sad, feeling happy...
Maybe music has that kind of power.
Because it has rhythm?
Rhythm, huh...
I think even sound waves have rhythm in their waves...
What about those radio waves you mentioned?
I don't know a lot about radio waves,
but those are some kind of wave, too.
I think light is a kind of wave, too.
Huh. So maybe we'll feel happy looking at light.
Like feeling happy when you
look at the lights of the city?
I dunno...
Man, I wanna see the sunlight again, though.
Yeah.
We've been in this infrastructure
ever since coming to this level.
And we don't know how far we traveled in that train.
For now, we gotta get up to the surface.
How?
Well, we go up.
Up, huh.
Oh, what's that, Chi?
That's a steep slope...
Is this the button?
Oooh, it worked!
Yeah, but...
Isn't it moving kinda fast?
Yuu, do you know how to stop this?
Oh.
What?!
That music...
I think we're close to the surface.
Close?
We can see it already.
Seriously? Man, this is fast!
Yuu, the switch, the switch!
Which one is it?
I dunno.
Chi, you okay?
Yeah...
You're right. It's sad music.
Look, Chi.
It's the sunset.
It's red.
This red light feels sad for some reason.
Is it because of the music, or...
I bet the red sunset has a sad rhythm to it.
The rhythm of the light, huh...
The sunset is making my eyes sting.
Is it that sad?
No, it hurts. I scratched them.
Oh.
What a nice day.
Nice music for a nice view.
It's not playing music.
The weather's...
well, don't know about the weather, but...
Hey, stop moving.
Sure is a big hole.
Wonder how it got there.
Think that's it.
The ends of our hair were getting pretty frizzy,
but now they're all tidied up on both of us.
Maybe I took off too much.
It hasn't changed at all.
Cheese.
Hey, let's go down in the hole.
Sure. I can hear water down there, anyway.
Can we get down there?
Capture
There are a lot of weapons lying around here...
I guess there was a fierce battle here or something.
Maybe the battle made this hole.
Who knows.
Judging from the weapons set up
around the inside of the hole...
I think it was made a lot longer ago.
A lot longer ago?
Yeah. This big hole was made
in a battle a long, long time ago...
And then there was another battle in the town
that was built around it... something like that.
That sure is complicated.
So cold!
What're you doing?
It's cold.
Let's go eat there.
Yay!
I felt like we had a lot of the ones we baked,
but a lot are gone now.
It feels good to cut our hair,
but losing these makes you feel kinda sad...
Yummy.
I wish there were fish in that puddle...
Fish, huh...
Man, I really wanted to eat that fish in the aquarium...
You literally said you wanted to save it,
but after all that, you just want to eat it.
That was then, this is different.
I thought you empathized with it.
You think food could come out of these holes?
Instead of just water?
That wouldn't happen.
What?
This weird living thing just...
Living thing?
It's inside! It's inside here!
A living thing? You mean like a fish?
No, it's something way different!
Chi, give it a little whack!
Huh? You want me to... what?
Like this?
Yuu!
You okay, Yuu?
Think I'm okay.
What is it? Definitely doesn't look like it's a fish...
I think I saw something in a book.
Think it's a "cat"?
A cat!
Okay, let's eat it!
Hold on a sec!
Think.
Held in a sec.
Hey, did you hear a voice from that device?
Huh? A voice?
Ce?
Vo?
Is this thing actually talking?
You mean the cat?
I dunno if it's really a cat, but...
Hey, cat! Are you a cat?!
Cu?
Cut.
It says it's a "cut".
Isn't it just repeating what we're saying?
It's a cut.
What should we do?
Roast it?
Hold on.
Let's leave it behind.
Aww, why?
We can't eat something that can say words.
Huh. This that "empathy" thing again?
Yeah, I guess.
Let's go.
Doesn't look like there's anything else here, anyway.
Bye.
Hey.
It's kinda following us.
Huh? So we're gonna eat it?
No.
I dunno how to put it.
We're always running out of stuff,
so maybe it'd be nice to try adding something instead.
Well, why not? I think it wants to follow us, anyway.
Whoa.
Sure, but can you gonna carry it, Yuu?
I'm kinda scared of it...
Aww, it's so cute, though.
It's so soft!
Don't mess with it too much.
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey
Like that?
You sure are bad at this, Chi.