Wonder if it can eat it.
Ooh, it ate it!
Huh? What'd it eat?
A bullet.
A bullet?!
Maybe today we should turn back
Maybe tomorrow we can go even further
Girls' Last Tour
Creaking
I want to find the many happy things far away
Hope sparkling with light, moving, moving
Unending talk continues on forever
Goodbye loneliness, moving, moving
Just like solving a difficult puzzle
I'm sure we'll keep learning the things we want to learn
So with a 1, 2, 3 start walking
Today and tomorrow and yesterday are all the same
In the opposite direction the world is turning
That's right, with a 1, 2, 3 start dancing
I want to forget today and tomorrow and yesterday
So with a 1, 2, 3 start moving
I'm sure that's the a-a-a-a-answer
There's no way it can eat something like that.
Gulp.
Ooh, it swallowed it.
Huh?
Now you say "yummy".
Yummy.
Seriously?
It's yummy, so I want to eat more.
Hear what it said?
It's learned a lot of words.
'Cause I'm teaching it.
Who am I?
Yuu.
Who's that?
Chito.
What's this?
Bullet.
There are different bullets, though. That's a 6.5.
Six point five.
This is a 12.7,
and this is a 20.
Don't pick up bullets that are that big, jeez.
I want to eat the twenty.
Ooh, that'll be a challenge!
Are you up to it?
Hey, now...
Still can't believe it can actually eat bullets.
Hard.
You can do it!
Maybe the gunpowder inside is giving it energy.
What's up? You interested in those tanks?
No...
I knew it!
Culture
It's a book!
What's it about?
I can't read this...
The letters are from an old, far-off place.
From a different culture.
Maybe grandpa could've read it...
Let's take it with us anyway.
Whaa?! But you can't even read it!
It's still important.
After you told me not to grab anything unimportant.
You're grabbing stuff, too.
You don't understand how valuable books are, Yuu!
Things I can't eat don't have value, nom, nom.
It's saying things I'd expect you to say, Yuu.
Nom, nom.
And what are you holding, Yuu?
A bullet.
Yeah, I can see that.
I was gonna feed it to the cut.
It definitely can't eat that. Get rid of it.
Gulp!
Ooh, it ate the 20 millimeter!
Seriously?!
Whoa, it got super heavy!
Don't mess with it so much.
Chi, gimme the camera!
Jeez...
Is being able to eat bullets a cultural difference?
That's less culture and more ecology.
Cultural differences are like the differences between
groups of humans, like alphabets or language.
Apparently, some wars were caused by culture.
I wonder why.
Maybe because things we don't understand
are scary... or something?
But you like to learn things you don't know, Chi.
Like, you like reading books.
That's why I don't do what you do and get close to things
I don't understand that seem dangerous.
But I mean, everything around us
is stuff we don't really understand.
Well, that is true.
Look, another thing we don't really understand.
It's moving little by little.
The wind, huh...
It's so cool!
Whee!
Don't break it.
Not after it's survived this long.
It is pretty cool.
You said it was cool!
Ow.
Another song we don't really understand.
I like this song.
So you have likes and dislikes, cut.
I can hear it from over there.
You know where?
I know. Over there.
Let's try going that way.
Yeah. Let's go see something
we don't really understand.
Alright, "cool" has beaten out "scary"!
It's not about what beats what.
But maybe it was actually people like Yuu
who created culture.
So...
about helmets.
What?
These helmets we're wearing.
Why are we always wearing them again?
Do we even need them?
I think they were originally to protect us from gunfire.
But nobody's shooting at us.
Yeah, well.
It's easy to climb you when you're wearing them.
Cut it out, you're heavy.
But hey, something could fall down on us.
Nah, nothing'll hit us unless we're really unlucky.
C'mere.
You don't know. There's always a chance that...
Whoa, something really did fall down!
You sure are unlucky, Chi!
Destruction
Chi, back up, back up!
I know, jeez!
Cough, cough.
Didn't think something this big
would come falling down.
We really would've been in a real bad spot
if we weren't wearing helmets.
We would've died either way.
This thing looks like those other ones.
Which ones?
The human-shaped ones that were all lined up in that
dark place we went through after we got off the train.
Oh, those.
Man, it's huge.
Can we get inside?
Maybe...
Cut!
H-hey!
Dark in here.
Wow...
Does it work?
What's this?
What was that just now?
Dunno.
Let's try pushing a different one.
Wha?!
Hey, stop it!
Awww, jeez...
Jeez...
Huh?
Fire!
Ow, ow, ow...
Jeez, Chi.
What incredible power.
I didn't know weapons like this existed...
It's so powerful!
This isn't funny!
Sorry.
So hot!
Fighting with a weapon like this
would turn stuff to a sea of fire in an instant.
You can't even compare our guns
to what this thing can do.
Did the people long ago build this, too?
Is all the destruction in the city because of
ridiculously powerful weapons like this?
Hey, it's this thing's fault!
You won't get away with this!
Take this, and this!
No, it's not the weapon's fault.
It's the person who used it.
A human pilots it, after all.
Really?
You're the worst, human!
I can't believe you've done this to the city!
You did it.
You were the one who destroyed it all.
Is that so...
Damn you, me!
I can't believe you've done this to the city!
You sure aren't hard on yourself.
Oh, cut!
Humans are scary.
There, there.
Guess we'll sleep here for today.
While watching the fire?
Seems pretty dangerous to stray too far out.
So in the end, it's a good idea to keep our helmets on.
Why?
'Cause bullets or beams might come flying at us.
Like I said, we'd die either way.
Yeah, but...
Is this rain?
We're beneath the city, so it's not rain.
No, it couldn't be.
Oh?
Huh? Is that it?
The main one's full but the spare's
about seventy percent full.
Well, guess that's alright.
Lick, lick.
Is fuel yummy?
Yummy.
The cut's so lucky. It's got food all over the place.
I'm thankful.
I mean, if push comes to shove for me...
You're thinking about eating that thing again, right?
Am not!
I don't think it's white, squishy, and yummy-looking...
It'll definitely taste like gunpowder and fuel.
Gunpowder might be yummy.
Fine then, start eating gunpowder.
The Past
Wind Power Plant
You're not gonna start saying
you wanna eat me anytime soon, right?
Don't act like you just got an idea.
That's that one thing, right? The "food chain".
A food chain with just you two is way too tough.
In that case, who'd be on top?
A forest.
What's that?
I thought this looked like a picture
I saw in a book a while back.
There were lots of plants growing like this.
A forest, huh...
I bet there were a lot of animals in it,
and there was a food chain, too.
Huh.
So how did things end up like this?
There's only machines.
Dunno.
Maybe they changed over a long period of time.
We don't know anything about the past.
All we've got is what's in books.
Oh, but you know,
even if we don't know about the past,
we can know about the future.
With enough time.
The future...
Yeah.
If we survive... right?
Oh, right, we can't know if we're dead!
We don't know much about stuff too far ahead...
Our lives are too short to learn a lot of things.
What's up?
Hey, cut, did the signal come from that direction?
Yes. That direction.
So does that mean it's coming from over there?
Probably.
Hey, what do you think this is?
Things that are big and look tough are usually...
A weapon?
It won't open?
Nope.
I know.
Chi, it's making noise.
Yeah.
SILENT
Do Not Enter
It's been running this whole time?
From way in the past?
It's not over till it's over
Where is this place I just woke up?
What's going to start now?
Before I realized it I'm getting ready to travel with you
Let's go to a paradise sparkling in black and white (let's go)
Let's make, let's make
C'mon, let's make a world for you and me
Let's start, let's start
What should we start with? (huh?!)
Let's dance, let's dance
Let's be happy and dance! (yay, yay!)
Our last trip is beginning (beginning)
The world made up of just the two of us
Is still spinning today (around and around)
Today and tomorrow and the day after that
Can I stay by your side?
Please
Not over yet, not over yet... (Travel)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Journey)
Not over yet, not over yet... (One more time!)
Not over yet, not over yet... (Yes!)
Journey