Girls' Last Tour
Weird machinery aside, this place is pretty clean.
'Cause it's been closed up this whole time.
I thought we might be able to find out more
about the past in a place like this, but...
Stuff from the past... like what?
Like how people in the past lived their lives...
Or what they wore, or how they spoke...
Why do you wanna know that stuff?
I dunno.
Oh hey, the cut's not here.
Oh, it goes off sometimes, huh.
Maybe it's eating some more bullets or something.
Are you worried about it?
Sometimes we run into someone
and become a group of three, right?
You mean like Ishii and Kanazawa?
Same with the cut, but...
I was just thinking it feels a little different than usual.
Like, lively, or something.
Are you lonely with it being just us?
...do you feel lonely, Chi?
Well... I guess a little, but...
Ow!
Oooh, the stuff inside feels just like... could it be?
Non-Perishable Chocolate
High Calorie
Ow, ow, ow...
Sniff sniff...
That's a familiar smell.
Huh?
Here.
Is it okay to eat? It's kinda dark-colored...
Edible things...
...can be eaten.
It's!
It's?
It's good...
It's...
This tastes like that one thing.
The chocolate flavor. It's so sweet.
Oh, you're right...
You sure do have a good memory
when it comes to food.
Maybe this is chocolate.
Nah, it's gotta be chocolate-flavored something.
...yeah, huh.
Non-Perishable Chocolate
High Calorie
But in a way, that's also
"something from the past", I guess.
What is?
Flavors are information, in a way.
Though you can't write them down.
Say chee...
CONNECTING
Huh?
What's up?
Some words came up on the camera.
It can connect.
Oh, cut...
What do you mean?
CONNECTING
SYNCING
Chi, those are the pictures we took!
It's displaying the pictures that were inside the camera...
...in the air?
I can't believe they could do this...
Oh, look, man, that takes me back!
It wasn't that far away that you'd be taken back.
What're these?
These pictures...
Those aren't ones that we took.
Oh, look.
It's the map guy.
Kanazawa.
...and who's that girl next to him?
Dunno...
I guess Kanazawa took these pictures over here.
He was alone when we met him...
There are lots of folders.
Folders?
Let's see them all!
I can open all of them.
Hey, wait...
Wow! There are so many people...
These... were all inside the camera?
Yes.
Uhh, so...
It moved! And talked!
A-are these what they called "videos"?
This is the 12th Report of the
Machine Evolution Research Society.
...is it recording?
It's going, it's going!
Umm, today's sample is this small machine.
We have named it No. 17 2nd-Class.
This machine can inject certain programs
into manufacturing equipment,
forcing the equipment to produce more of itself.
They looks like they're around our age...
One would scarcely consider that this difficult process
would be born from variation and selection…
Yeah.
Hey, wait a sec...
It's totally okay to call that evolution!
Saying it's a human design is way too self-serving!
Huh... was that it?
That's kinda important!
Hey.
I think I've started to get why you
wanna know more about the past.
Um... I'm hungry.
Now?!
It's been just the two of us for a long time, but...
Once you find out that people used to live like this...
Look, Midori, it's your Papa!
She says she doesn't like you, Papa.
The hell is wrong with you!
How dare you speak to me like that!
You bastard!
Stop it, I said!
C'mere, Bochi!
Japan formally declared war on
the neighboring states...
Okay, we'll put out another report
once we reconcile our opinions.
I never said that!
Large-scale air raids...
C'mon, it's all your fault, Papa!
Our military has secured a great victory,
with the neighboring state's casualties
numbering over fifty million...
So, we bought French fries!
Oh my god...
You sure love to eat.
Warning: Electromagnetic bombs
have been deployed.
All electronic devices have lost functionality...
Miki comes in first!
Happy birthday to you...
The Bunny and
the Bear's Adventure
Happy birth...
All telecommunications between every city
and every layer have been lost...
Father in heaven, we pray you share endless joy
with the brethren you have called to your side...
I kinda feel a little less lonely.
Yeah.
You're probably the only one who'll be able to
get out through the pipe storehouse.
Get on.
The two of you should be able to live
a long time with just a little food.
What about you, Grandpa?
Go, hurry.
The cut's gone again.
I wonder what kind of being that thing is.
It can open doors, and use machines, too.
And it uses the receiver to talk.
Well, whatever.
Oh, there you are!
Hey, where were...
Aren't you bigger than before?
Big...
Wait, cut?!
Yuu!
What do I do?
I... I've gotta go after her!
Are you gonna eat me, too?
So you can't talk without that receiver...
Can't you just talk to that big one?
Can you ask it to spit out Yuu?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
You might be little, but you might actually be
one of mankind's enemies...
Enemy...
An enemy, so what!
Yuu...
I'm coming right now!
If I lost Yuu, I'd...
Chi.
I'd...
Chi!
Yuu!
Are you okay?! You got eaten, but you're...
Somehow, once I tried, I got out...
What do you mean by tried...?
We do not eat living humans.
This voice...
This one's talking?
We do not possess vocal organs,
but we can decipher sound waves as language.
That is why we have used the equipment on this ship.
Juveniles are only capable of short-range
transmission, so these situations sometimes occur.
This song...
This is a part of our transmission signal
that the device received.
Just what are you guys, and why did you eat Yuu?
We only ingested the small device
that human possessed.
Oh, you're right!
Even some small devices from the generations of old
possess high amounts of energy.
We ingest thermally unstable materials
and dismantle them internally
into a stable, static state.
When this processing is complete,
the long period of life activity on Earth will end,
and the Earth will slumber once more.
When that time comes, we will hibernate as well.
Most of our activities in this city have come to an end.
All the weapons in the city...?
The city will slowly come to an eventual halt.
A halt?
We have surveyed most locations,
aside from those on the highest level,
and to our knowledge, you are
the only two humans still alive today.
Thank you for bringing this little one to us.
We must move together as a group.
Oh?
Why're you scared, cut?
You'll be fine. You've got lots of friends.
Goodbye.
Hey, Chi. It said the world's gonna end.
Yeah.
But...
Even if the world ends... I wouldn't really care.
As long as I have you, Yuu, I'm happy...
What?
Nothing.
So that singing voice was theirs.
I bet they got along with the feeling of hopelessness.
That's why they seem sad. It's a song about the End.
Maybe.
Friends
Ready, up!
Canned Goods
Good thing there were canned goods
in the cafeteria, huh, Chi?
Yeah, really.
What?
We're back to being just us.
For now... and forever more.
Are you lonely with it just being us?
You're lonely, right, Chi?
Wha-?! I thought you were lonely, Yuu, so I...
Oh, c'mon! You really aren't honest about how you feel.
You know, I-!
I'm not lonely.
I've got you, Chi.
Same.
Huh?
Nothing. Let's go. Hurry up and get on.
Okay.
So, where are we going?
To the highest level, right?
You're right. There might be something up there.
There might be nothing up there, though.
There's a level up there, so we're gonna go up there!
What're you going on about?
Alright. Which way should we go?
Hold on a sec!
Here we go.
That way!
The way the wind blows...
Though I guess that's not so bad.
Oh yeah, Chi, once we get to the top level,
let's go to the Moon next!
The Moon?
You're the one who said you wanted to go there, Chi.
I did?
But the Moon, huh? Could be nice.
It's a promise, then!
Yep.